<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>'Dancing with the Stars' returns with 2 Floridians: See week 1 scores</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/17/dancing-with-stars-premiere-scores-dances-voting-mormon-wives-alix-earle/86195620007/</link><description>ABC's hit reality dancing show"Dancing with the Stars" returned last nightto celebrate its 20th anniversary and its 34th season, with 14 contestants and their pro partners dancing to their "personal anthem."</description></item><item><title>FSU/Asolo Conservatory staging a diverse season of new, classic plays</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/09/18/asolo-conservatory-alum-takes-charge-as-programs-new-director/85958313007/</link><description>A lot has changed in the world and in theater education since Marcus Denard Johnson graduated with his Master of Fine Arts in acting from the FSU/Asolo Conservatory in 2008, but the mission and motivations remain the same as he takes over as director of the three-year graduate acting program.</description></item><item><title>Free outdoor festivals and more fun Sarasota area events this weekend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/18/best-things-to-do-sarasota-this-weekend-sept-18-21/86113145007/</link><description>Summer is almost over, and there’s plenty to get excited about this weekend in Sarasota — fromfootball seasontoOktoberfest, with local bars hosting Bavarian-style beer bashes, including one of my favorites, Calusa Brewing.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week: Cardinal Mooney volleyball player Brooke Gruhl</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/18/herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-winner-cardinal-mooney-volleyball-player-brooke-gruhl/86100385007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects girls athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Health Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Week 5 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/18/week-5-previews-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/86081796007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Thursday, Sept. 18 and Friday, Sept. 19, 2025</description></item><item><title>Parrish man injured in second deputy-involved shooting in 2 weeks</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/18/parrish-man-injured-in-second-deputy-involved-shooting-in-2-weeks/86201010007/</link><description>A domestic disturbance call in Parrishended in gunfirelate Sunday after a 29-year-old manpointed a handgun at Manatee County deputies, according to the sheriff’s office.</description></item><item><title>FWC staffer fired over Charlie Kirk Instagram post. What…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/18/fwc-employee-fired-charlie-kirk-post/86215250007/</link><description>The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission has fired an employee who reportedly shared an Instagram post joking about Charlie Kirk, the controversial conservative activist who was shot and killed on Sept. 10.</description></item><item><title>Florida displays double standard on vaccines…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/09/18/florida-gender-vaccines-ban/86208355007/</link><description>As both a parent and a pediatric registered nurse, I know how important it is to have access to medical care. That’s why I’m outraged by Florida’s latest decisionnot to mandate vaccinesfor school attendance.</description></item><item><title>What's not to like about National Cheeseburger Day deals?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/18/mcdonalds-cheeseburger-day-deals-freebies-list-locations/86215906007/</link><description>Today, Sept. 18, is National Cheeseburger Day.</description></item><item><title>Trump reacts to 'Jimmy Kimmel Live!' suspended. What did…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/09/18/trump-tweet-jimmy-kimmel-show-charlie-kirk-death/86215408007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpapplauded ABC's move to suspend"Jimmy Kimmel Live!"after the host commented on conservative reactions toCharlie Kirk's death.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week: ODA…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/18/herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-winner-oda-quarterback-edouard-chaput/86100349007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects boys athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Health Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Schools removes race, gender, disability from code of conduct</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/18/sarasota-county-schools-removes-race-gender-disability-protections-from-code-of-conduct/86189914007/</link><description>The Sarasota County School Board amended the student code of conduct on Tuesday to remove terms such as race, disability, gender identity, gender expression and sexual orientation.</description></item><item><title>Connor, School Board must avoid closing Sarasota County schools</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/18/sarasota-school-closing-free-speech/86211494007/</link><description>Sarasota County taxpayers are being asked to accept a plan that would have far-reaching effects on the local economy and property values.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County offers $30M for affordable housing projects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/18/sarasota-offers-30m-to-build-affordable-housing-developers-will-bid/86186659007/</link><description>Sarasota County will allow housing developers to bid for $30 million to build multifamily affordable housing as part of itsResilient SRQ hurricane recovery program.</description></item><item><title>Why are some Sarasota residents opposed to the changes at Selby Gardens?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/18/why-some-sarasota-residents-opposed-to-the-changes-at-selby-gardens/86219502007/</link><description>At its meeting on Monday, theSarasota City Commission heard an aggrieved party appeal from a Laurel Park residentseeking to halt Phase Two of Marie Selby Botanical Gardens' master plan because it would diminish her quality of life and property value.</description></item></channel></rss>