<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:31:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 3: 8 items to get rid of for sure</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/30/marni-jameson-walking-the-rightsizing-walk-part-3-the-power-purge/85813421007/</link><description>I am so embarrassed. All these columns and books I have written on downsizing and decluttering and my oh my, the mess I am in. Moving is the ultimate truth test. As I pack up the house my husband, DC, and I have lived in for eight years, box towers line the halls, packed and stacked like big city skylines. Each room coughs up its contents like a kid with consumption. I fear I may never see a clear counter again.</description></item><item><title>Who won 'Bachelor in Paradise' finale? See who got the cash prize</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/03/bachelor-paradise-finale-winners-jess-spencer-engaged-kat-dale-alexe-andrew/85952123007/</link><description>For the first time ever, two couples took home a significant chunk of change on the“Bachelor in Paradise” season 10 finale, which aired on Tuesday, Sept. 2.</description></item><item><title>When is Saturday Night Live coming back? See new comedian from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/04/saturday-night-live-season-october-peacock-streaming-florida/85968843007/</link><description>Live from New York, it's almost time forSaturday Night Live!</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend: Sept. 4-7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/04/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-sept-4-7/85866691007/</link><description>September may be Sarasota’s slowest month forlocal events, but there are still plenty of reasons to get out — includingthe start of the 2025 NFL season.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 3 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/04/week-3-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85852367007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Sept. 5, 2025</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/01/sarasota-herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-poll-for-aug-25-30/85851897007/</link><description>Each week the Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for theHerald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week pollsponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then votein the online pollto determine the Girls Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/01/sarasota-herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-poll-for-aug-25-30/85851674007/</link><description>Each week The Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for the Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then vote in the online poll to determine the Boys Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Three boys golfers shoot under par to lead…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/03/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-1-6-2025/85852537007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 1-6, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.If you don't see your results, have your coach email them tohtincoming@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Pics: Powerball, Mega Millions billion-dollar lottery…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/powerball-winner-florida-publix-michigan-kroger-california/85977057007/</link><description>Mega Millions and Powerball jackpots have reached$1 billion 13 times in history: Will the next Powerballdrawingresult in the latest billion-dollar lottery winner?</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man arrested for second-degree murder in death of girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/04/bradenton-man-arrested-for-second-degree-murder-in-death-of-girlfriend/85971535007/</link><description>Manatee County deputies arrested a 33-year-old on Sept. 3 for the second-degree murder of his girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>Community leaders have mixed emotions on SCS board appointment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/04/sarasota-school-board-seat-to-be-filled-by-rose-after-campaign-loss/85869351007/</link><description>Karen Rose’s return to the Sarasota County School Board — throughappointment by Gov. Ron DeSantisless than a year after she lost her seat in an election — is drawing mixed reactions from board members and education advocates who are weighing what her presence could mean for classrooms, families and district stability.</description></item><item><title>Battle on the right: Florida-based Newsmax takes Fox News to court</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/04/lawsuit-florida-based-newsmax-says-fox-news-froze-it-out-of-conservative-cable/85972120007/</link><description>Two of the largestright-wing TV outletsare battling their claims over being the nation's top right-leaning news source inMiami's federal court.</description></item><item><title>How may PGT's parent firm's plant closures affect Venice, Fort Myers?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/04/pgt-parent-company-plans-plant-closures-on-east-coast-of-florida/85957242007/</link><description>A “strategic realignment” of  Florida operations bythe parent company of PGT Innovationsmeans closure of window and door manufacturing plants in South Florida's Medley and Hialeah, with some of the work shifting to PGT facilities in Venice and Fort Myers.</description></item></channel></rss>