<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Van Wezel blends comedy, music, Broadway and legends for new season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/08/24/van-wezel-season-celebrates-musical-legends-on-stage/85574102007/</link><description>With three Broadway musicals celebrating the careers of pop music stars, a handful of living musical legends and tributes to other classic rock acts, the Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall’s 2025-26 season may resemble a nostalgic survey of changing musical styles over the last 60 years.</description></item><item><title>The eight college football coaches that start season on hot seat</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/08/25/college-football-coaches-hot-seat/85339704007/</link><description>Marcus Freeman’s seat at Notre Dame is an ice-cold tundra. The temperature ofClemson coach Dabo Swinney’s seat sits at absolute zero. Likewise with Georgia’s Kirby Smart, Indiana’s Curt Cignetti and Colorado’s Deion Sanders, among a few others.</description></item><item><title>Football recruiting: Which out-of-state programs are raiding Florida?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/08/25/florida-high-school-football-recruiting-texas-syracuse-notre-dame/85743580007/</link><description>It's no secret that Florida is ahotbed for recruiting talent.</description></item><item><title>Bowl projections: Expect playoff surprises ahead of unpredictable season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/08/25/college-football-bowl-projections-playoff-cfp/85676707007/</link><description>Forecasting the future can be intimidating when the world is chaotic and uncertain. Thankfully, making successful college football bowl predictions aren't as important as some of the biggest issues in the world.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for Aug. 24, 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/24/florida-lottery-results-sunday-august-24-2025/85811673007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, Aug. 24, 2025</description></item><item><title>The Patterson Foundation donates $500,000 to hurricane…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/24/patterson-foundation-donates-500000-to-sarasota-hurricane-recovery/85774649007/</link><description>As area residents prepare for the heart of hurricane season, The Patterson Foundation is also getting ready by once again seeding theSuncoast Disaster Recovery Fundwith a $500,000 contribution.</description></item><item><title>New Trader Joe's planned for Sarasota, sparks community…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/08/24/new-trader-joes-proposed-for-sarasota-how-a-second-location-could-solve-parking-nightmares-and-revit/85577632007/</link><description>Sunday morning in Sarasota often means a leisurely coffee, a stroll along the beach, and, for many, a trip to the grocery store. But not just any grocery store. For a certain segment of our community, a trip to Trader Joe’s is a pilgrimage. It’s an adventure marked by unique finds, friendly staff, and, often, a heroic effort to find a parking space.</description></item><item><title>Where is Tropical Storm Fernand? NHC tracks AL99. Next…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/24/fernand-hurricane-florida-track-path/85806187007/</link><description>Fernand has formed− what else is out in the Atlantic?</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: Find out what happened between Jaguars…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/24/jaguars-play-dolphins-in-south-florida-college-football-is-back-2md/83674675007/</link><description>The NFL preseason is over. Next stop: Week 1 after Labor Day. Here's what happened on the final weekend forFlorida's NFL teams.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Art Center Sarasota celebrates 100 years of making art accessible</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/08/25/art-center-sarasota-celebrates-100-years-of-making-art-accessible/85766975007/</link><description>Raised in Sarasota by a single mother, Katherine Ceaser’s first encounters with fine art came on school field trips. As a girl, she wandered museums and galleries with her class, drawn to bursts of color and form that suggested other possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Popular downtown Sarasota restaurant relocating with new name</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/25/tsunami-sushi-moving-sarasota-reopens-as-hanami/85722966007/</link><description>A fixture of downtown Sarasota's dining and drinking scene formore than a decade nowwill soon have a new location — and a new name.</description></item><item><title>Karen Rose returns to Sarasota School Board by DeSantis appointment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/25/karen-rose-returns-to-sarasota-school-board-by-desantis-appointment/85800977007/</link><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis hasappointed Karen Rose to the Sarasota County school board, despite her losing her seat in the 2024 primary election.</description></item><item><title>As Sarasota County faces budget shortfall, sheriff's budget looms as largest expense</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/25/sarasota-county-sheriff-slated-to-take-up-44-of-total-county-budget/85730865007/</link><description>Sarasota County commissioners signaled they were unhappy with the size of the sheriff’s budget request this year at abudget meetingwhere they forecast storm clouds on the fiscal horizon.</description></item></channel></rss>