<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:31:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Looking for Labor Day fun? 5 top events in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/28/best-things-to-do-sarasota-labor-day-weekend-2025/85779365007/</link><description>Looking forfun waysto spend the long Labor Day weekend? From the waters of Sarasota Bay to the streets of Englewood, the holiday brings a mix of family-friendly events and more adult-oriented entertainment.</description></item><item><title>10 best Sarasota sports bars for food, drinks, and game-day fun</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/29/sarasota-sports-bars-best-food-drinks/85833149007/</link><description>It has been a long, hot summer in Sarasota —especially for the local restaurant and bar scene— but things are about to pick up with the return of football season.</description></item><item><title>Who are the Sarasota, Manatee cross country runners to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/cross-country/2025/08/26/fhsaa-2025-high-school-cross-country-runners-sarasota-manatee-area/85575213007/</link><description>A freshman from Riverview High earned the spotlight as the area’s most dominant cross country runner in 2024. Madison Muller was the area’s top finisher as runner-up at the FHSAA Class 4A State Cross Country Championships at Apalachee Regional Park in Tallahassee.</description></item><item><title>Who are the high school boys swimmers to watch this…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/swimming-diving/2025/08/28/top-high-school-boys-swimmers-in-sarasota-manatee-area-for-2025/85715433007/</link><description>After the Sarasota boys swim team claimed the 2023 FHSAA Class 4A State Championship crown, the Sailors slipped to fourth place as a team in 2024. Right behind the Riverview Rams in third place.</description></item><item><title>Voters don't want Rose on School Board. Why won't Ron…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/28/desantis-sarasota-county-conservative-melania/85851808007/</link><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis recently appointedKaren Rose to the Sarasota County School Boardafter she lostre-election in 2024 to Liz Barker.</description></item><item><title>North Port, Sarasota and Bradenton Costco stores close…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/29/three-sarasota-manatee-costco-locations-are-closing-for-labor-day/85864230007/</link><description>If you need bulk hot dogs, drinks or a new BBQ for yourLabor Daycelebrations, you may want to hitCostcoearly.</description></item><item><title>Pops Orchestra to mark 50 years of Bradenton, Sarasota…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/29/pops-orchestra-offers-elton-john-four-seasons-country-tributes/85625989007/</link><description>The Pops Orchestra of Bradenton and Sarasota marks its 50th anniversary this season with an expanded schedule and added responsibilities for its conductor and artistic director, Robyn L. Bell.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/29/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-palmetto/85715078007/</link><description>We say farewell toAugustand kick offSeptember's new lineup of local events this week, which will feature some interesting live music offerings. For instance, we have not one but two concerts featuring regional Mexican music stars taking place Saturday at area fairground arenas: Robarts Arena in Sarasota Fairgrounds and Mosaic Arena at Manatee County Fairgrounds in Palmetto.</description></item><item><title>Water quality health advisory issued for Palma Sola Beach in Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/29/water-quality-health-advisory-issued-for-palma-sola-beach-in-manatee/85890958007/</link><description>Health authorities in Manatee County have again issued a water quality health advisory cautioning swimmers about high levels of fecal bacteria at Palma Sola South beach ahead of Labor Day weekend.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota family mourns 5-year-old who died after storm drain incident</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/29/sarasota-girl-swept-into-storm-drain-dies-after-days-in-hospital/85894094007/</link><description>A 5-year-old girlswept into a Sarasota storm drain by a main water breakon Sunday night, Aug. 24, has died..</description></item><item><title>Venice City Council in another development showdown with Pat Neal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/29/venice-council-developer-pat-vote-to-reject-development-settlement-for-vistera-mirrors-2024-decision/85784672007/</link><description>VENICE – For the second time in 16 months the Venice City Councildenied a request by developer Pat Neal to add 317 homes to his proposed Vistera development.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 2</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/29/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-2/85821227007/</link><description>We have survived Week 1 of the Florida high school football season, so let's play another.</description></item></channel></rss>