<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Want to visit a castle in Florida? St. Augustine is home to eight</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/local/2025/07/26/st-augustine-florida-castles-locations/85370364007/</link><description>St. Augustine is commonly known as theNation’s Oldest City.  Located between Northeast and East Central Florida, and just a short drive from Jacksonville, this ancient town holds the distinction of being the longest continuously inhabited European-founded city in the continental United States.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/07/25/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-sarasota-bradenton-punta-gorda/85242974007/</link><description>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte counties</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/24/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-july-24-27/85272193007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</description></item><item><title>Jack Nicklaus' former caddie on Senior PGA Tour now heads South Florida PGA</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/pga/2025/07/26/south-florida-pga-jack-nicklaus-eric-veilleux-bears-club/85357869007/</link><description>Eric Veilleux knows the game of golf is changing faster thanBryson DeChambeau’s downswing. This point was hammered home last month when Veilleux officially became the 24thpresident of the South Florida PGA during its annual meeting.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship volleyball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/21/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-volleyball-team-poll/85258207007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area volleyball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee all-time state football championship teams</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/24/looking-back-manatee-sarasota-all-time-football-championship-teams/84181976007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee all-time state football championship teams</description></item><item><title>Did you win $350 million? Check Powerball tickets for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/26/powerball-numbers-saturday-july-florida-lottery-winner/85392199007/</link><description>Will a$2 Powerball ticket make you a multimillionaire? As they say in the lottery business, “it could happen to you.”</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/26/florida-lottery-results-saturday-july-26-2025/85392422007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, July 26, 2025</description></item><item><title>School grades: more than just a letter, they're a…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/07/27/sarasota-manatee-school-grades-why-florida-does-annual-results-boost-local-communities-student-suc/84609493007/</link><description>The release of the Florida Department of Education's annual school grades is more than just an academic exercise; it's a vital public service that empowers our communities in Sarasota and Manatee counties. While the numbers might seem dry, these grades offer a crucial snapshot of our schools' health, fostering transparency, accountability and ultimately, improvement.</description></item><item><title>What does the 'One Big Beautiful Bill' mean for Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/real-estate/2025/07/27/huskey-what-does-one-big-beautiful-bill-mean-for-floridas-housing/85312298007/</link><description>How will the 'One Big Beautiful Bill' – a sweeping package of tax and other economic reforms – influence the state of residential housing across the country and in the Sunshine State?</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for July 27…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/27/florida-lottery-results-sunday-july-27-2025/85400803007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, July 27, 2025</description></item><item><title>I'm a Gold Star dad. Obama, Hillary, others must be held accountable.</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/07/26/obama-hillary-mueller-comey-russia/85373640007/</link><description>The Merriam-Webster Dictionary defines "treason" as "the offense of attempting by overt acts to overthrow the government of the state to which the offender owes allegiance . . . "</description></item><item><title>New Venice flood barrier done; work on city fishing pier begins soon</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/07/27/glass-seawall-in-venice-offers-a-new-view-of-tarpon-center-drive/85370150007/</link><description>VENICE – Progress on repairs to high profile areas following damage from hurricanes in 2023 and 2024 continues in Venice, with theglass flood barrier atop the new seawall at Tarpon Center Driveunveiled, whilesupplies are arriving to fix the Venice Municipal Fishing Pier.</description></item><item><title>What is the legacy of Dr. G. Duncan Finlay at Sarasota Memorial?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/27/collaborative-touch-of-late-ceo-helped-smh-outgrow-turbulent-period/85371192007/</link><description>What is the legacy of Dr. G. Duncan Finlay at Sarasota Memorial?</description></item><item><title>Wetlands in Sarasota, Manatee among those lost in Southwest Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/27/sarasota-manatee-wetlands-among-those-drained-for-development/84429461007/</link><description>It should come as no surprise that a huge swath ofour wetlands have vanishedfrom Southwest Florida in the last two decades.</description></item></channel></rss>