<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Explore Sarasota area’s September arts scene</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/08/27/whats-new-in-theater-concerts-museumon-stage-in-concert-and-on-exhibit-in-sarasota-area-in-september/85648161007/</link><description>No matter what the weather is like outside, the arts scene in Sarasota, Manatee and Charlotte counties in September is like the calm before the storm of much busier calendars. But the lighter schedule allows you time to explore new shows, plays, exhibitions and concerts indoors and outdoors in the region.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Music Festival director leaving after nine years</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/27/sarasota-music-festival-cut-to-two-weeks-for-2026-in-transition-period/85821633007/</link><description>After 61 years as one of the more prominent summer chamber music training programs, theSarasota Music Festivalis heading into transition period with some significant changes coming.</description></item><item><title>Who are the Sarasota, Manatee cross country runners to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/cross-country/2025/08/26/fhsaa-2025-high-school-cross-country-runners-sarasota-manatee-area/85575213007/</link><description>A freshman from Riverview High earned the spotlight as the area’s most dominant cross country runner in 2024. Madison Muller was the area’s top finisher as runner-up at the FHSAA Class 4A State Cross Country Championships at Apalachee Regional Park in Tallahassee.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 8 Volleyball Power Poll after Week 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/27/top-10-sarasota-manatee-high-school-volleyball-2025-team-rankings-after-week-1/85746153007/</link><description>The top spot in local high school volleyball is up for grabs this year.</description></item><item><title>Who are the high school girls swimmers to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/swimming-diving/2025/08/27/top-sarasota-manatee-high-school-girls-swimmers-2025/85715062007/</link><description>The Riverview High girls swim team is beginning to rival Thanksgiving when it comes to being reliable in the month of November. Just like the treasured family holiday, that’s the month the Rams annually win the FHSAA Class 4A state championship.</description></item><item><title>Will the city of Venice cut property taxes for the 2025-26 budget?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/27/city-of-venice-may-cut-properety-tax-rate-at-sept-9-budget-hearing/85832580007/</link><description>VENICE – The Venice City Council indicated a desire to adopt the reduce property tax rate to keep revenues flat when itapproves the 2025-26 fiscal year budget in September.</description></item><item><title>Got a minute? Here's the latest on what's happening in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/08/27/tropics-update-in-a-minute-tropical-storm-fernand-what-to-do-now-hurricane-supplies/85834908007/</link><description>Tight on time? This story is for you. It's an abbreviated, text view of what's happening in the tropics. Want more? Here's astory with more details,including photos and graphics.</description></item><item><title>What's the Florida forecast for Labor Day weekend?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/08/27/florida-labor-day-forecast-nws-radar-cold-front-rain-tropics-quiet/85835097007/</link><description>Labor Day weekend is almost here.</description></item><item><title>Southwest’s new seat refund policy may cost plus-size…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/27/southwest-airlines-updates-plus-size-passenger-extra-seat-refund-policy/85845477007/</link><description>Southwest Airlines is making more changes to theirtraditional seating policies. This time, the airline is making it a bit tougher forplus-size passengers to get refundedfor extra space.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy lull in tropical activity. It's not expected to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/08/27/tropics-update-accuweather-noaa-csu-when-quiet-ends-florida-impacts-preparations/85834978007/</link><description>You can thank Hurricane Erin, partially, for thequiet in the tropicsright now.</description></item><item><title>Florida declares war on Sarasota crosswalk art. Let's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/26/sarasota-florida-crosswalks-ban-desantis/85805539007/</link><description>Local control has long been a cornerstone of American governance – the idea that communities closest to the people should have the greatest say in their daily lives.</description></item><item><title>Big talk and tiny results: Corcoran's disastrous reign at New CollegeWilliam Rosenberg Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/27/new-college-spending-woke-athletes/85830702007/</link><description>In 2023New College of FloridaPresidentRichard Corcorandemanded a change to the school's mascot.</description></item><item><title>School Board picks local educator as new superintendent in district</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/27/manatee-graduate-chosen-as-superintendent-in-manatee-school-district/85846717007/</link><description>The School Board of Manatee County has selected Laurie Breslin as the district’s next superintendent following a 10-week search. Breslin is a Manatee Schools graduate and the mother of a current student. She is expected to step into the role in early September, pending contract approval.</description></item><item><title>What is cashless bail? Pres. Trump's executive order tackles cashless bail</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/08/27/what-is-cashless-bail-pres-trumps-executive-order-tackles-cashless-bail/85832068007/</link><description>President Donald Trump signed an executive order Monday, Aug. 25, to eliminate cashless bail citing public safety concerns and threatening to withhold state and federal funding to local and state governments that offer the bail option.</description></item><item><title>5 Sarasota restaurants opening, 2 closing — plus downtown fave moving</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/27/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing-downtown-fave-moving/85746714007/</link><description>From afine-dining favorite calling it quitsto adowntown sushi spot preparing for a big move, there’s been no shortage of restaurant news around Sarasota and Manatee counties this past month.</description></item></channel></rss>