<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 07:04:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The Big Beautiful Bill and its big opportunity for wealthy families</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/11/the-big-beautiful-bill-and-its-big-opportunity-for-wealthy-families/85402413007/</link><description>If you’ve ever felt like everything shifted overnight – tax laws, investment dynamics, retirement realities – you’re not imagining it. The Big Beautiful Bill, signed July 3, may seem like political theater, but for affluent families, it quietly reshapes how wealth is saved, transferred, and preserved.</description></item><item><title>See the winners of the Herald-Tribune's 2025 Sarasota-Manatee Top Workplaces</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/13/the-herald-tribunes-2025-sarasota-manatee-top-workplaces/85645985007/</link><description>How do you judge the quality of a workplace? Ask the experts: The employees.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>SSAA Previews: Bradenton Christian, ODA, Saint Stephen's, Sarasota Christian</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/15/2025-ssaa-football-previews-bradenton-christian-out-of-door-saint-stephens-sarasota-christian/85542079007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in the Sunshine State Athletic Association.</description></item><item><title>Nonprofit will test for 'forever chemicals' in North Port water</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/15/suncoast-waterkeeeper-launches-free-testing-for-forever-chemicals/85638893007/</link><description>NORTH PORT –Suncoast Waterkeeper is launching a free water testing programin the city, designed to raise awareness about the presence of “forever chemicals” in water.</description></item><item><title>New luxury real estate listing on St. Armands Circle hits the market</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/15/historic-st-armands-circle-home-hits-the-market-at-17-5-million/85677209007/</link><description>New luxury real estate listing on St. Armands Circle hits the market</description></item><item><title>Vote for best 2025 high school football team in Manatee…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/best-manatee-sarasota-area-2025-high-school-football-team-vote/85531382007/</link><description>High school football teams are getting ready to take the field for the first time in the 2025 season on Friday, Aug. 15.</description></item><item><title>Artist Series sets past favorites and rising stars for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/15/music-stars-and-emerging-artists-mark-artist-series-30th-season/85546679007/</link><description>Artist Series sets past favorites and rising stars for…</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/15/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-palmetto/85528088007/</link><description>As we enter mid-August, we're definitely in the slow time of the year for Sarasota area events, including live music. However, we still found five items for this week's concert picks installment, starting with a few notable tribute shows.</description></item><item><title>'More to come': Florida, ICE launch first TLH…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/15/florida-works-with-ice-to-fly-immigrants-from-tallahassee-airport/85678781007/</link><description>A "deportation flight" out of the Tallahassee International Airport is a Florida first, state Attorney General James Uthmeier says.</description></item><item><title>11,000 gallons of sewage spill into Hatchett Creek in Venice</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/15/workers-treat-spill-of-11000-gallons-of-sewage-in-hatchett-creek/85683258007/</link><description>VENICE – About 11,000 gallons of untreated wastewater spilled in Hatchett Creek early Friday near the intersection of East Venice and Warfield avenues after failure of a contractor’s pumping equipment as part of a city sewer pipeline project.</description></item><item><title>St. Thomas Aquinas survives Cardinal Mooney in Kickoff classic</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/cardinal-mooney-falls-to-st-thomas-aquinas-in-kickoff-classic/85657130007/</link><description>FORT LAUDERDALE — Cardinal Mooney wanted a chance to test their mettle against not only a top program in the state, but in the nation.</description></item><item><title>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now, before season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/15/best-legendary-sarasota-restaurants-and-bars-to-visit-now/84509634007/</link><description>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now, before season</description></item><item><title>Football Roundup: Venice cruises past Gadsden; Booker edges Manatee in ugly win</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/sarasota-manatee-football-roundup-for-fhsaa-ssaa-games-for-aug-15/85542153007/</link><description>Football Roundup: Venice cruises past Gadsden; Booker edges Manatee in ugly win</description></item></channel></rss>