<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:06:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sarasota Orchestra welcomes new music director to lead after 5 years</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/27/conductor-giancarlo-guerrero-ushers-in-new-era-at-sarasota-orchestra/86223888007/</link><description>After five years without a music director, the Sarasota Orchestra is welcoming a new artistic leader.</description></item><item><title>SBAC launches 2025–26 with “Harmonies of Sound and Vision” exhibit</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/28/suncoast-black-arts-collaborative-debuts-exhibit-at-sarasota-orchestra/86167948007/</link><description>Suncoast Black Arts Collaborative is kicking off its 2025–26 season with bold color and sound. The organization’s fifth Art Innovation Zone exhibition, “Harmonies of Sound and Vision: A Celebration of the Improvisational Spirit and Classical Elegance,” opens Sept. 28 at Sarasota Orchestra’s Harmony Gallery.</description></item><item><title>Alabama answers doubters, makes big splash in latest CFP projections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/09/28/miami-oregon-alabama-make-moves-in-latest-cfp-projections-playoff/86407567007/</link><description>We’ll remember thiswild weekendby one play above all else, and how it was a microcosm ofAlabama’s returnto the heart of the College Football Playoff race.</description></item><item><title>US loses Ryder Cup on home soil, could Tiger Woods be the next captain?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/pga/2025/09/28/ryder-cup-2025-us-europe/86404994007/</link><description>FARMINGDALE, NY — EuropeanRyder Cupcaptain Luke Donald sent the message early: We aim to write history.</description></item><item><title>World War II hero, one of last Tuskegee Airmen, dies at Sarasota home</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/26/george-hardy-tuskegee-airmen-world-war-ii-hero-dies-sarasota-home/86374419007/</link><description>World War II hero Lt. Col. George Hardy, the youngest of the Tuskegee Airmen pilots who fought during the war and helped pave the way for the integration of the armed forces, hasdied at his Sarasota home at age 100.</description></item><item><title>Townhome and condo prices are on the decline in Sarasota and Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/25/august-real-estate-report-indicates-transitional-period-for-suncoast/86313415007/</link><description>The Sarasota-Bradenton area's August real estate market points to a period of transition for the region, according to the most recentindustry report.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota makes waves as $130M Mote SEA Aquarium Opens…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/09/28/mote-sea-aquarium-opens-oct-8-in-sarasota-130m-marine-science-hub-marks-new-era-in-education-conserv/86244328007/</link><description>On October 8, Sarasota will witness the grand opening of theMote Science Education Aquarium— a $130 million facility that promises to redefine how our community engages with marine science, conservation and education.For Mote Marine Laboratory &amp; Aquarium, this moment marks not just the culmination of years of planning and construction, but also the beginning of a new chapter in its 70-year history as an independent nonprofit research institution.</description></item><item><title>'There's no place like Harvey' for Parrish ESE aide</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/28/vin-mannix-theres-no-place-like-harvey-for-parrish-ese-aide/85813945007/</link><description>Laron Cainhas only been at Harvey K-8 at Copperstone Elementary School since August, yet the ESE aide and paraprofessional has become a beloved member of the school family.</description></item><item><title>National Coffee Day deals in Florida. Dunkin, 7-11…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/28/national-coffee-day-florida-starbucks-dunkins-deals-freebies/86370035007/</link><description>Break out your travel mugs and get your route ready for tomorrow morning — we're preplanning ourcoffee order.</description></item><item><title>Daylight saving time ends soon, when we reset clocks to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/28/when-time-change-fall-back-daylight-savings-history/86364902007/</link><description>As fall rolls in, we are a little over a month away from falling back and changing our clocks to get one more hour of sleep and less daylight.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for Sept. 28, 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/28/florida-lottery-results-sunday-september-28-2025/86414240007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, Sept. 28, 2025</description></item><item><title>Vote for Sarasota, Manatee 2025 Midseason Volleyball Player of Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/09/25/sarasota-manatee-2025-midseason-high-school-volleyball-player-of-year-poll/86328407007/</link><description>The halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school volleyball season is upon us. As we head into the second half of the season, we selected Lakewood Ranch High player Ava Collins as our Midseason Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>100 years of Art Center Sarasota: Centennial season brings four shows</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/29/art-center-sarasota-launches-exhibitions-centennial-season-oct-9/86167352007/</link><description>Art Center Sarasota is celebrating its 100th year with a Centennial Season that opens Oct. 9. The yearlong slate of exhibitions and events honors the organization’s roots while spotlighting contemporary artists shaping Sarasota’s future.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County School Board won't succeed with sneaky time change</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/28/sarasota-school-board-bridget-ziegler/86389932007/</link><description>Recently the majority of theSarasota County School Boardvoted tochange the board’s meeting timeto 10 a.m., making it difficult for students, staff and working parents to attend.</description></item></channel></rss>