<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 23:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Create your own team in College Football 26 using the Team Builder</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/2025/07/08/college-football-26-team-builder-how-to-use/84504973007/</link><description>College Football 26 is back, and so too is the popular feature,Team Builder, with plenty of updates.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Woods, Miles Russell earn Junior Players Championship invitations</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/golf/pga-tour/2025/07/08/charlie-woods-miles-russell-junior-players-championship-tpc-sawgrass-pga-tour/84510438007/</link><description>Miles Russell, a Jacksonville Beach resident and the American Junior Golf Association’s top-ranked player, andCharlie Woodshave officially earned invitations to theJunior Players ChampionshipAug. 28-31 at the Players Stadium Course at TPC Sawgrass.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship softball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Check out these Prime Day deals on GoPro cameras, accessories</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/shop-amazon-prime-day-gopro-deals-camera-sales/84504498007/</link><description>Summer isall about adventureandexploring new places. For many, capturing moments that will last a lifetime includes your phone or camera.</description></item><item><title>My favorite Kasa Smart Plug is 42% off for Prime Day 🔌</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/amazon-prime-day-kasa-smart-home-deals/84499383007/</link><description>I don't think I have asupersmart home, but I have a few hacks that make it so much more streamlined. My biggest shoutout goes to theKasa Smart Plug. Seriously, these clever little things do basic tasks for me, like turning on my table lamps or holiday lights in the winter!</description></item><item><title>Prime Day has 20% off the crazy popular Coop adjustable pillows</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/coop-sleep-adjustable-pillow-amazon-prime-day-deals/84484207007/</link><description>Don't overcomplicate yoursleep routine; sometimes the best way to achieve a better night's rest is by swapping in a new set of sheets or adding a new pillow to your bedroom setup. And withAmazon's Prime Day 2025 salehappening now throughFriday, July 11, this week is the perfect time to stock up and save on coveted sleep accessories at a fraction of their usual cost—including best-sellers from Coop Sleep.</description></item><item><title>Gov. DeSantis lets three bills become law without…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/08/gov-desantis-lets-three-bills-become-florida-law-without-signature-non-compete-ken-griffin/84496316007/</link><description>For the first time since he took office in 2019, Gov. Ron DeSantis allowed legislation to become law without his signature.</description></item><item><title>Why did Cierra leave 'Love Island USA'? How to stream…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/08/how-when-watch-love-island-cierra-ortega-florida-when-finale-what-hideaway-baby-challenge/84502274007/</link><description>Thelast week of "Love Island USA" season sevenis bringing back some classic "Love Island" challenges and rewards.</description></item><item><title>Craving BBQ? Study declares 37 Florida cities best for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/08/florida-cities-barbecue-orlando-kansas-city-food/84485617007/</link><description>While Florida might be known more for its key lime pie, Cuban sandwiches and stone crabs, is it also a hot spot for barbeque fanatics?</description></item><item><title>Age verification for porn sites lawsuit dropped in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/08/lawsuit-against-florida-law-requiring-age-checks-on-porn-sites-dropped/84507875007/</link><description>The Free Speech Coalition dropped alawsuit challenging a Florida law requiring age verificationfor adult websites after theU.S. Supreme Courtupheld asimilar Texas lawmid-June.</description></item><item><title>Where does Florida stand on its latest mass immigration…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/08/florida-mass-deportation-legal-alligator-alcatraz-open/84502215007/</link><description>So far, more than 1,000 migrants have been detained under the state’s aggressive“Operation Tidal Wave,”a crackdown that officials say could become a model for federal immigration enforcement. The operation gained traction in May after a joint ICE raid led to over 100 arrests at construction sites in Tallahassee.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County announces leader of forthcoming Stormwater Department</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/08/sarasota-county-names-director-of-new-stormwater-department/84498355007/</link><description>Sarasota County announces leader of forthcoming Stormwater Department</description></item><item><title>Booker, Sarasota High among Sarasota Schools that improved grades</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/07/08/school-grades-2025-sarasota-county-maintains-top-state-ranking/84502203007/</link><description>Booker, Sarasota High among Sarasota Schools that improved grades</description></item><item><title>Nathan Benderson Park doesn't need massive, wasteful sports facilityTerry Galvin Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/08/benderson-park-rowing-sports-money/84505188007/</link><description>I have loved and supportedNathan Benderson Parksince before it held its first event more than 15 years ago.</description></item><item><title>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police Chief</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/08/josh-cramer-officially-replaces-controversial-melanie-bevan-as-chief/84507671007/</link><description>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police Chief</description></item></channel></rss>