<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 18:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Get the new Millie Bobby Brown x Crocs Unfurgettable Clog for fall</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/08/14/new-crocs-unfurgettable-collection-millie-bobby-brown/85667152007/</link><description>Crocs knows how to nail a good collab. FromKrispy Kremeto "The Summer I Turned Pretty," the iconic footwear brand has been teaming up with some heavy hitters this summer. Oh, and Millie Bobby Brown just entered chat.</description></item><item><title>Get ready for the U.S. Open by saving 30% on Nike tennis shoes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/08/16/jannik-sinner-carlos-alcaraz-nike-tennis-shoe-discount-30-percent/85681612007/</link><description>Tennis' besthead to NYC for the U.S. Open, the final major of the season.</description></item><item><title>Mega Millions winning numbers for Aug. 15: $198 million jackpot</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/money/lottery/2025/08/15/mega-millions-winning-numbers/85683639007/</link><description>TheMega Millionsjackpot rose to $198 million for the drawing on Friday, Aug. 15, after no one matched all the winning numbers in the drawing on Tuesday, Aug. 12.</description></item><item><title>NFL Sunday Ticket 2025: Price breakdown, discounts, what to know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/nfl/2025/08/16/nfl-sunday-ticket-youtube-tv-2025/85573272007/</link><description>The kickoff ofthe NFL regular seasonis rapidly approaching and if you are a football junkie or a fan of an out-of-town team, you will want to get connected withNFL Sunday Ticket.</description></item><item><title>Erin expected to strengthen into Category 4 hurricane with 140-mph winds</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/15/hurricane-erin-path-spaghetti-models-tracker-florida/85670066007/</link><description>In a rush? Get an abbreviated, text view of what's happening withHurricane Erin.</description></item><item><title>Here's a quick look on what you should know about Hurricane Erin</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/15/hurricane-erin-quick-answers-questions-florida-impact-tracker-path/85670207007/</link><description>Tight on time? This story is for you. It's an abbreviated, text view of what's happening withTropical Storm Erin.Click here for more detailsand to see thelatest spaghetti models.</description></item><item><title>Haters won't admit Trump's success and popularity</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/15/trump-immigrants-inflation-safety-fbi-doge-pelletier/85657736007/</link><description>The truth is thatPresident Donald Trumpis making life for ALL Americans better.</description></item><item><title>Greater Sarasota Chamber of Commerce hosts annual Leadership Awards</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/11/greater-sarasota-chamber-of-commerce-hosts-annual-leadership-awards/85404410007/</link><description>TheGreater Sarasota Chamber of Commercewill host the annual Celebrate Outstanding Leadership Awards on Aug. 13 from 11:30 a.m. to 1 p.m. at Michael’s On East in Sarasota.</description></item><item><title>The Big Beautiful Bill and its big opportunity for wealthy families</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/11/the-big-beautiful-bill-and-its-big-opportunity-for-wealthy-families/85402413007/</link><description>If you’ve ever felt like everything shifted overnight – tax laws, investment dynamics, retirement realities – you’re not imagining it. The Big Beautiful Bill, signed July 3, may seem like political theater, but for affluent families, it quietly reshapes how wealth is saved, transferred, and preserved.</description></item><item><title>See the winners of the Herald-Tribune's 2025 Sarasota-Manatee Top Workplaces</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/13/the-herald-tribunes-2025-sarasota-manatee-top-workplaces/85645985007/</link><description>How do you judge the quality of a workplace? Ask the experts: The employees.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>11,000 gallons of sewage spill into Hatchett Creek in Venice</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/15/workers-treat-spill-of-11000-gallons-of-sewage-in-hatchett-creek/85683258007/</link><description>VENICE – About 11,000 gallons of untreated wastewater spilled in Hatchett Creek early Friday near the intersection of East Venice and Warfield avenues after failure of a contractor’s pumping equipment as part of a city sewer pipeline project.</description></item><item><title>New College of Florida attracts top educatorsDavid Rohrbacher Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/16/new-college-educators-students/85675977007/</link><description>If you want to see the future of higher education, don’t look to theIvy League. Look to the shores of Sarasota Bay.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota’s performing arts center trails other major local projects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/16/sarasota-performing-arts-center-behind-other-projects-in-progress/85673126007/</link><description>Seven years ago, Sarasota unveiled an ambitious plan for its bayfront — a reimagined 53-acre waterfront park crowned by a state-of-the-art performing arts center to replace the agingVan Wezel, funded equally by private donations and public dollars.</description></item></channel></rss>