<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:05:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>'Golden' cast joins 'Bachelor in Paradise' after dramatic rose ceremony</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/16/golden-bachelor-in-paradise-how-to-watch-florida-reality-tv/85204395007/</link><description>Bachelor Nation is buzzing with opinions about thetenth season of "Bachelor in Paradise,"which premiered last week to much less online fanfare than is typical for the franchise.</description></item><item><title>Asolo Rep delays Billy Joel-Twyla Tharp musical for a year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/07/16/asolo-rep-to-stage-come-from-away-in-fall-and-delay-billy-joel-show/85206074007/</link><description>Asolo Rep delays Billy Joel-Twyla Tharp musical for a year</description></item><item><title>Here's how Kai Trump fared in first round of tournament at Lost City</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/golf/2025/07/16/kai-trump-golf-tournament-score-palm-beach/85240902007/</link><description>Kai Trumpis in contention this week at a South Florida PGA junior golf tournament in Palm Beach County.</description></item><item><title>No 'prosthetic arm' for DJ Lagway: What the UF QB said about his health</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/07/16/florida-football-qb-dj-lagway-says-hes-making-all-the-throws-during-otas/85201820007/</link><description>ATLANTA ―Florida footballsophomore quarterback D.J. Lagway gave himself a clean bill of health heading into the 2025 season.</description></item><item><title>Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship baseball team?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/14/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-baseball-team-poll/84537090007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Perseids aren't only meteors this summer: What will be…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/nation/2025/07/16/perseid-meteor-shower-2025/85235670007/</link><description>If it feels like it's been a while since you've been able towatch a stunning meteor showerlight up the night sky, you're in luck.</description></item><item><title>Storm forecast: 93L a flood threat amid relatively…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hurricane/2025/07/16/hurricane-forecast-93l-a-florida-mississippi-louisiana-flood-threat/85198136007/</link><description>The summer of floodingand irritant-level tropical threatsrolls on like a big wheel through a Georgia cotton field, with this week’s focus on adisorganized disturbance in the northern Gulf.</description></item><item><title>Are tickets on sale for Halloween Horror Nights 2025…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/16/halloween-horror-nights-ticket-frequent-fear-pass-prices-universal-orlando/85204281007/</link><description>While it's still technically summer, the pull of spooky season is slowly creeping up atFlorida's theme parks.</description></item><item><title>New Florida CFO is a poker player. Here's what he played</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/16/new-florida-cfo-blaise-ingoglia-internationally-ranked-poker-player/85241161007/</link><description>Florida'snew Chief Financial Officeris used to handling money. Sometimes he's playing cards over it.</description></item><item><title>Will Congress send bills to Trump to make daylight…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/16/sunshine-protection-act-daylight-saving-time-permanent-florida-bills-status/85239033007/</link><description>Will this be the year when we end the twice-annual changing of our clocks?</description></item><item><title>Flesh-eating bacteria case in Manatee County. What to know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/16/vibrio-vulnificus-flesh-eating-bacteria-manatee-county-florida/85241804007/</link><description>Eleven people in Florida, including one in Manatee County, have contracted Vibrio vulnificus, the so-called"flesh-eating" bacteriain 2025.</description></item><item><title>Trump co-campaign manager, top pollster join Gruters CFO campaign</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/16/trump-desantis-political-conflict-flares-in-florida-cfo-race/85239866007/</link><description>Even the race to see who will run Florida's lesser known Department of Financial Services isn't immune to wider political battles.</description></item><item><title>Less than an inch of rain forecast for Sarasota Manatee as invest</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/16/low-pressure-system-moving-west-less-rain-expected-through-friday/85244000007/</link><description>Invest 93Lcontinued Wednesday morning on its path across Florida, but its expected impacts on the Sarasota, Manatee area for the next two days appear limited.</description></item><item><title>Venice restaurant closing this month after 45 years of memories</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/16/venice-restaurant-wee-blew-inn-permanently-closing/85215457007/</link><description>One of Venice’s oldest restaurants has announced it’sclosing for good.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Art Museum highlights Miami artist’s peaceable kingdom</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/07/16/sarasota-art-museum-hosts-site-specific-exhibit-by-miami-artist/84497356007/</link><description>Chris Friday is a Miami-based, African American artist. “Where We Never Grow Old” at Sarasota Art Museum is her first solo museum exhibition. Her ageless realm exists on many levels in her site-specific installation, which is a loving celebration of the artist’s family. It’s also a memory palace of Friday’s cultural history. And a defiant refusal to see that history erased.</description></item></channel></rss>