<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>'Golden' cast joins 'Bachelor in Paradise' after dramatic rose ceremony</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/16/golden-bachelor-in-paradise-how-to-watch-florida-reality-tv/85204395007/</link><description>Bachelor Nation is buzzing with opinions about thetenth season of "Bachelor in Paradise,"which premiered last week to much less online fanfare than is typical for the franchise.</description></item><item><title>Shark Week 2025 kicks off this weekend: Here's what to know, how to watch</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/17/when-shark-week-air-schedule-discovery-shows-how-where-watch-stream/85236543007/</link><description>Summer in Floridameans more shark activityin the oceans that surround the Sunshine State … And more sharks on TV.</description></item><item><title>The two SEC teams that could rattle the College Football Playoff committee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/sec/2025/07/17/college-football-playoff-florida-oklahoma/85193201007/</link><description>Billy Napierchuckled when I asked him aboutFlorida’s schedule. What else could the Gators coach do but laugh?</description></item><item><title>Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship baseball team?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/14/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-baseball-team-poll/84537090007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>What are the 'Good Trouble' protests? See events across Florida today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/17/good-trouble-lives-on-protests-florida-donald-trump-john-lewis/85236352007/</link><description>Over 50 cities in Florida are hosting events today toprotest the Trump administrationunder the name“Good Trouble Lives On."</description></item><item><title>Rule changes by Florida education officials draw First…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/16/florida-education-officials-change-requirements-for-media-specialists/85244891007/</link><description>Florida's State Board of Educationvoted to reduce competency requirements for educational media specialists, who manage library books in schools – and who some say are defenders of students'First Amendment rights.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/16/florida-lottery-results-wednesday-july-16-2025/85252563007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Wednesday, July 16, 2025</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk wants to start a third US political party…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/07/17/america-elon-musk-third-political-party-vote-elections/85100293007/</link><description>Question:Tech billionaire and former Trump Administration official Elon Musk has promised to fund his own “America Party”instead of President Donald Trump’s Republican Party. But can athird political partysucceed in the United States?</description></item><item><title>Gay pride crosswalks are symbols of progress. FL wants…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/07/17/florida-gay-pride-crosswalk-ban-traffic-safety-orlando-lgbtq/85208628007/</link><description>It’s not a secret that Florida goes out of its way to demean and discriminate against itsLGBTQresidents.</description></item><item><title>Florida ranks 2nd in most tick-infested states list…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/17/ticks-florida-bites-infested-states/85237412007/</link><description>Be careful where you walk. Emergency room visits related totick bites have spiked in 2025, reaching their highest point nationwide in five years, according to the CDC'sTick Bite Data Tracker.</description></item><item><title>Trump co-campaign manager, top pollster join Gruters CFO campaign</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/16/trump-desantis-political-conflict-flares-in-florida-cfo-race/85239866007/</link><description>Trump co-campaign manager, top pollster join Gruters CFO campaign</description></item><item><title>Less than an inch of rain forecast for Sarasota Manatee as invest</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/16/low-pressure-system-moving-west-less-rain-expected-through-friday/85244000007/</link><description>Invest 93Lcontinued Wednesday morning on its path across Florida, but its expected impacts on the Sarasota, Manatee area for the next two days appear limited.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state volleyball championship teams</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/17/all-time-list-of-every-sarasota-manatee-fhsaa-volleyball-championship-team/84287388007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state volleyball championship teams</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/17/best-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton/84636836007/</link><description>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</description></item></channel></rss>