<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 16:04:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/10/best-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton-venice-fl/84471720007/</link><description>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</description></item><item><title>10 essential new Sarasota restaurants that live up to the hype</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/11/best-new-sarasota-restaurants-essentials-that-are-worth-the-hype/83648754007/</link><description>10 essential new Sarasota restaurants that live up to the hype</description></item><item><title>Nordstrom Anniversary Sale is open to everyone with up to 50% off</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/12/shop-nordstrom-anniversary-sale/84550581007/</link><description>Get ready,Nordstrom shoppers! TheNordstrom Anniversary Saleis officially live now throughSunday, August 3. If you're familiar with this annual sale, you know how quickly in-demand items sell out. Our pro-tip? Shop early to grab your favorite pieces before they're gone.</description></item><item><title>Amazon has a 100-foot Flexzilla hose for under $70 today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/11/prime-day-deal-flexzilla-garden-hose/84546285007/</link><description>BeforeAmazon’s Prime Day 2025 saleendstonight, July 11, the 100-foot Flexzilla hose is 37% off, bringing the original $109.99 price down to just $69.</description></item><item><title>↠ Popular still-live Prime Day deals worth clicking today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/11/last-chance-amazon-prime-day-deals-sales/84448163007/</link><description>What day is it? Is it still July? After four product-packed days, we've reached the final countdown:Amazon Prime Day 2025technically endedFriday, July 11, but there are a few still-live deals you can shop. TheUSA TODAY Shopping teamhas been tracking all the most popular price cuts, the deepest discounts and yes, some of the most unexpected finds from the big sale.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/10/all-time-list-of-every-sarasota-manatee-fhsaa-baseball-championship-team/84287441007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state…</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/07/11/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-englewood-anna-maria-island-palmetto/84430282007/</link><description>Like many weeksin Julyandthe Sarasota area's off-season, this week's concert picks largely consist of talented musicians who call Florida home. However, we do kick things off with a reggae musician from California, who visits the area while on tour with a group from Maryland.</description></item><item><title>MLB Draft: Venice High grad Marek Houston projected to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/mlb/2025/07/11/2025-mlb-draft-first-round-marek-houston-wake-forest-shortstop-venice-graduate/84518614007/</link><description>After his senior season on the Venice High baseball team, Marek Houston received an invitation to attend the Major League Baseball Draft Combine in San Diego.</description></item><item><title>Early peek into governor campaign war chests: Donalds…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/11/florida-governor-campaign-fundraising-donalds-rakes-it-in-jolly-lags/84536816007/</link><description>Since late-April, when newly mintedDemocrat David Jollyentered the 2026 Florida governor’s race, he’s raised about $1 million through his political committee and main campaign account.</description></item><item><title>15th Sarasota Improv Festival features new acts and old favorites</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/07/12/fst-marks-15-years-of-spontaneous-laughter-at-sarasota-improv-fest/84444733007/</link><description>15th Sarasota Improv Festival features new acts and old favorites</description></item><item><title>Manatee County hosting housing services, legal clinic July 16</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/12/manatee-county-hosting-housing-services-legal-clinic-july-16/84536812007/</link><description>In an effort to makehousing servicesmore accessible to residents experiencing hardship, Manatee County Community Development officials are hosting an information session and legal assistance clinic to help residents with housing support.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee recreational fishing pros eligible for storm aid</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/12/grants-available-for-recreational-fishing-pros-hit-by-24-hurricanes/84545400007/</link><description>Suncoast Waterkeeper and Tampa Bay Waterkeeper are teaming up to provide grants up to $1,000 to local recreational fishing professionals impacted byhurricanes Helene and Milton.</description></item><item><title>Mira Mar redevelopment moves forward with Sarasota Commission OK</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/12/rezone-clears-the-way-for-18-story-towers-on-mira-mar-site/84538363007/</link><description>Mira Mar redevelopment moves forward with Sarasota Commission OK</description></item></channel></rss>