<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>NBA legend Shaq wants to retire to The Villages in Florida: Here's why</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/28/shaq-podcast-mike-tyson-where-the-villages-what-loofah-code-florida/85370024007/</link><description>Retired NBA legend and former FloridianShaquille O’Neal, 53,wants to retire to Ocala, Florida, for an eye-opening reason: The rumors about The Villages that have circulated among Floridians for years.</description></item><item><title>Arts groups highlight new work in August in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/07/28/art-exhibits-new-plays-and-classics-open-in-sarasota-area-in-august/84539109007/</link><description>Arts groups highlight new work in August in Sarasota area</description></item><item><title>Who has the best college football stadium? We ranked the top 25</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/07/28/college-football-stadium-rankings-top-25/85269960007/</link><description>Talent and coaching will take you places in college football, but only so far. Thebest programs in the Bowl Subdivision playfor conference and national championships in part because of mesmerizing home-field advantages that have etched many Power Four and Group of Five venues into the very fabric of the sport.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant Classic will be stuck between four high-profile events in 2026</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/pga/2025/07/28/pga-tour-cognizant-classic-2026-schedule/85373480007/</link><description>A shift in the calendar has helped the Cognizant Classic in the Palm Beaches boost its field the last two years.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship football team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/28/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-football-team-poll/85345091007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area football teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Want a new home on the Suncoast? It likely comes with developer debt</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/28/want-a-new-home-on-the-suncoast-it-likely-comes-with-developer-debt/85376802007/</link><description>Want a new home on the Suncoast? It likely comes with developer debt</description></item><item><title>First Amendment: What to know about Trump's lawsuit…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/28/first-amendment-issues-in-trumps-lawsuit-against-wall-street-journal/85342527007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trump'slawsuit against the Wall Street Journal, filed in South Florida, raises potential First Amendment concerns regarding freedom of the press, speech and accountability.</description></item><item><title>Which lakes house the most snakes in Florida? Study…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/28/florida-snakes-lakes-reptiles-worldatlas-everglades-pythons/85353083007/</link><description>Reptiles and Florida might as well be synonymous, especially when it comes to ourslithering neighbors.</description></item><item><title>Can you buy a car at Costco in Florida? Here’s what to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/28/costco-sells-cars-auto-sales-florida/85402615007/</link><description>You knowCostcohas stacks of bulk snacks, monster packages of cheap meat, discounted clothing, new glasses, lawn furniture, electronics and the best value for food court hot dogs and pizza anywhere. But what if you want to buy a car?</description></item><item><title>Extreme heat warnings, watches, advisories issued for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/severe/2025/07/28/extreme-heat-warnings-watches-florida-heat-index-counties-list/85402610007/</link><description>If you thought it was hot last week, get ready for some unwelcome news, especially today, July 28.</description></item><item><title>What were EU tariffs before Trump? What to know after…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/28/eu-us-tariffs-before-trump/85402668007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpreached a trade deal with theEuropean Unionduring histrip to Scotlandover the July 27 weekend.</description></item><item><title>New local spot serves Jersey-style bagels, pork roll and sandwiches</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/28/new-bradenton-restaurant-serves-jersey-style-bagels-sandwiches-open/85373328007/</link><description>New local spot serves Jersey-style bagels, pork roll and sandwiches</description></item><item><title>Florida law could allow WSJ to 'SLAPP' Donald Trump with attorney fees</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/28/florida-anti-slapp-law-may-cost-trump-attorney-fees-in-wsj-lawsuit/85341726007/</link><description>A lawcentral to First Amendment protections in Florida may apply in a federal lawsuit fromPresident Donald Trumpagainst theWall Street Journal, which came after a report about a birthday letter from Trump to convicted sex offenderJeffrey Epstein.</description></item><item><title>Donors must back up empty promises on Sarasota's Nathan Benderson ParkPat Rounds and Bill Zoller Guest columnists</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/28/sarasota-rowing-sports-orioles/85393730007/</link><description>Donors must back up empty promises on Sarasota's Nathan Benderson ParkPat Rounds and Bill Zoller Guest columnists</description></item><item><title>Police: Fishing trip ends with Holmes Beach man nearly killing wife</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/crime/2025/07/28/holmes-beach-husband-leaves-wife-for-dead-in-gulf-twice/85375424007/</link><description>Police: Fishing trip ends with Holmes Beach man nearly killing wife</description></item></channel></rss>