<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:20:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Ozzy Osbourne: Where to stream his MTV reality show for free</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/23/stream-osbournes-free-amazon-prime-how-when-watch-ozzy/85335302007/</link><description>Heavy metal legendOzzy Osbourne diedat 76 years old yesterday, about five years after publicly announcing a Parkinson’s disease and emphysema diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Florida State QB doubles down on Alabama trash talk ahead of opener</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/acc/2025/07/23/florida-state-thomas-castellanos-comments-alabama/85339747007/</link><description>Thomas Castellanos is standing firm.</description></item><item><title>FHSAA to review recruiting bylaws after Teddy Bridgewater suspension</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/23/fhsaa-recruiting-bylaws-teddy-bridgewater-suspension/85339492007/</link><description>The Florida Department of Education has formally taken steps to address fairness and competition in the Florida High School Athletic Association.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell subpoenaed to testify behind bars on Epstein case</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/23/ghislaine-maxwell-subpoenaed-to-testify-before-congressional-committee/85346120007/</link><description>Amid a day of blockbuster disclosures in the case of the lateconvicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein, a U.S. House committeeissued a subpoenafor Epstein accomplice Ghislaine Maxwell to appear at a deposition in the federal women's prison in Tallahassee, Florida, where she is serving her20-year sentence.</description></item><item><title>Cook Out is coming to Florida. Here's where new…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/23/cook-out-restaurants-florida-locations/85335201007/</link><description>Florida is finally, officially invited to join a 10-state cookout.Cook Out, probably the only fast food restaurant where you can order a quesadilla as a side to your cheeseburger, is expanding to the Sunshine State after 36 years of service andmore than 350 locationsthroughout the southeast.</description></item><item><title>Court says couple can sue over gun range noise in Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/07/23/florida-couples-gun-range-noise-lawsuit-gets-green-light/85345727007/</link><description>TALLAHASSEE — An appeals court July 23 allowed an Okaloosa County couple to pursue a lawsuit over noise from a neighboring gun range, saying a 1999 state law aimed at shielding gun ranges from liability violated the couple’s constitutional rights.</description></item><item><title>Did you win $325 million? Check Powerball tickets for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/23/powerball-numbers-wednesday-july-florida-lottery-winner/85322117007/</link><description>Will a$2 Powerball ticket make you a multimillionaire? As they say in the lottery business, “it could happen to you.”</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/21/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-volleyball-team-poll/85258207007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area volleyball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>North Port leaders decide big new police station would be too costly</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/07/23/north-port-commissioners-seek-to-downsize-proposed-police-station/85315422007/</link><description>North Port leaders decide big new police station would be too costly</description></item><item><title>50+ things to do in August in Sarasota, Bradenton, Venice, Punta Gorda</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/23/50-things-to-do-in-august-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice-punta-gorda/84533841007/</link><description>50+ things to do in August in Sarasota, Bradenton, Venice, Punta Gorda</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County should rethink risky Benderson park project | Letter</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/07/23/park-sarasota-rowing-sports/85317738007/</link><description>I like and respect Louis Kosiba, a Nathan Benderson Park Conservancy board member who volunteers to work at Nathan Benderson Park events.</description></item><item><title>NPPD Chief Todd Garrison joins Florida Criminal Justice Commission</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/23/north-port-police-chief-joins-florida-criminal-justice-commission/85339807007/</link><description>NPPD Chief Todd Garrison joins Florida Criminal Justice Commission</description></item></channel></rss>