<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>New Urbanite Theatre season explores identity, ethics and family</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/09/06/sarasotas-urbanite-theatre-gets-bold-and-intimate-for-12th-season/85629533007/</link><description>With no more than 70 seats available for some performances, Urbanite Theatre operates Sarasota's smallest professional theater venue on a tighter budget for each production than most other companies in the area.</description></item><item><title>Big Sarasota festival reveals 2026 headliners, celebrity guest</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/06/thunder-by-the-bay-sarasota-festival-reveals-2026-headliners-celebrity-guest/85975593007/</link><description>One ofSarasota's largest annual eventshas announced next year's headlining entertainment, a celebrity guest and a (slightly) new name.</description></item><item><title>10 biggest concerts and comedy shows coming to Florida this fall</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/09/08/biggest-concerts-comedy-shows-florida-october-december-2025/85957352007/</link><description>As we near the end of September and the first day of fall, thesummer blockbuster concert and comedy tour seasonwill soon come to a close too, yet that doesn't mean a shortage of big names visiting Florida through the rest of 2025.</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: USF drops Gators; Hunter, Jaguars roll to victory</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/09/07/usf-upsets-gators-jaguars-roll-in-travis-hunters-debut-2md/85197486007/</link><description>It was a bad weekend for Gators and Dolphins fans, but most every other state NFL and college team was made happy.</description></item><item><title>SEC Power Rankings: Gators sink near Swamp bottom, MSU exits cellar</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/columns/2025/09/08/sec-power-rankings-gators-sink-near-swamp-bottom-msu-exits-cellar/85518560007/</link><description>Mississippi State has spent a hot minute at the bottom of our SEC Power Rankings, but a stunning upset ofArizona Statehas given us a new face in the cellar. Meanwhile, theFlorida Gatorsjust barely avoided being the new occupants after a home loss to South Florida. With little movement at the top this week, the shake-up is closer to the bottom. Onto the rankings!</description></item><item><title>Adams: Oklahoma soars in Big Ten/SEC top 25. Tennessee passes Georgia</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/columnists/university-of-tennessee/john-adams/2025/09/08/big-ten-sec-top-25-tennessee-oklahoma-georgia-lsu-oregon/85857695007/</link><description>My crowded inbox included an email from someone who couldn’t understand why I would have onlyBig TenandSEC teamsin my top 25.</description></item><item><title>The Post's outspoken long-running news columnist has run…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/09/07/columnist-frank-cerabino-retires-after-34-years-at-palm-beach-post/85646332007/</link><description>In the mid-90s, Ron Howard directed a gritty movie about the inner workings of a daily newspaper.</description></item><item><title>USF QB commit, star-studded defense lift Armwood over…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/07/florida-high-school-football-armwood-tampa-bay-tech-rhys-brush/85993617007/</link><description>Armwood football is one of the more complete teams in the state, and highlighted that fact with a resounding 28-7 win over rival Tampa Bay Tech on Sept. 5.</description></item><item><title>Invest 91L formation chances dissipate. NHC watching 2…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/07/national-hurricane-center-invest-91l-tropical-update-florida/86026224007/</link><description>Chances of formation for a tropical wave over the Atlantic, formerlyInvest 91L, dissipated on Sept. 6, according to theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton argument turns deadly in fatal stabbing…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/07/bradenton-fight-ends-in-fatal-stabbing-man-arrested-by-deputies/86028587007/</link><description>Manatee County Sheriff’s Office deputieshave arrested a 39-year-old manin a fatal Bradenton stabbing of another man on Sept. 7.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Venice residents deserve tax relief. We must provide it.</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/07/venice-property-taxes-insurance/86000420007/</link><description>Thecity of Venicestands at a crossroads.</description></item><item><title>North Port rejects hiring freeze during first public hearing on budget</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/08/north-port-commission-moves-331-3-million-budget-to-second-hearing/85885606007/</link><description>NORTH PORT – The North Port City Commission made no appreciable change to the projected $331.3 million budget for the 2025-26 fiscal yearat its first public hearing on the spending plan on Sept. 4.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis plan excluded from consideration in property tax overhaul</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/08/desantis-plan-sidelined-in-house-tax-reform-committee-talks/85978152007/</link><description>With aFlorida House committeetaking its first steps toward overhauling how muchFloridians pay in property taxes,“everything is on the table,” the panel’s co-chair said.</description></item><item><title>Ex-insider pushes New College privatization in break with DeSantis</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/08/privatization-push-emerges-at-new-college-by-ex-insider/85993497007/</link><description>A former senior member ofNew College of FloridaPresident Richard Corcoran’s administration is leading a push to privatize the institution — a dramatic turn for a conservative insider once tapped to help carry out Gov. Ron DeSantis’ ideological overhaul of the Sarasota-based school.</description></item></channel></rss>