<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>5 closed Sarasota restaurants we still miss</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/12/closed-sarasota-restaurants-we-still-miss/86096114007/</link><description>From beloved diners to fine‑dining landmarks, Sarasota hassaid goodbye to some unforgettable restaurants in recent years.</description></item><item><title>Iconic Sarasota restaurant open since 1987 closing for remodel</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/10/sarasota-restaurant-michaels-on-east-remodel-closure/86055608007/</link><description>One of Sarasota’s top fine-dining icons — renowned as a premier special-occasion destination and among thecity’s most romantic restaurants— will soon close for a major makeover ahead of its 40th anniversary.</description></item><item><title>Did Billy Napier consider benching DJ Lagway after struggles vs LSU?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/09/14/why-florida-football-coach-billy-napier-didnt-change-qbs-with-dj-lagway-struggling-vs-lsu/86106514007/</link><description>BATON ROUGE, La. −Florida footballcoach Billy Napier stood by quarterback DJ Lagway throughout his struggles against LSU on Sept. 13.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Palmetto girls golf, Sarasota Christian volleyball win</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/09/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-8-13-2025/85855502007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 8-13, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>SMH named among 350 'smart hospitals' in the world by Newsweek</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/13/sarasota-memorial-hospital-ranked-a-smart-hospitals-by-newsweek/86090028007/</link><description>Sarasota Memorial Health Care Systemhas been named to Newsweek’s listof the “World’s Best Smart Hospitals 2026,” earning international recognition for its leadership in health technology and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Who are mystery $1.8 billion Powerball winners? Check numbers for Sept. 13</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/13/powerball-winner-texas-missouri-saturday-billion-taxes-cash/86142520007/</link><description>A week after the historic $1.787 billion Powerball win,lottery fever is still spiking!</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man arrested in fatal DUI crash, fled 2…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/13/bradenton-man-arrested-in-fatal-dui-crash-fled-2-crashes-troopers/86135648007/</link><description>A Bradenton manwas arrested Friday, Sept. 12, after troopers say he struck and killed a pedestrian, fled, and latercrashed again while driving without a licenseand under the influence.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota deputies respond to fatal drowning…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/13/sarasota-deputies-respond-to-fatal-drowning-investigation-underway/86139584007/</link><description>The Sarasota County Sheriff’s Office isinvestigating a drowning that claimed a man’s lifeSaturday morning at Turtle Beach.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/13/florida-lottery-results-saturday-september-13-2025/86146748007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, Sept. 13, 2025</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Game Balls: Week 4 top Sarasota, Manatee high school football performances</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/13/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-top-week-4-performers/86041095007/</link><description>Sarasota and Manatee area high school football teams lit up scoreboards in Week 4, with several local teams winning by multiple scores.</description></item><item><title>Politicians are now targets for violence. Let us protect ourselves.Commissioner Tom Knight Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/09/13/kirk-trump-open-carry-second-amendment/86110066007/</link><description>There is no denying it: political violence is now status quo in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota's Stephen King apologizes for false claim about Charlie Kirk</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/13/sarasota-stephen-king-apologizes-for-false-claim-about-charlie-kirk/86135037007/</link><description>Longtime Sarasota County resident and celebrity authorStephen King has repeatedly apologizedfor a false accusation he made about conservative activistCharlie Kirk, who was fatally shot on a Utah college campus on Sept. 10 and also owned a waterfront home in Sarasota.</description></item><item><title>‘Art Deco’ show reveals a brave new world at Sarasota Art Museum</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/14/art-deco-posters-reveal-dreams-of-the-future-at-sarasota-art-museum/85930567007/</link><description>Sarasota Art Museum’s “Art Deco: The Golden Age of Illustration” marks the movement’s centennial with 100 Deco posters. It’s easy to view these lithographs through nostalgia’s rose-colored glasses. Curator Yangsook Roon reveals them through the eyes of the target audience. These images captured the machine age – a fast-paced era of airplanes, ocean liners, roadsters, and electrification. It was a brave new world. And it was all brand new.</description></item></channel></rss>