<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 22:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fly away! Breeze adds 19 new routes, including several from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/02/06/breeze-airways-florida-airports-destinations-new-routes-cost/78251054007/</link><description>Sometimes you just need to get away. Even if where you are is where others head to when they want to get away.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>The Big 15: Herald-Tribune's top 2025 college football prospects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/06/top-sarasota-manatee-college-football-prospects-for-2025-high-school-season/84231653007/</link><description>The Big 15: Herald-Tribune's top 2025 college football prospects</description></item><item><title>Ranking all 17 high school football teams in Sarasota and Manatee area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/08/ranking-all-fhsaa-ssaa-football-teams-sarasota-manatee-2025-season/85526072007/</link><description>Ranking all 17 high school football teams in Sarasota and Manatee area</description></item><item><title>'Perfect Match' season 3: See couples, how to watch new…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/08/how-where-watch-perfect-match-season-three-when-new-episodes-drop-netflix/85555199007/</link><description>The "Avengers: Endgame" of reality dating shows is back.</description></item><item><title>Better Business Bureau warns about scam loan calls from…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/08/loan-application-scams-evelyn-florida-better-business-bureau/85578223007/</link><description>Have you received a worrying phone call or voicemail from a woman named Evelyn who isdeeplyconcerned about your loan application and just needs a little more info?</description></item><item><title>DeSantis faces legal action for another delay in judge…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/08/aclu-desantis-judicial-appointment/85577447007/</link><description>For the second time in two months, Gov. Ron DeSantis has failed to meet the deadline to appoint someone to fill a judicial vacancy, prompting a legal challenge from the American Civil Liberties Union of Florida.</description></item><item><title>Jim Lovell dies weeks ahead of Tom Hanks film, 'Apollo…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/08/jim-lovell-dies-tom-hanks-film-apollo-13-nasa-florida/85581868007/</link><description>Apollo astronaut Jim Lovell diedsix weeks before the movie about his rescue mission is set for re-release.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota today through the…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/07/best-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton-venice-fl/85474919007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota today through the…</description></item><item><title>Dual language school on track to expand campus through eighth grade</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/08/students-welcome-new-teachers-new-year-at-sarasotas-dreamers-academy/85515628007/</link><description>Dual language school on track to expand campus through eighth grade</description></item><item><title>Uncertainty in funding, prompts budget cuts for Sarasota Schools</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/08/teachers-school-advocates-sound-alarm-on-layoffs-as-classes-start/85515779007/</link><description>With Sarasota County’s first day of school Aug. 11, the School District enters the year after scores of layoffs across a range of positions and under a hiring freeze — moves leaders say are necessary to protect classrooms as they navigate a series of financial setbacks.</description></item><item><title>10 essential hidden gem restaurants in Sarasota worth discovering</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/08/best-hidden-gem-restaurants-sarasota/83648784007/</link><description>10 essential hidden gem restaurants in Sarasota worth discovering</description></item><item><title>Sarasota neighborhoods use controversial technology to fine speeders</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/08/sarasota-neighborhoods-use-controversial-technology-to-fine-speeders/85574104007/</link><description>A motorist driving a small Toyota hatchback turned into the Laurel Oak neighborhood off Bee Ridge Road in Sarasota County on an afternoon in late February.</description></item></channel></rss>