<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 21:04:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>College football poll hot takes: SEC whips Big Ten in rankings, not playoff</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/08/04/college-football-preseason-coaches-poll-predictions-hot-takes/85410070007/</link><description>After an offseason filled with interconferencepropaganda wars, thinlyveiled shotsandpublic sniping, the 67 coaches who vote in theUS LBM Coaches Pollgot to offer one last, private word on which conference is strongest.</description></item><item><title>IMG, American Heritage headline Florida teams on USA Today preseason Super 25</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/04/img-american-heritage-florida-teams-high-school-usa-today-preseason-super-25-aquinas-chaminade/85511178007/</link><description>Five Florida teams cracked the preseasonUSA Today High School Sports Super 25 football poll.</description></item><item><title>What Billy Napier said about Florida football during 'critical week' of camp</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/08/04/florida-football-coach-billy-napier-seeking-continued-effort-intensity-in-fall-camp/85475454007/</link><description>Florida footballcoach Billy Napier was pleased with the intensity and effort theFlorida Gatorsshowed in their fifth practice of fall camp on August 4.</description></item><item><title>What qualifies as middle class in Florida? See the income range</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/04/what-middle-class-florida-cheapest-places-live-cost-of-living-cities/85471822007/</link><description>A massive influx of new residents made Florida one of themost popular U.S. states to moveto from 2021 through 2023. In 2022, it became the country’s fastest-growing state for the first time since 1957, according tothe U.S. Census Bureau.</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' new episode tonight: Here's how…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/where-when-how-watch-stream-bachelor-paradise-cash-prize-amount-full-cast-list-contestants/85505409007/</link><description>"Bachelor in Paradise"is back after a year-long hiatus, followingformer Bachelor Nation contestantsas they attempt a second (or third, or fourth) chance at finding their soulmate on national television.</description></item><item><title>Cracking window doesn't help: How to prevent child hot…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/04/hot-car-deaths-children-list-locations-florida-us-prevent/85506188007/</link><description>The number of deaths of babies and children dying in hot cars continues to increase.</description></item><item><title>Tampa rapper Doechii snubs Florida during upcoming tour…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/doechii-live-from-the-swamp-tour-florida-dates-tickets/85502384007/</link><description>Doechiiis hitting the road this fall!</description></item><item><title>What is redistricting? Will Florida redraw maps to keep…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/04/redistricting-republicans-districts-map-florida/85505559007/</link><description>What is redistricting? Will Florida redraw maps to keep…</description></item><item><title>What is Trump’s approval rating? Poll shows term low…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/04/approval-rating-trump-epstein/85402761007/</link><description>The ongoing controversy aroundJeffrey Epsteinhas roiled the Trump administration for weeks, and at least one poll shows most Americans arenot approving of how it is being handled.</description></item><item><title>Waterfront access improved at small Nokomis park for Legacy Trail</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/04/lots-bought-at-trailhead-for-legacy-trail-and-north-port-connector/85458007007/</link><description>Waterfront access improved at small Nokomis park for Legacy Trail</description></item><item><title>New local restaurant replaces Applebee’s with 'value' steaks, seafood</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/04/new-restaurant-replaces-applebees-bradenton-affordable-steak-seafood/85476455007/</link><description>New local restaurant replaces Applebee’s with 'value' steaks, seafood</description></item><item><title>Anti-Trump protests could keep Americans divided, angry</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/04/trump-protests-no-kings-violent-rage/85505352007/</link><description>It is easy to appreciate the righteous anger that leads todemonstrationsagainst the policies of the current leadership of the United States.</description></item><item><title>YIGBY could help Sarasota County address affordable housing crisis</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/04/yes-in-gods-back-yard-law-churches-could-address-housing-crunch/85411086007/</link><description>YIGBY could help Sarasota County address affordable housing crisis</description></item></channel></rss>