<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:05:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Another Trump episode of ‘South Park’? How to watch tonight’s show</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/06/south-park-trump-episode-tonight/85538332007/</link><description>The battle between the president of the United States and araunchy animated comedy showcontinues tonight.</description></item><item><title>Wendy’s launches 'Wednesday' Meal of Misfortune ahead of season 2</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/06/wendys-wednesday-meal-of-misfortune-florida-netflix/85538038007/</link><description>We might be months away from Halloween, but the eerie vibes are already here.</description></item><item><title>Teddy Bridgewater: Miami Northwestern suspension 'very difficult'</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/06/teddy-bridgewater-miami-northwestern-suspension-tampa-bay-buccaneers/85543579007/</link><description>Teddy Bridgewater addressedhis suspensionand subsequentdeparture as head coach at Miami Northwesternduring his introductory news conference with theTampa Bay Buccaneers.</description></item><item><title>The Big 15: Sarasota and Manatee's top 2025 college football prospects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/06/top-sarasota-manatee-college-football-prospects-for-2025-high-school-season/84231653007/</link><description>The Big 15: Sarasota and Manatee's top 2025 college football prospects</description></item><item><title>Manatee County plans a new curfew for minors</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/06/manatee-plans-a-new-curfew-for-minors-despite-chairmans-opposition/85523626007/</link><description>Manatee County plans a new curfew for minors</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>McFarland's bill gives expectant mons proper parking…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/06/pregnant-mothers-disabled-florida/85429783007/</link><description>State Rep.Fiona McFarlanddeserves kudos and thanks for her efforts to make parking easier for pregnant women.</description></item><item><title>It's not fall, but pumpkin spice is back at Krispy Kreme</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/06/krispy-kreme-fall-menu-pumpkin-spice-doughnuts-latte-coffee-florida-locations/85538936007/</link><description>Is there anything better than fall? Cooler weather. The leaves turning color.</description></item><item><title>Increased rain chances may help Florida cool down, but…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/08/06/florida-weather-forecast-radar-tropics-rain-cooler-temps/85539659007/</link><description>It may be August, but temperatures keep reminding us we still live in Florida, and this month is hot.</description></item><item><title>Best local bars? 11 unique spots worth a road trip in Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/06/best-bars-florida-2025/85420804007/</link><description>Thebest barsin Florida aren’t just for grabbing a drink — they’re for creating memories, and maybe a story you shouldn’t share at work on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Pregnant women shouldn't have disability parking access</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/06/pregnant-disabled-parking-florida-mothers/85538049007/</link><description>As a mother, grandmother, anthropologist, disabled senior and rational human being, I'm struggling to retrieve my chin from the floor having read therecent guest columnreferencing a successful bill by state Rep. Fiona McFarland allowing pregnant women to obtain disabled parking permits ("McFarland stands up for Florida's pregnant women," Aug. 4</description></item><item><title>Sarasota deputies arrest woman for arson, homicide after trailer fire</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/06/sarasota-deputies-arrest-woman-for-arson-homicide-after-trailer-fire/85526389007/</link><description>Sarasota deputies arrest woman for arson, homicide after trailer fire</description></item><item><title>The Meadows Country Club submits summary of assets and liabilities</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/06/the-meadows-country-club-submits-bankruptcy-documents-to-court/85507990007/</link><description>The Meadows Country Club submits summary of assets and liabilities</description></item></channel></rss>