<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Stretch your summer at Florida’s best spas and wellness escapes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/09/05/where-to-unwind-in-florida-10-spas-to-keep-summer-going-strong/85851862007/</link><description>Labor Day may mark the unofficial end of summer, but in Florida, the heat and the chance for indulgence between hurricanes linger long after the last backyard barbecue. For those not ready to trade flip-flops for fall, the state’s top spas and wellness spaces offer one more excuse to savor summer.</description></item><item><title>Free festival, Ozzy tribute and more fun Sarasota events this weekend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/11/things-to-do-sarasota-sept-11-14/85995510007/</link><description>Famed Sarasota dining and drinking destination St. Armands Circlewill soon welcome back the Tommy Bahama restaurant and retail store, this time under one roof. But before the highly anticipated opening, you can head there Saturday or Sunday for an arts and crafts festival while visiting other restaurants thriving there, such asColumbiaandCha Cha Coconuts.</description></item><item><title>No masking it anymore, Tennessee won quarterback trade with UCLA</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/sec/2025/09/14/tennessee-joey-aguilar-nico-iamaleava/86039974007/</link><description>KNOXVILLE, TN – The disguise slipped off around the timeJoey Aguilarcarved throughGeorgia’s defense for a third consecutive touchdown drive with a few minutes still left in the first quarter.</description></item><item><title>College football rankings: SEC teams in updated Coaches, AP polls</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/SEC/2025/09/14/college-football-rankings-updated-sec-coaches-poll-ap-top-25-week-3/86075657007/</link><description>The top-rankedSEC teamsonce again faced major tests during Week 3 of the 2025 college football season.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Palmetto girls golf, Sarasota Christian volleyball win</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/09/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-8-13-2025/85855502007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 8-13, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>Gabrielle? Tropical disturbance in Atlantic has high chance of formation</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/14/gabrielle-hurricane-florida-track-path/86149732007/</link><description>Forecasters arekeeping an eye on tropical waves− what else is out in the Atlantic?</description></item><item><title>Sarasota deputies respond to fatal drowning…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/13/sarasota-deputies-respond-to-fatal-drowning-investigation-underway/86139584007/</link><description>The Sarasota County Sheriff’s Office isinvestigating a drowning that claimed a man’s lifeSaturday morning at Turtle Beach.</description></item><item><title>Who are mystery $1.8 billion Powerball winners? Check…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/13/powerball-winner-texas-missouri-saturday-billion-taxes-cash/86142520007/</link><description>A week after the historic $1.787 billion Powerball win,lottery fever is still spiking!</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/13/florida-lottery-results-saturday-september-13-2025/86146748007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, Sept. 13, 2025</description></item><item><title>Powerball, Mega Millions billion-dollar wins: List of…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/14/powerball-edwin-castro-california-how-much-cash-tax-texas-missouri/86105597007/</link><description>Someonewon the $1.787 billion Powerball− in Texas and Missouri.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Politicians are now targets for violence. Let us protect ourselves.Commissioner Tom Knight Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/09/13/kirk-trump-open-carry-second-amendment/86110066007/</link><description>There is no denying it: political violence is now status quo in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Southeast Athletic Hall of Fame to honor legendary players</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/14/vin-mannix-southeast-athletic-hall-of-fame-honors-legendary-players/85606362007/</link><description>Thirty years laterBob Carrollstill remembers heading toward the locker room, thinking over his pregame pep talk before Southeast’s boys basketball state championship game in Tallahassee.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota's Stephen King apologizes for false claim about Charlie Kirk</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/13/sarasota-stephen-king-apologizes-for-false-claim-about-charlie-kirk/86135037007/</link><description>Longtime Sarasota County resident and celebrity authorStephen King has repeatedly apologizedfor a false accusation he made about conservative activistCharlie Kirk, who was fatally shot on a Utah college campus on Sept. 10 and also owned a waterfront home in Sarasota.</description></item><item><title>‘Art Deco’ show reveals a brave new world at Sarasota Art Museum</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/14/art-deco-posters-reveal-dreams-of-the-future-at-sarasota-art-museum/85930567007/</link><description>Sarasota Art Museum’s “Art Deco: The Golden Age of Illustration” marks the movement’s centennial with 100 Deco posters. It’s easy to view these lithographs through nostalgia’s rose-colored glasses. Curator Yangsook Roon reveals them through the eyes of the target audience. These images captured the machine age – a fast-paced era of airplanes, ocean liners, roadsters, and electrification. It was a brave new world. And it was all brand new.</description></item></channel></rss>