<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:03:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota-Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/09/12/top-concerts-this-week-near-me-sarasota-bradenton/85970630007/</link><description>With the end ofSeptemberand the start of season in the Sarasota area approaching, we have multiple big names in this week's concert picks installment. We start with a Puerto Rican rapper and end with a North Carolina country musician, both rising stars in their respective genres with millions of TikTok followers and monthly Spotify listeners to their names, each playing Sarasota shows.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week: Palmetto football player Matthew Hennesey</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/11/herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-palmetto-football-player-matthew-hennesey/86039096007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects boys athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Health Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week: ODA volleyball player Ella Kwon</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/11/herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-out-of-door-academy-volleyball-player-ella-kwon/86039224007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects girls athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>High school football: Midseason QB transfers legal, but don't feel right</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/12/fhsaa-football-qb-transfers-midseason-venice-american-heritage/86102628007/</link><description>High school football players transferring schools has become so common in Florida that it's sometimes more newsworthy when a player stays at their original school than when they leave for greener pastures.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota murder that shocked 'paradise' in 1995 marks 30-year anniversary</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/09/12/sarasota-murder-case-30-years-later-no-execution-date-for-death-row-inmate/85609209007/</link><description>In 1995, Sarasota was on the precipice of transitioning from being a laid-back beach town, known for its eclectic arts community, to experiencing a development boom that would transform it into the city many know today.</description></item><item><title>Murder charge for Charlie Kirk's suspected assassin: live updates</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/nation/2025/09/12/charlie-kirk-shooting-suspect-live-updates/86104818007/</link><description>WASHINGTON CITY, Utah – The suspect in the fatal shooting of conservative activistCharlie Kirkat a college speaking event in Utah allegedly confessed to a family member and is in custody, authorities said Friday morning.</description></item><item><title>Top lawmaker: 'We’ve got to keep chipping away' at…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/12/florida-legislative-budget-commission/86110894007/</link><description>With a big surplus looming next year but multi-billion-dollar deficits right behind it, House budget chief Lawrence McClure says state lawmakers must cut deeper now to head off the red ink ahead.</description></item><item><title>Why are videos of Charlie Kirk's death allowed on social…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/12/charlie-kirk-death-graphic-videos-social-media-iryna-zarutska/86105598007/</link><description>Social media users have been bombarded withhorrifying videoson their feeds this week.</description></item><item><title>What we know about $1.787 billion Powerball winners from…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/12/powerball-texas-missouri-louis-fredericksburg-quiktrip/86106320007/</link><description>Who won the $1.787 billion Powerballjackpot?</description></item><item><title>Free festival, Ozzy tribute and more fun Sarasota events…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/11/things-to-do-sarasota-sept-11-14/85995510007/</link><description>Famed Sarasota dining and drinking destination St. Armands Circlewill soon welcome back the Tommy Bahama restaurant and retail store, this time under one roof. But before the highly anticipated opening, you can head there Saturday or Sunday for an arts and crafts festival while visiting other restaurants thriving there, such asColumbiaandCha Cha Coconuts.</description></item><item><title>When will North Port install school zone speed cameras?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/12/ten-north-port-schools-targeted-for/85996338007/</link><description>NORTH PORT – The North Port City Commission approved the first reading Tuesday of an ordinance that may placespeed zone cameras on roads adjacent to at least 10 schools– possibly as soon as the end of the calendar year.</description></item><item><title>Vern Buchanan: Political violence has no place in AmericaU.S. Rep. Vern Buchanan Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/09/12/buchanan-kirk-trump-violence-political/86110003007/</link><description>Life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness are more than historic virtues; they are the foundation of our republic. These core American values are protected and preserved by our Constitution and our First Amendment right to freedom of speech.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man accused in dispensary robbery ID'd in deputy shooting</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/12/bradenton-man-accused-in-dispensary-robbery-idd-in-deputy-shooting/86112081007/</link><description>The Manatee County Sheriff’s Office has identified the manwho was killed in a deputy-involved shootingon Sept. 10.</description></item><item><title>5 closed Sarasota restaurants we still miss</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/12/closed-sarasota-restaurants-we-still-miss/86096114007/</link><description>From beloved diners to fine‑dining landmarks, Sarasota hassaid goodbye to some unforgettable restaurants in recent years.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota-Manatee teachers warned not to post 'despicable' comments about Charlie Kirk</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/12/charlie-kirk-shooting-spotlights-sarasota-teachers-social-media-policy/86116338007/</link><description>Thefatal shooting of conservative activist Charlie Kirkhas sparked a statewide conversation about teachers' social media posts – and what lines school districts can draw.</description></item></channel></rss>