<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:03:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>National Coffee Day deals in Florida. Dunkin, 7-11, Circle K, more</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/28/national-coffee-day-florida-starbucks-dunkins-deals-freebies/86370035007/</link><description>Break out your travel mugs and get your route ready for tomorrow morning — we're preplanning ourcoffee order.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/09/26/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86198157007/</link><description>We say farewell toSeptemberand enter October this week, and you'll find notable shows across both months in this latest concert picks installment. We start with a contemporary Christian musician who's earned 60 Dove Awards, five Grammys and induction into the Grand Ole Opry, visiting Sarasota while on tour celebrating the recent 25th anniversary of one of his most popular albums.</description></item><item><title>SBAC launches 2025–26 with “Harmonies of Sound and Vision” exhibit</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/28/suncoast-black-arts-collaborative-debuts-exhibit-at-sarasota-orchestra/86167948007/</link><description>Suncoast Black Arts Collaborative is kicking off its 2025–26 season with bold color and sound. The organization’s fifth Art Innovation Zone exhibition, “Harmonies of Sound and Vision: A Celebration of the Improvisational Spirit and Classical Elegance,” opens Sept. 28 at Sarasota Orchestra’s Harmony Gallery.</description></item><item><title>College football Week 5 featured six upsets in top 25</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/09/28/college-football-upsets-scores-top-25-week-5/86401566007/</link><description>Through five weeks of the2025 college football season, one theme is becoming apparent: survival.</description></item><item><title>Oregon, Alabama surge as US LBM Coaches Poll gets makeover after Week 5</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/09/28/coaches-poll-college-football-rankings-top-25/86325611007/</link><description>As one might expect,the US LBM Coaches Polllooks a lot different afterall the Week 5 results. But one of the few things that didn’t change is Ohio State remains No. 1.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Sarasota, Manatee 2025 Midseason Volleyball Player of Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/09/25/sarasota-manatee-2025-midseason-high-school-volleyball-player-of-year-poll/86328407007/</link><description>The halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school volleyball season is upon us. As we head into the second half of the season, we selected Lakewood Ranch High player Ava Collins as our Midseason Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>State college football wrapup. FSU, UCF both handed…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/09/28/virginia-outlasts-fsu-in-2ot-ucf-loses-college-football-wrapup-video/86350542007/</link><description>FSU is upset by Virginia in double overtime. And UCF suffers a tough loss toKansas State.</description></item><item><title>Florida outlook for impending Tropical Storm Imelda</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/28/national-hurricane-center-tropical-storm-imelda-path-track-florida-impact/86403531007/</link><description>A tropical storm watch remains in effect for a portion ofFlorida's east coastSunday, Sept. 28, asTropical Depression 9tracks toward the southeast U.S. coast, expected to become Tropical Storm Imelda today, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Tuskegee Airman Goerge Hardy, 100, remembered</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/28/one-of-last-tuskegee-airmen-george-hardy-he-was-100/86395889007/</link><description>Lieutenant Colonel George E. Hardy, one of the last surviving members of theTuskegee Airmen, passed away on Sept. 25 in Sarasota. He was 100 years old.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Daylight saving time ends soon, when we reset clocks to fall back</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/28/when-time-change-fall-back-daylight-savings-history/86364902007/</link><description>As fall rolls in, we are a little over a month away from falling back and changing our clocks to get one more hour of sleep and less daylight.</description></item><item><title>World War II hero, one of last Tuskegee Airmen, dies at Sarasota home</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/26/george-hardy-tuskegee-airmen-world-war-ii-hero-dies-sarasota-home/86374419007/</link><description>World War II hero Lt. Col. George Hardy, the youngest of the Tuskegee Airmen pilots who fought during the war and helped pave the way for the integration of the armed forces, hasdied at his Sarasota home at age 100.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County School Board won't succeed with sneaky time change</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/28/sarasota-school-board-bridget-ziegler/86389932007/</link><description>Recently the majority of theSarasota County School Boardvoted tochange the board’s meeting timeto 10 a.m., making it difficult for students, staff and working parents to attend.</description></item><item><title>Townhome and condo prices are on the decline in Sarasota and Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/25/august-real-estate-report-indicates-transitional-period-for-suncoast/86313415007/</link><description>The Sarasota-Bradenton area's August real estate market points to a period of transition for the region, according to the most recentindustry report.</description></item></channel></rss>