<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 3: 8 items to get rid of for sure</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/30/marni-jameson-walking-the-rightsizing-walk-part-3-the-power-purge/85813421007/</link><description>I am so embarrassed. All these columns and books I have written on downsizing and decluttering and my oh my, the mess I am in. Moving is the ultimate truth test. As I pack up the house my husband, DC, and I have lived in for eight years, box towers line the halls, packed and stacked like big city skylines. Each room coughs up its contents like a kid with consumption. I fear I may never see a clear counter again.</description></item><item><title>Who is on 'Dancing with the Stars' season 34? See cast, when to watch</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/03/dancing-with-the-stars-cast-abc-florida-how-to-watch-disney-plus-hulu/85952050007/</link><description>Goodbye reality dating competitions, hello realitydancingcompetitions!</description></item><item><title>Inspections: Rodent droppings temporarily close local restaurant</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/03/inspections-rodent-droppings-close-sarasota-restaurant/85939206007/</link><description>Ourdigital databaseof restaurant health inspections is updated regularly with the latest information on which Sarasota, Bradenton and Venice area restaurants passed or failed.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 10 Football Power Poll after Week 2</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/03/top-10-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-team-rankings-after-week-2/85837033007/</link><description>We're already two weeks into a new high school football season, and not much changed for the area hierarchy after the opening slate of games.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 8 Volleyball Power Poll after Week 2</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/09/03/top-8-sarasota-manatee-high-school-volleyball-team-rankings-after-week-2/85852179007/</link><description>As indicated in last week's article, there has already been a big shakeup in the local volleyball power rankings.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Menard leads Sarasota boys golf over Cardinal Mooney</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/03/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-1-6-2025/85852537007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 1-6, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.If you don't see your results, have your coach email them tohtincoming@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Who won 'Bachelor in Paradise' finale? See who got the…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/03/bachelor-paradise-finale-winners-jess-spencer-engaged-kat-dale-alexe-andrew/85952123007/</link><description>For the first time ever, two couples took home a significant chunk of change on the“Bachelor in Paradise” season 10 finale, which aired on Tuesday, Sept. 2.</description></item><item><title>Powerball, Mega Millions billion-dollar winners: List of…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/03/powerball-edwin-castro-casarotti-struyck-how-much-lump-sum/83077860007/</link><description>Lucky No. 13!</description></item><item><title>What vaccines are currently recommended by CDC, Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/03/florida-governor-desantis-surgeon-general-ladapo-end-all-vaccine-mandates/85959953007/</link><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis and Florida Surgeon General have announced plans toend all vaccine mandatesin the state, including immunization requirements for schools, the first state to do so.</description></item><item><title>Experts 'profoundly concerned' as Florida moves to end…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/03/florida-vaccine-requirements-medical-experts-profoundly-concerned-desantis-ladapo/85959858007/</link><description>Hours after Florida Surgeon General Joseph Ladapo announced the Department of Health and the Legislature wouldwork hand-in-hand to repeal vaccine mandatesin the state, national organizations, state university medical centers and former Florida officials came out against the move.</description></item><item><title>¿Florida eliminó las vacunas obligatorias escolares…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/03/florida-eliminar-mandatos-vacunas-escolares-regla/85960399007/</link><description>El cirujano general de Florida,Dr. Joseph Ladapo, dijo en conferencia de prensa el 3 de septiembre que el estado trabajará para eliminar todos los mandatos de vacunas.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County upgrades 911 dispatch system, boosting emergency response</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/03/sarasota-county-upgrades-911-dispatch-system-boosting-emergency-response/85425518007/</link><description>Sarasota County first respondersjust got a major upgradethat could help save more lives – faster.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota LGBTQ+ group plans pulse tribute after 'PrideWalk' removal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/03/sarasota-lgbtq-group-plans-pulse-tribute-after-pridewalk-removal/85942668007/</link><description>Project Pride SRQ is planning a “compassion at the crosswalk” eventto honor the 49 people who lost their lives during the Pulse shooting. The event, which won't be scheduled until later this month, will be held where the "PrideWalk" satbefore it was removed on Aug. 28.</description></item><item><title>Upset about DeSantis ban on artwork? Stop crying and do something.</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/03/desantis-crosswalks-diversity-rainbow-trump/85956742007/</link><description>I propose to fellow progressives to stop whining about rainbowcrosswalks being painted overby the state government and do something about it.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota rent prices down nearly 6% over the past year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/03/sarasota-rental-prices-are-falling-compared-with-august-2024/85943519007/</link><description>Rent in Sarasota continued totrend downwardin August, bringing the median rent price in the city to $1,386.</description></item></channel></rss>