<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 3: 8 items to get rid of for sure</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/30/marni-jameson-walking-the-rightsizing-walk-part-3-the-power-purge/85813421007/</link><description>I am so embarrassed. All these columns and books I have written on downsizing and decluttering and my oh my, the mess I am in. Moving is the ultimate truth test. As I pack up the house my husband, DC, and I have lived in for eight years, box towers line the halls, packed and stacked like big city skylines. Each room coughs up its contents like a kid with consumption. I fear I may never see a clear counter again.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend: Sept. 4-7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/04/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-sept-4-7/85866691007/</link><description>September may be Sarasota’s slowest month forlocal events, but there are still plenty of reasons to get out — includingthe start of the 2025 NFL season.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 3 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/04/week-3-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85852367007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Sept. 5, 2025</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man arrested for second-degree murder in death of girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/04/bradenton-man-arrested-for-second-degree-murder-in-death-of-girlfriend/85971535007/</link><description>Manatee County deputies arrested a 33-year-old on Sept. 3 for the second-degree murder of his girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Panthers, Cougars, Tigers volleyball win in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/03/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-1-6-2025/85852537007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 1-6, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.If you don't see your results, have your coach email them tohtincoming@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Free speech group sends letter to Florida schools…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/04/free-speech-group-florida-schools-cant-enforce-book-ban-law/85977828007/</link><description>One of the nation's leadingFirst Amendment advocacy groupsreminded school districts across Florida that they can't enforce thestate law that's been used to remove thousands of library books.</description></item><item><title>Palmetto High grad LaJohntay Wester ready to tackle NFL…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/nfl/2025/09/05/nfl-baltimore-ravens-rookie-wide-receiver-lajohntay-wester-fau-colorado-palmetto-high/85956232007/</link><description>Baltimore Ravensrookie LaJohntay Wester had dreamed about this moment.</description></item><item><title>Joining the Herald-Tribune has been a long game for new…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/05/sports-writer-vinnie-portell-joins-the-herald-tribune/85947519007/</link><description>The first time I saw formerHerald-Tribunesportswriter Dennis Maffezzoli at a high school basketball game, it hit me.</description></item><item><title>See spaghetti models for Invest 91L. Will Florida feel…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/05/invest-91l-spaghetti-models-tropical-storm-hurricane-gabrielle-what-to-know-florida-impacts/85987081007/</link><description>TheNational Hurricane Centerexpects Invest 91L to strengthen into atropical depressionby the weekend as it moves west across the Atlantic.</description></item><item><title>Community leaders have mixed emotions on SCS board appointment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/04/sarasota-school-board-seat-to-be-filled-by-rose-after-campaign-loss/85869351007/</link><description>Karen Rose’s return to the Sarasota County School Board — throughappointment by Gov. Ron DeSantisless than a year after she lost her seat in an election — is drawing mixed reactions from board members and education advocates who are weighing what her presence could mean for classrooms, families and district stability.</description></item><item><title>Saying farewell after 40 years of covering the arts in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/09/05/a-new-chapter-arts-writer-steps-away-from-a-dream-job-after-40-years/85894368007/</link><description>I came to the Sarasota Herald-Tribune from Washington, D.C., in 1984 as an assistant city editor overseeing a large team of local reporters, with a dream of being a theater critic one day.</description></item><item><title>Popular Sarasota restaurant opening at new spot after storm closure</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/05/sarasota-restaurant-tommy-bahama-opening-st-armands-after-hurricane/85970778007/</link><description>It’s been along, tough summer for the Sarasota restaurant scene— especially on the iconic island destination St. Armands Circle, where dining spots like Le Colonne and Meaney’s Mini Donuts remainclosednearly a year after flooding from hurricanes Helene and Milton.</description></item><item><title>What do developers plan for the intersection of I-75 and SR 681?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/05/multi-family-housing-two-hotels-and122-acre-parcel-at-i-75-and-s-r-681-the-topic-of-sept-11-workshop/85885725007/</link><description>Palmer Ranch developer Hugh Culverhouse Jr. is proposing to create a mixed-use community that could include multi-family housing, hotels and businesses on 122 acres west of Interstate 75 and south of State Road 681, which is also known as the Venice Connector.</description></item></channel></rss>