<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:05:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Acclaimed Sarasota restaurant closing for good after ‘tough summer’</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/20/sarasota-restaurant-adeline-closing/85725308007/</link><description>Acclaimed Sarasota restaurant closing for good after ‘tough summer’</description></item><item><title>VOTE: Who would you pick to be No. 1 volleyball player on The Fab 15 list</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/18/vote-for-top-high-school-volleyball-player-on-2025-herald-tribune-fab-15-poll/85639568007/</link><description>TheSarasota Herald-Tribunerecently unveiled its The Fab 15 list of the Sarasota-Manatee counties' top players to watch entering the 2025 high school volleyball season. To see the full listCLICK HERE</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Sailors win John Ryan Invitational; Mustangs finish second</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-august-18-23-2025/85715808007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Aug. 18-23, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>District 5A-9 Football Previews: Manatee, Braden River together again</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/20/2025-fhsaa-class-5a-9-high-school-football-team-previews-braden-river-manatee/85545472007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in FHSAA District 5A-9.</description></item><item><title>Alachua school board punished for silencing critic in Hulk Hogan clash</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/state/2025/08/20/state-panel-orders-free-speech-training-after-maga-jab-sparks-uproar/85743811007/</link><description>What started as a jab at the late pro wrestler Hulk Hogan turned into a legal pile-driver for one Florida school board, which now faces mandatory free speech training – and possible pay cuts – after state officials said it muzzled a critic.</description></item><item><title>FPL's settlement proposal substantially lowers initial rate request</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/20/fpl-settlement-proposal-to-end-8-9-billion-rate-hike-controversy/85740362007/</link><description>After reaching an agreement with 10 key stakeholders,Florida Power &amp; Light filed on Wednesdaya comprehensive four-year settlement agreement with state regulators.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/20/florida-lottery-results-wednesday-august-20-2025/85752247007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Wednesday, Aug. 20, 2025</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>'Secret plea deal' by prosecutors is a betrayal to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/21/epstein-maxwell-victims-plea-deal-acosta-krischer/85715347007/</link><description>As a lawyer who has represented many of Jeffrey Epstein’s and Ghislaine Maxwell’s victims dating back to 2008, I cannot stay silent while politicians and government officials continue to hide the truth.</description></item><item><title>A farewell letter to Venice and Florida - and America, too</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/19/us-florida-canada-maga-desantis/85706663007/</link><description>We have just completed the sale of our Venice, Florida, property.</description></item><item><title>I serve the LGBTQ+ community. Republicans want me off the school board.Tom Edwards Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/20/sarasota-school-board-gay-pride-lgbtq-republican/85721178007/</link><description>To Americans, the word “epidemic” has become familiar sinceCOVID appeared on our shores.</description></item><item><title>District 4A-11, 3A-11 Football Previews: Southeast, Bayshore, Booker</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/21/manatee-sarasota-southeast-bayshore-booker-high-school-football-team-previews/85545364007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in FHSAA Districts 4A-11 and 3A-11.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 1 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/21/week-1-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85565939007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Aug. 22, 2025</description></item></channel></rss>