<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 01:31:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Idina Menzel to perform at Sarasota gala. Tickets on sale today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/10/03/idina-menzel-sarasota-tickets/86445224007/</link><description>Tony Award-winning Broadway star and Disney’s “Frozen” voiceIdina Menzelwill headline the Sarasota Performing Arts Foundation Gala on March 6, 2026, at Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall.</description></item><item><title>FHSAA expands 2025 football playoffs with 16-team invitational brackets</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/fhsaa-expands-2025-high-school-football-playoffs-16-team-invitational-tournaments-fit/86499211007/</link><description>The FHSAA has expanded the football postseason with additional 16-team tournaments for teams that don't qualify for the traditional brackets, according to an email obtained by USA TODAY's Florida Network.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man found incompetent after stabbing brother’s girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/10/03/bradenton-man-found-incompetent-after-stabbing-brothers-girlfriend/86480455007/</link><description>A Bradenton manaccused of stabbing his brother’s girlfriend multiple timesin mid-August has been found incompetent to proceed with his case, according to court records.</description></item><item><title>Get your tickets to the 2026 World Cup in Seattle</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/how-to-buy-seattle-2026-world-cup-tickets/86503570007/</link><description>The 2026 FIFA World Cup will bring six matches to Seattle, includingRound of 32andRound of 16.</description></item><item><title>Wavytalk’s viral hair tools are up to 40% off for October Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wavytalk-amazon-prime-day-deals/86506025007/</link><description>If your hair could use a seasonal refresh, now’s the time to make it shine.Wavytalk, the fast-growing hair tools brandranked #1 on TikTok Shop and an Amazon best-seller, is making waves ahead of October Prime Day with some unbelievable discounts.</description></item><item><title>Pre-order the WSJ 2025 Wine Advent Calendar with free shipping today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wsj-2025-wine-advent-calendar/86501883007/</link><description>Thecountdown to Christmasjust got a lot more festive. TheWSJ Wine Advent Calendar is officially back for 2025and it is already flying off virtual shelves. With 24 mini bottles of wine, each window features a spirited glassful of something delicious, from silky reds to dry whites, refreshing rosés and even award-winning Prosecco for your holiday toasts.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/10/03/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86312835007/</link><description>It's the first full week of October, a month that'll bringa stacked events calendarto the Sarasota area, including live music. The biggest show in town this week will be an annual Circus Arts Conservatory fundraiser and electronic dance music concert, once again headlined by an internationally renowned DJ.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Did Trump say a shutdown falls on the president? Yes…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/10/03/trump-2011-2013-blamed-president-shutdown/86472266007/</link><description>Old news clips are circulating on social media showing PresidentDonald Trumpsaying the fault of agovernment shutdownshould lie with the president.</description></item><item><title>Clearwater road named for Hulk Hogan, DeSantis says</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/10/03/hulk-hogan-desantis-trail/86497341007/</link><description>Drivers passing a long a two-mile stretch of road in Clearwater will soon be traversing the Hulk Hogan Trail instead.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues Bradenton hospital after leg amputation over alleged delay</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/10/03/mom-sues-bradenton-hospital-after-leg-amputation-over-alleged-delay/86062040007/</link><description>When Hailey Van Dam woke up on July 2, 2024, she couldn’t have predicted that her life would forever be changed in less than 24 hours.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Congressman says he will vote to release Epstein files</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/10/03/steube-epstein-files-trump/86484574007/</link><description>Sarasota CongressmanGreg Steubetold the Herald-Tribune he would vote in favor of releasing the famedEpstein Fileswhen the motion likely comes before the U.S. House of Representatives later this month.</description></item><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item></channel></rss>