<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:04:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' week 8: 3 of 4 Floridians dumped from the beach</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/19/who-got-roses-bachelor-in-paradise-cast-list/85718775007/</link><description>The beach of ABC's"Bachelor in Paradise"is now three-fourths less Floridian.</description></item><item><title>Acclaimed Sarasota restaurant closing for good after ‘tough summer’</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/20/sarasota-restaurant-adeline-closing/85725308007/</link><description>I love dishing out praise forSarasota and Manatee’s best restaurants— fromhidden gemstobuzzy new essentials— but today’s story is tougher: theclosingof an acclaimed fine-dining spot I’ve championed many times before.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 21-24</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/21/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-21-24/85677582007/</link><description>Don’t let the summer heat keep you from enjoying all the fun in Sarasota and Bradenton, witheventsstarting today and running through the weekend.</description></item><item><title>Out-of-Door Academy wins Preseason Top Football Team Poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/21/out-of-door-academy-wins-preseason-sarasota-manatee-top-football-team-poll/85762149007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune recently ranked eight high school football teams to be the best in the Sarasota and Manatee County area entering the 2025 football season. Then we asked you, the readers, to vote for the high school football team you think is the best in the area heading into the new season.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 1 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/21/week-1-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85565939007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Aug. 22, 2025</description></item><item><title>Have you seen this snake? Why FWC wants to know about…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/20/florida-rainbow-snake-photos-rare/85737365007/</link><description>Roughly a week afterFlorida's 2025 Python Challenge wrapped up, wildlife officials are asking the public to search for another snake. Just for very different reasons.</description></item><item><title>District 4A-11, 3A-11 Football Previews: Southeast…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/21/manatee-sarasota-southeast-bayshore-booker-high-school-football-team-previews/85545364007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in FHSAA Districts 4A-11 and 3A-11.</description></item><item><title>NASA moon reactor, X-37B mission and Cargo Dragon |…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/tech/science/space/2025/08/21/nasa-moon-reactor-directive-x-37b-space-plane-and-more-space-beat/85751034007/</link><description>NASA's received marching orders to develop and build a nuclear reactor on the moon by the mid-2030s. The reason? The United States is now in a renewed space race with Russia and China to build a power source on the moon and claim our stake on the lunar surface.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County set to appoint new planning commissioners</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/21/who-is-going-to-end-up-on-the-sarasota-county-planning-commission/85747739007/</link><description>As concerns with development have become the preeminent political issue in Sarasota, the County Commission will appoint new members to its important Planning Commission next week.</description></item><item><title>COVID-era teaching dispute ends in ruling against UF prof</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/21/uf-professors-free-speech-appeal-undone-by-late-filing/85756117007/</link><description>A federal appellate court has handed aFlorida professora loss in his First Amendment case against his employer, the University of Florida.</description></item><item><title>Three Sarasota deputies on leave after fatal deputy-involved shooting</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/21/three-sarasota-deputies-on-leave-after-fatal-deputy-involved-shooting/85681684007/</link><description>Three Sarasota County Sheriff’s Officedeputies are on administrative leavefollowing a fatal Venice deputy-involved shooting on Aug. 13. The man who was killed told friends he felt he was being unnecessarily targeted by law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Jay Collins blames Gavin Newsom for fatal Florida Turnpike crash</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/21/florida-lt-gov-slams-newsom-escorts-crash-suspect-from-california/85761890007/</link><description>Florida's lieutenant governor flew out to the West Coast to accompany an undocumented immigrant accused of killing three people in a traffic crash back to Florida, but also took time to criticize California Gov. Gavin Newsom for his "failed policies."</description></item><item><title>Manatee County cancels wetlands vote meant to challenge SB 180</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/21/manatee-county-cancels-wetlands-vote-meant-to-challenge-sb-180/85738343007/</link><description>Faced with potential removal from office, Manatee County Commissioners scrapped plans to vote in favor of wetlands protections and development regulations on Thursday that would clash with the controversial state policy established by Senate Bill 180.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County budget talks end with few cuts, $600K school bill</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/21/sarasota-county-budget-talks-end-with-few-cuts-600k-school-bill/85755413007/</link><description>Despite tough talk from Sarasota County commissioners, this year’sfinal budget workshopended with little progress on curbing spending.</description></item></channel></rss>