<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:07:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Trump, Vance defend Sydney Sweeney 'jeans' ad. Is she from Florida?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/sydney-sweeney-florida-jeans-ad-american-eagle-trump-vance/85502382007/</link><description>Six words many didn't think they'd ever see together: "American Eagle jeans" and "promotion of eugenics." Now, it's all anyone can talk about.</description></item><item><title>Tampa rapper Doechii snubs Florida during upcoming tour. See all shows</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/doechii-live-from-the-swamp-tour-florida-dates-tickets/85502384007/</link><description>Doechiiis hitting the road this fall!</description></item><item><title>E. coli infections linked to raw milk from Florida farm. What we know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/05/raw-milk-florida-e-coli-farm/85521254007/</link><description>Twenty-onepeople in Central and northeast Floridahave been infected by Campylobacter and E. coli related to drinking raw milk, including six children under 10, according to the Florida Department of Health,. Severe complications were reported in at least two cases.</description></item><item><title>Contract: Florida prepping Camp Blanding for immigration detention</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/05/florida-gets-camp-blanding-ready-for-immigration-detention-facility-desantis/85507606007/</link><description>Florida is preparing a second immigration detention center, which is already being labeled in public records as the "North Detention Facility."</description></item><item><title>QB Teddy Bridgewater eyes NFL return with the Tampa Bay…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/nfl/buccaneers/2025/08/05/quarterback-teddy-bridgewater-tampa-bay-buccaneers-miami-northwestern-suspended-fhsaa/85521953007/</link><description>Teddy Bridgewater is expected to sign with theTampa Bay Buccaneers.</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>2023 Cardinal Mooney state champion win All-Time Best…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/2023-cardinal-mooney-wins-all-time-best-football-team-poll/85511663007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area football teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Gun control battle heats up in Florida governor's race</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/05/byron-donalds-david-jolly-clash-over-gun-rights-records/85479920007/</link><description>When Republican candidate for governorRep. Byron Donaldscalled out Democratic candidateDavid Jollyfor a “radical anti-gun past,” in the dustup that followed a leading gun rights group returned fire saying it was hypocritical for Florida Republicans to accuse anyone of being soft on Second Amendment rights.</description></item><item><title>Who's committed, who has offers: IMG Academy's top football recruits</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/recruiting-img-academy-football-recruits-jake-kreul-breck-kolojay-preston-carey/85471053007/</link><description>IMG Academy has a new head coach, and plenty of transfers ready to make an impact.</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota City Commission rejects development at Temple Beth Sholom</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/05/city-commission-rejects-development-at-temple-beth-shalom-synagogue/85506773007/</link><description>Sarasota City Commission rejects development at Temple Beth Sholom</description></item><item><title>29 Sarasota area restaurants get high-priority violations, 6 ace inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/05/sarasota-restaurants-get-high-priority-violations-health-inspections/85509841007/</link><description>29 Sarasota area restaurants get high-priority violations, 6 ace inspections</description></item></channel></rss>