<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee countiesmusic</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/09/26/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86198157007/</link><description>We say farewell toSeptemberand enter October this week, and you'll find notable shows across both months in this latest concert picks installment. We start with a contemporary Christian musician who's earned 60 Dove Awards, five Grammys and induction into the Grand Ole Opry, visiting Sarasota while on tour celebrating the recent 25th anniversary of one of his most popular albums.</description></item><item><title>See latest spaghetti models for Invest 94Lhurricane</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/26/invest-94l-hurricane-storm-imelda-noaa-spaghetti-models-tracker-florida/86350300007/</link><description>Showers and thunderstorms associated withInvest 94Lcontinue to show signs of organization, Sept. 26.</description></item><item><title>What Florida should know as dueling tropical systems develophurricane</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/26/national-hurricane-center-hurricane-humberto-invest-94l-imelda-florida/86350099007/</link><description>TheNational Hurricane Centeris keeping a close eye on two systems east of the United States as Gabrielle continues to weaken.</description></item><item><title>Universal sued in separate case over Epic Universe ride after man diesnews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/26/universal-orlando-lawsuit-stardust-racers-florida-kevin-rodriguez-zavala/86364639007/</link><description>A week after a Kissimmee man died afterriding Stardust Racersat Epic Universe, a woman is suing Universal for injuries she sustained while riding the roller coaster.</description></item><item><title>Mass shutdown layoffs? How many federal workers does Florida have?news</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/26/florida-federal-worker-layoff-firing-government-shutdown/86364645007/</link><description>Another government shutdown is fast approaching, but the White House is taking adifferent, harsher tacticthis time.</description></item><item><title>Just in case, here's how to pronounce Tropical Storm Imeldahurricane</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/26/tropical-storm-imelda-pronounce-spaghetti-models-florida-impact-invest-94l/86366909007/</link><description>After a slow start, the 2025 Atlantichurricane season is making up for lost time.</description></item><item><title>One dead, several hurt in crash near Kennedy Space Center. What we knownews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/26/fatal-crash-nasa-kennedy-space-florida-max-brewer-bridge/86366030007/</link><description>Troopers were on scene of an early morningfatal crash near NASA's Kennedy Space Center.</description></item><item><title>Trump headed to the Ryder Cup. How many days has he golfed this year?Politics</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/09/26/trump-ryder-cup-golf-afternoon-tee-times/86342724007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpis attending the Ryder Cup, a U.S. versus Europe golf tournament that occurs every other year in New York.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Week 6 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictionsfootball</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/25/week-6-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/86223690007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Thursday, Sept. 25 and Friday, Sept. 26, 2025.</description></item><item><title>New College's plan for a Kirk statue is part of its larger problemguest</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/09/25/charlie-kirk-richard-corcoran-new-college-statue/86343591007/</link><description>On Sept. 16, New College of Florida announced it wouldcommission a statueto commemorate the slain conservative activistCharlie Kirk.</description></item><item><title>Why the Herald-Tribune covered the Wilkinson Elementary School debateopinion</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/09/26/wilkinson-elementary-school-sarasota-declining-enrollment/86116527007/</link><description>Earlier this month, as the Sarasota County School Board convened for a special meeting, the Herald-Tribune published a story online about a proposal that could reshape our community. We did so because the discussion centered on converting a well-known elementary school —Wilkinson Elementary— but the implications reached far beyond its campus. The story was a flashpoint, and it was crucial that our community had access to the facts as the debate unfolded.</description></item><item><title>10 must-try Sarasota area food and drink events this falldining</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/26/food-drink-events-sarasota-bradenton-fall/86205557007/</link><description>This week marks the start of fall, and that means plenty ofOktoberfest celebrations offering beer and brats, and pumpkin festivals bringing autumnal vibes to the Sarasota area (look for our upcoming October events guide for more on those.) However,they’re far from the only food and drink events to look forward to this season.</description></item><item><title>US Recycling used deceased lawyer in state filings, records show</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/26/us-recycling-may-have-used-falsified-signatures-in-state-filings/86344425007/</link><description>Acrushing site in north Sarasotathat has drawn the ire of local residents and advocates has been found to be using a registered agent in its annual state filings who has been dead for nearly six years.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton releases 1.7 million gallons of partly treated sewage</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/26/bradenton-sewage-release-manatee-river/86329848007/</link><description>The City of Bradenton recently released 1.7 million gallons of partially treated sewage water into the Manatee River, but Mayor Gene Brown says work to fix thecity's chronic sewage system problemsis alreadywell underway.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota sweets shop with 40 years of history reopens after hurricane</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/26/sarasota-kilwins-armands-circle-reopens/86346177007/</link><description>St. Armands Circle is welcoming backanother beloved businessthis weekend. Kilwins, an ice cream and chocolate store, is celebrating its grand re-opening Saturday, Sept. 27, after being closed for a year due toHurricane Milton.</description></item></channel></rss>