<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>'Happee Birthdae' to Harry Potter! Where to stream movies, celebrate</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/31/harry-potter-birthday-universal-orlando-florida-jk-rowling-theme-parks/85436038007/</link><description>Don your birthday hats and grab your wands — it's time to wish a "Happee Birthdae" to one of the most iconic characters in pop culture.</description></item><item><title>10 best Sarasota bars we wish made USA TODAY Bars of the Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/30/best-sarasota-bars-missing-usa-today-bars-of-the-year-list/84351177007/</link><description>10 best Sarasota bars we wish made USA TODAY Bars of the Year</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota area this weekend (July 31-Aug. 3)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/31/things-to-do-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice-fla/85377075007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota area this weekend (July 31-Aug. 3)</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship football team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/28/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-football-team-poll/85345091007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area football teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Our can't miss Sarasota, Manatee area high school football games list</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/29/2025-high-school-football-games-to-watch-in-sarasota-manatee-county/85306567007/</link><description>Our can't miss Sarasota, Manatee area high school football games list</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Supersized luxury condo doesn't belong in downtown…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/30/sarasota-luxury-condo-poor-door/85411946007/</link><description>As a resident of downtown Sarasota and a member of theSansaracondominium community, I am calling on my fellow citizens to speak out against the proposedAdagiodevelopment.</description></item><item><title>Florida death row inmate Edward Zakrzewski has been…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/crime/2025/07/31/florida-execution-today-live-updates-edward-zakrzewski/85454831007/</link><description>Three decades after brutally murdering his wife and kids and escaping to Hawaii,Edward Zakrzewskiwill be executed today after the U.S. Supreme Court on Wednesday rejected an eleventh-hour attempt to halt theexecution.</description></item><item><title>August can be worst month in many ways and when it comes…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/31/florida-hurricane-season-forecast-slow-start-august-tropical-threats-katrina-andrew/85441728007/</link><description>August arrives with a whiff of impending calamity. Fourth-graders who have eschewed summer reading in favor of Minecraft must hastily identify the setting and main characters of "The Giver" by Lois Lowry. Miami Dolphins fans attempt to stay positive while knowing yet another seven-to-nine-win season lies ahead. Many are unprepared for the existential agita of National Clown Month, which feels like a gratuitous quantity of time in which to celebrate the clowning arts.</description></item><item><title>Mote unites combat wounded veterans and youth to help…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/31/mote-partnership-units-combat-wounded-veterans-and-youth-for-coral/85423640007/</link><description>Mote unites combat wounded veterans and youth to help…</description></item><item><title>After 2024 storm expenses, Sarasota eyes property rate tax increase</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/31/sarasota-says-it-will-assume-no-fema-reimbursements-in-coming-year/85403785007/</link><description>After 2024 storm expenses, Sarasota eyes property rate tax increase</description></item><item><title>Where did SMH rank on the 2025 Forbes best employers for women list?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/31/sarasota-memorial-among-top-3-of-americas-best-employers-for-women/85450816007/</link><description>Where did SMH rank on the 2025 Forbes best employers for women list?</description></item><item><title>What are the hottest days on record in Sarasota-Bradenton?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/31/what-are-the-hottest-days-on-record-in-sarasota-bradenton/85459927007/</link><description>What are the hottest days on record in Sarasota-Bradenton?</description></item><item><title>How much did Longboat mansion sells for after just 25 days on market?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/real-estate/2025/08/01/longboat-key-mansion-breaks-residential-sale-record-at-30-3-million/85462153007/</link><description>Compass Real Estate – a nationwide residential real estate firm –seized the recordfor the most expensive residential sale in Sarasota County history at $30.3 million on Thursday, July 31, according to the company's press release.</description></item></channel></rss>