<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sarasota Chamber of Commerce executive earns sales achievement award</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/04/sarasota-chamber-of-commerce-executive-earns-sales-achievement-award/85306344007/</link><description>Zach Henkel, membership investment manager for theGreater Sarasota Chamber of Commerce, was recently awarded the Dana Ketterling Lifetime Sales Achievement Award by theAssociation of Chamber of Commerce Executives.</description></item><item><title>Fly away! Breeze adds 19 new routes, including several from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/02/06/breeze-airways-florida-airports-destinations-new-routes-cost/78251054007/</link><description>Sometimes you just need to get away. Even if where you are is where others head to when they want to get away.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Trump, Vance defend Sydney Sweeney 'jeans' ad. Is she from Florida?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/sydney-sweeney-florida-jeans-ad-american-eagle-trump-vance/85502382007/</link><description>Six words many didn't think they'd ever see together: "American Eagle jeans" and "promotion of eugenics." Now, it's all anyone can talk about.</description></item><item><title>The five biggest snubs in the preseason college football poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/08/04/college-football-coaches-poll-rankings-snubs/85441264007/</link><description>The voters inthe preseason US LBM Coaches Pollhave weighed in, and the Top 25 is now out for fans and pundits to debate until they actually take the field in a few weeks.</description></item><item><title>Arch Manning expectations have Texas at No. 1. Are we sure he is ready?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/columnist/dan-wolken/2025/08/04/arch-manning-texas-coaches-poll-rankings-preseason/85458321007/</link><description>If everything we know about Texas’ starting quarterback was exactly the same except that his name was Art Janning instead of Arch Manning, theLonghornswould not bethe No. 1 teamin thepreseason US LBM Coaches Poll.</description></item><item><title>Why Charlie Woods could still earn place on Junior Ryder Cup team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/golf/2025/08/04/charlie-woods-junior-ryder-cup-captains-pick/85508805007/</link><description>Charlie Woods' hopes of makingUnited States Junior Ryder Cup teamaren't completely lost despite coming up short of an automatic last week at the49th Junior PGA Championships</description></item><item><title>Publix recalls Cheddar &amp; Herb Biscuits, here’s why</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/04/publix-cheddar-herb-biscuit-recall-soy-allergens/85505553007/</link><description>Did you pick up some Chedder &amp; Herb Biscuits from Publix last week? If you or someone in your household is allergic to soy, get rid of them.</description></item><item><title>Cracking window doesn't help: How to prevent child hot…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/04/hot-car-deaths-children-list-locations-florida-us-prevent/85506188007/</link><description>The number of deaths of babies and children dying in hot cars continues to increase.</description></item><item><title>Tropical Storm Dexter forms. Will Sarasota-Manatee see…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/08/04/national-hurricane-center-tropical-storm-dexter-sarasota-manatee-county/85506482007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Dexterformed late Sunday night, Aug. 3, off the coast of North Carolina, becoming thefourth named stormin the 2025 Atlantic hurricane season.</description></item><item><title>Tampa rapper Doechii snubs Florida during upcoming tour…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/doechii-live-from-the-swamp-tour-florida-dates-tickets/85502384007/</link><description>Doechiiis hitting the road this fall!</description></item><item><title>Waterfront access improved at small Nokomis park for Legacy Trail</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/04/lots-bought-at-trailhead-for-legacy-trail-and-north-port-connector/85458007007/</link><description>Waterfront access improved at small Nokomis park for Legacy Trail</description></item><item><title>Anti-Trump protests could keep Americans divided, angry</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/04/trump-protests-no-kings-violent-rage/85505352007/</link><description>It is easy to appreciate the righteous anger that leads todemonstrationsagainst the policies of the current leadership of the United States.</description></item><item><title>YIMBY could help Sarasota County address affordable housing crisis</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/04/yes-in-gods-back-yard-law-churches-could-address-housing-crunch/85411086007/</link><description>As Sarasota County policymakers and advocatessit down this fallto hash out bold approaches to the region's ongoing housing crisis, they’ll have a major new tool on the table – one that could help open hundreds of parcels of land owned by religious institutions.</description></item></channel></rss>