<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:05:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>FST wants to bring people together for human stories in 2025-26 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/31/sarasotas-fst-embraces-humanity-humor-as-202526-season-embraces-humanity-humor-and-heartfelt-stories/85663246007/</link><description>After several years ofCOVID-related challengesthat forced his five theaters to shut down and then slowly rebuild, Florida Studio Theatre Producing Artistic Director Richard Hopkins believes the company has “turned the last corner” on COVID and can look forward in new and more adventurous ways.</description></item><item><title>Finally! Sarasota to honor local hero Dickey Betts of Allman Brothers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/30/sarasota-dickey-betts-allman-brothers-highway-41-tribute/85852358007/</link><description>Dickey Betts’ nod to Highway 41 in the Allman Brothers Band anthem“Ramblin’ Man”is one of classic rock’s most recognizable lyrics — inspiring impromptu singalongs for more than half a century.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Woods highlights mercurial Junior Players round with hole-in-one</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/golf/pga-tour/2025/08/31/charlie-woods-junior-players-championship-hole-in-one/85921050007/</link><description>Daniel Montero isn't sure what compelled him to raise his camera phone an instant beforeCharlie Woodstook the club back for his tee shot at the par-3 third hole of thePlayers Stadium Courseat TPC Sawgrass on Aug. 31 during the final round of theJunior Players Championship.</description></item><item><title>How Charlie Woods fared in final round of Junior Players Championship</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/pga/2025/08/31/charlie-woods-score-today-junior-players-championship/85920398007/</link><description>Charlie Woodshad one major highlight in an otherwise mundane three days at the Junior Players Championship.</description></item><item><title>Game Balls: Week 2 top Sarasota, Manatee high school football performances</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/31/sarasota-manatee-florida-high-school-football-top-week-2-performers/85566016007/</link><description>Week 2 was a story of redemption for Sarasota-Manatee high school football teams.</description></item><item><title>Who may qualify for gynecologic cancer clinical trial at SMH?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/01/smh-hosting-clinical-trial-for-women-with-gynecologic-cancer/85867742007/</link><description>Women with advanced or recurring ovarian, peritoneal, or fallopian tube cancer may be eligible to participate in a newclinical trial offered by Sarasota Memorial’s Kolschowsky Research and Education Institute.</description></item><item><title>Labor Day weekend rains come and go. What about tropical…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/08/31/hurricane-center-forecast-outlook-labor-day-season-peak/85918729007/</link><description>While some of Florida is seeing soaking rains this Labor Day weekend,tropical systemsand their potential development are far from any land and it's expected to stay that way even as we move close to the traditional peak of hurricane season.</description></item><item><title>FSU football delivers an iconic Doak moment in upset win…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/fsu/football/2025/08/31/florida-state-football-alabama-doak-campbell-stadium/85811619007/</link><description>Mike Norvell said it best.</description></item><item><title>Who won largest Powerball, Mega Millions prizes in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/31/powerball-mega-millions-biggest-jackpot-edwin-castro-struyck-casarotti-kaltschmidt-cheng/85335143007/</link><description>Mega Millions and Powerball jackpots have reached$1 billion 13 times in history: Will theLabor Day 2025 Powerball drawingresult in the latest billion-dollar lottery winner?</description></item><item><title>Giuliani injured in New Hampshire car crash, spokesman…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/accident/2025/08/31/former-nyc-mayor-giuliani-injured-in-new-hampshire-car-crash/85923258007/</link><description>Former New York Mayor Rudolph Giuliani has been injured in a car crash in New Hampshire, his spokesman said.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Looking for Labor Day fun? 5 top events in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/28/best-things-to-do-sarasota-labor-day-weekend-2025/85779365007/</link><description>Looking forfun waysto spend the long Labor Day weekend? From the waters of Sarasota Bay to the streets of Englewood, the holiday brings a mix of family-friendly events and more adult-oriented entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota sidewalk cleanup removes safety risks</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/30/sarasota-desantis-sidewalks-art/85906177007/</link><description>A recentletterexpressed concern that our governor is causing sidewalks to be cleansed of artwork at Burns Court.</description></item><item><title>State DOGE scrutiny follows Manatee development stance</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/01/state-doge-audit-spotlight-on-manatee-after-development-decisions/85893288007/</link><description>Manatee County voters snubbed Tallahassee last fall when they rejected Gov. Ron DeSantis’ hand-picked, pro-development commission candidates and instead elected a slate of grassroots Republicans who promised to rein in runaway growth.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County commissioners looks for less expensive jail options</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/01/sarasota-county-considering-less-costly-jail-expansion-alternative/85893209007/</link><description>For years, Sarasota County has struggled with a problem it has yet to solve — a jail built for 773 inmates that now holds well over a thousand. Hallways double as sleeping quarters. Inspections flag chronic overcrowding. And every proposed fix has come with a price tag large enough to give taxpayers pause.</description></item></channel></rss>