<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:05:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Idina Menzel to perform at Sarasota gala. Tickets on sale today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/10/03/idina-menzel-sarasota-tickets/86445224007/</link><description>Tony Award-winning Broadway star and Disney’s “Frozen” voiceIdina Menzelwill headline the Sarasota Performing Arts Foundation Gala on March 6, 2026, at Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Week 7 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/week-7-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/86371291007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Oct. 3, 2025.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason Newcomer, Coach of Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>This weekend's best Prime Day deals you won't want to miss</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/weekend-october-amazon-prime-day-deals/86465982007/</link><description>October Prime Day 2025 is almost here, withAmazon’s Prime Big Deal Dayskicking off onTuesday, October 7. But honestly, I've never been one to wait around for anything. If you're impatient and want the deals now, I'm with you and I'm here to help.</description></item><item><title>Get the new 2025 Lego Star Wars Advent Calendar on sale while you can</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/shop-2025-lego-star-wars-advent-calendar/86497184007/</link><description>Believe it or not, it’salready time to buy Advent calendarsfor the2025 holiday season. We know, we know—it’s only October.</description></item><item><title>Get Target's exclusive 'Life of a Showgirl' CDs, vinyl: Shop now ❤️‍🔥</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/how-to-buy-taylor-swift-the-life-of-a-showgirl-cds-vinyl-at-target/86495795007/</link><description>Taylor Swift's newest album era has (at long last) arrived, with the release of "The Life of a Showgirl!" To celebrate her 12th album release, the pop star has teamed up with Target forthree exclusive "The Life of a Showgirl" CDs.</description></item><item><title>How much did Venice cut taxes for the 2025-26 fiscal…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/10/03/venice-council-approves-172-5-million-budget-adopts-reduced-tax-rate/86241306007/</link><description>VENICE – The Venice City Council needed less than 10 minutes Tuesday, Sept. 23, to approve the “rolled-back” rate for  the millage and approve a $172.5 million budget for the 2025-26 fiscal year budget.</description></item><item><title>FHSAA expands 2025 football playoffs with 16-team…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/fhsaa-expands-2025-high-school-football-playoffs-16-team-invitational-tournaments-fit/86499211007/</link><description>The FHSAA has expanded the football postseason with additional 16-team tournaments for teams that don't qualify for the traditional brackets, according to an email obtained by USA TODAY's Florida Network.</description></item><item><title>'Mean Girls' Day 2025, here's how to stream all 3 'Mean…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/10/03/mean-girls-day-streaming-movies-october/86494318007/</link><description>Friday, Oct. 3, may be the date of Taylor Swift’s highly anticipated“Life of a Showgirl” album release,but it’s already a very important day in the pop culture world for another reason entirely.</description></item><item><title>Goliath grouper? See photos of this giant found in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/03/goliath-grouper-photos-video-florida-habitat-apply-harvest/86499134007/</link><description>What's over8 feet long and can hit 800 pounds?</description></item><item><title>Democrats still seek gun reforms after Stoneman Douglas…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/10/03/florida-democrats-push-jaimes-law-to-close-ammo-loophole/86498253007/</link><description>Two South Florida Democrats will once again try to close a loophole inFlorida gun laws that allows people to buy ammunition when they can’t pass a background check to purchase a firearm.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues Bradenton hospital after leg amputation over alleged delay</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/10/03/mom-sues-bradenton-hospital-after-leg-amputation-over-alleged-delay/86062040007/</link><description>When Hailey Van Dam woke up on July 2, 2024, she couldn’t have predicted that her life would forever be changed in less than 24 hours.</description></item><item><title>Reports: Prosecutors to convene grand jury in Hope Florida case</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/10/03/grand-jury-to-meet-in-tallahassee-on-hope-florida-reports-say/86498268007/</link><description>Prosecutors in Tallahassee are preparing to convene agrand juryin connection with theHope FloridaFoundation controversy, according to news reports published Oct. 3.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Congressman says he will vote to release Epstein files</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/10/03/steube-epstein-files-trump/86484574007/</link><description>Sarasota CongressmanGreg Steubetold the Herald-Tribune he would vote in favor of releasing the famedEpstein Fileswhen the motion likely comes before the U.S. House of Representatives later this month.</description></item><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item></channel></rss>