<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:04:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte countiesmusic</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/07/25/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-sarasota-bradenton-punta-gorda/85242974007/</link><description>As we've said before,summer in the Sarasota areais when the many talented musicians that call Florida home take center stage, and that's certainly true of this week's concert picks, composed entirely of performers from the Sunshine State.</description></item><item><title>Feds begin flights out of Florida-run Alligator Alcatrazstate</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/25/feds-begin-flights-out-of-florida-run-alligator-alcatraz/85371340007/</link><description>Flights out of aremote state-run detention centerin the Florida Everglades have started, according to state and federal officials.</description></item><item><title>Florida's Lake Placid highlighted by Southern Charm. Here's whyHidden Gems</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/07/25/southern-living-florida-lake-placid-small-town-caladium-festival/85353081007/</link><description>Need new places to explore? Try outLake Placid; no, not the one in New York.</description></item><item><title>Why is Trump going to Scotland? It may be an unfriendly welcomePolitics</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/25/trump-scotland-national-newspaper-front-page-viral/85370608007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpis headed toScotland on July 25, where he is expected to meet with the British Prime Minister and visit his golf resorts.</description></item><item><title>Miller Lite giving away free beers: List of Florida bars participatingnews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/25/when-where-how-miller-lite-free-beer-florida-bars-list/85369935007/</link><description>Free beer in Florida next Friday!Miller Lite is celebrating 50 yearsof beers in all 50 states by giving out 50,000 free beers on International Beer Day next week. And more than 30 bars in Florida are participating.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota commits to spend $1.7 million on nature park at Bobby Jonessarasota</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/25/bobby-jones-club-nature-park-to-get-1-7-million-in-improvements/85198035007/</link><description>The city of Sarasota plans to spend $1.7 million to improve Bobby Jones Golf Club and supplement the publicly owned course's nature park for the wildlife, residents and the environment as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Workforce housing for DeSoto teachers could be model for Sarasota-Manatee countieslocal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/24/affordable-housing-for-desoto-teachers-could-be-model-for-sarasota-manatee/85329082007/</link><description>Facing a severe housing crunch for its teachers – many of whom endure long commutes – DeSoto County Schools has given the green light to a Sarasota-based developer to build workforce apartments for educators on school-owned property.</description></item><item><title>St. Armands residents want quicker access back home after hurricanessarasota</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/24/survey-shows-support-on-st-armands-for-city-to-manage-stormwater/85321419007/</link><description>Residents and stakeholders of St. Armands Key, one of Sarasota’s “crown jewels” in destinations, showed overwhelming support for more focused help for those on thebarrier islandbefore and after storms, nearly a year after it wasinundated by Hurricane Helene’s storm surge.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)events</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/24/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-july-24-27/85272193007/</link><description>From a tropical-themed Christmas celebration and a patriotic car show fundraiser to circus thrills and classic movies,Sarasota is stacked with fun things to dothis weekend — indoors, outdoors, and even under the stars.</description></item><item><title>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announces DOGE audit for Manatee CountyManatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/24/florida-gov-ron-desantis-announces-doge-audit-for-manatee-county/85361775007/</link><description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis put Manatee County front and center on Thursday, July 24, inhis effort to impose DOGE-styled, state scrutiny and potentially mandated budget cuts on local governments across the state.</description></item><item><title>Best restaurants in Florida? 17 fun, local spots worth the drivedining</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/25/best-florida-restaurants-unique-spots-worth-road-trip/84505274007/</link><description>Forget the chainsduring your next road trip. Florida is home tosome of the finest restaurants in the country— and also some of the funkiest, funniest, and flat-out most unforgettable.</description></item><item><title>Trump wants Sarasota politician to run Republican National Committeesarasota</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/25/trump-backs-sarasotas-gruters-as-rnc-chair-amid-florida-cfo-race/85370742007/</link><description>This story was updated with a statement from State Senator Joe Gruters.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis's Ringling Museum plan scares off donors, threatening $750K.</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/25/fears-realized-ringling-museum-donors-reconsider-gifts-post-desantis-plan/85364077007/</link><description>When Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis proposedtransferring The John and Mable Ringling Museum of Artfrom Florida State University to New College of Florida earlier this year, museum supporters warned the move would scare away donors.</description></item><item><title>Video: Heckler calls Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis a "nazi"</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/state/2025/07/25/video-heckler-calls-florida-gov-ron-desantis-a-nazi-during-remarks-about-hulk-hogan-death/85371873007/</link><description>Florida Gov.Ron DeSantis put Manatee County front and centeron Thursday, July 24, inhis effort to impose DOGE-styled, state scrutiny and potentially mandated budget cuts on local governments across the state.</description></item><item><title>Donor family alleges breach of contract against New College Foundation</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/07/25/donor-family-alleges-breach-of-contract-against-new-college-foundation/85354668007/</link><description>Four years after a family donated $156,000 toNew College of Florida Foundationto establish a scholarship fund in honor of their late wife and mother, the family is suing the foundation for breach of contract.</description></item></channel></rss>