<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 07:04:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 21-24</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/21/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-21-24/85677582007/</link><description>Don’t let the summer heat keep you from enjoying all the fun in Sarasota and Bradenton, witheventsstarting today and running through the weekend.</description></item><item><title>Top Sarasota restaurant for Philly cheesesteaks closed — what’s next</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/22/sarasota-philly-cheesesteak-restaurant-gentiles-closes-johnny-longhots-opening-oct/85758265007/</link><description>One of thebest sandwich shops in Sarasotahasshuttered.</description></item><item><title>District 2A-9, Independent Football Previews: Cardinal Mooney, North Port</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/22/cardinal-mooney-north-port-2025-high-school-football-team-previews/85545504007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in FHSAA District 2A-9 and Independent.</description></item><item><title>Will the historic Blackburn Point Road Swing Bridge be replaced?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/22/sarasota-county-weights-options-for-historic-casey-key-swing-bridge/85662742007/</link><description>OSPREY – For the second time in 25 years, Sarasota County is faced with the decision of whether to replace the historic Blackburn Point Road swing bridge.</description></item><item><title>'Cooling' Sarasota-Manatee real home sales continue downward trend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/22/cooling-sarasota-manatee-real-home-sales-continue-downward-trend/85765680007/</link><description>The Sarasota-Bradenton area's real estate market showed signs of stabilization in July, according to the most recentindustry report.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Sarasota boys golf wins match against…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-august-18-23-2025/85715808007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Aug. 18-23, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/22/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice/85630718007/</link><description>This week inSarasota area eventswill feature concerts by out-of-town acts touring, locally based musicians playing their hometown, and even one show combining both.</description></item><item><title>Venice High volleyball player wins Fab 15 fan poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/22/venice-high-volleyball-player-wins-fab-15-fan-poll/85778104007/</link><description>TheSarasota Herald-Tribunerecently unveiled its The Fab 15 list of the Sarasota-Manatee counties' top players to watch entering the 2025 high school volleyball season. To see the full listCLICK HERE</description></item><item><title>Sarasota must act now on Van Wezel's future</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/22/van-wezel-sarasota-maga-canada-trump/85777984007/</link><description>Just as it is unreasonable for the Sarasota City Commission totake over a year choosing a new city manager, it is also unreasonable to take more than two years todecide the fate of the Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/22/florida-high-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-1/85565971007/</link><description>We have arrived at another Florida high school football season, and Sarasota-Manatee county programs will join others from across the state in taking the gridiron.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County Schools avoid layoffs, but budget woes linger</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/22/sarasota-superintendent-reshuffles-staff-to-weather-budget-shortfall/85776604007/</link><description>Sarasota County Schools Superintendent Terry Connor says no teachers have been laid off this year — despite swirling rumors — and insists the district’s proactive summer staffing moves were designed to “protect the classroom” in the face of budget shortfalls and enrollment shifts.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Roundup: See which teams came out as winners in Week 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/23/high-school-football-week-1-roundup-cardinal-mooney-cruises-to-win-manatee-venice-fall/85565985007/</link><description>SARASOTA – The Cougars scored 35 points before the Friday Night Lights were even turned on for the regular-season opener, but they had no answer for Friday Night Lightning.</description></item></channel></rss>