<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:05:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Players stages premiere of festival winning comedy</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/09/festival-winning-comedy-gets-premiere-at-sarasota-players/85458001007/</link><description>As a pastry chef, Hannah Mitchell could be providing any of the sweet treats that accompany the ceremonies that take place in the “Happy Endings Wedding Chapel,” which has its premiere Aug. 12 at the Sarasota Players.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota’s Rise Above stages musical ‘Matilda’ to kick off school year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/10/musical-version-of-roald-dahls-matilda-takes-stage-at-rise-above/85463754007/</link><description>Whenever he stages a show for Rise Above Performing Arts with many young characters, Artistic Director Jacob Ruscoe knows he will see a lot of people sign up for auditions, but even he was surprised by the “huge response” for his upcoming production of “Matilda: The Musical.”</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>The 10 best Florida high school football games vs. national powers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/11/florida-high-school-football-aquinas-chaminade-mater-dei-img-academy-frances-miami-northwestern/85480946007/</link><description>Florida high school football teams will take on some of the biggest programs in the nation this year.</description></item><item><title>It's first day of school in most Florida counties. Here's a list</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/11/school-start-florida-list-by-county-sales-tax-holiday-no-cell-phones/85578536007/</link><description>Give yourself some extra time this morning.</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: Travis Hunter, a 70-yard field goal…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/10/travis-hunter-a-70-yard-field-goal-and-tua-starts-for-dolphins-2md/83674673007/</link><description>The first week of NFL preseason games is in the books. Here's what happened with Florida's three NFL teams:</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for Aug. 10…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/10/florida-lottery-results-sunday-august-10-2025/85604573007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, Aug. 10, 2025</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>The vias of Palm Beach's Worth Avenue are hidden gems to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/08/11/the-vias-of-palm-beachs-worth-avenue-are-hidden-gems-to-explore/78410369007/</link><description>This story is part of our weeklyHidden Gems feature seriesas the USA TODAY Network–Florida takes readers around the state to highlight some of our most interesting attractions.</description></item><item><title>Florida DOGE audit of Manatee County spending starts with site visit</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/11/florida-doge-audit-team-checks-out-manatee-county-spending-in-review/85557667007/</link><description>The Florida Department of Government Efficiency audited and interviewed Manatee County officials and staff onsite during the first week of August as part ofstatewide efforts to cut down on local government spending.</description></item><item><title>VOTE: Who would you pick to be No. 1 on The Big 15 list for 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/11/vote-for-top-sarasota-herald-tribune-2025-big-15-high-school-football-recruit-poll/85540827007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune unveiled its The Big 15 list of the Sarasota-Manatee counties' top college football recruits entering the 2025 high school football season. To see the full listCLICK HERE</description></item><item><title>Gastropub opens in Lakewood Ranch, with nearby Irish pub in the works</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/11/allswell-gastropub-opens-lakewood-ranch/85541957007/</link><description>Gastropub opens in Lakewood Ranch, with nearby Irish pub in the works</description></item><item><title>Rent prices in Sarasota are down 5% year-over-year in July</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/11/rent-prices-continue-to-fall-in-sarasota/85576196007/</link><description>Sarasota’s July rent report brought good news for renters: Rent prices are falling in the area market.</description></item></channel></rss>