<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:05:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>New adventure park opens in Sarasota with family fun attractions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/10/01/sarasota-new-urban-air-adventure-park-family-fun-attractions/86445539007/</link><description>Another adventure park just opened its doors in Sarasota County for family fun, afterDo The Beach Adventure Parkopened in North Port earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>1 of 2 Florida celebs sent home on 'Dancing with the Stars,' see scores</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/10/01/who-voted-off-dancing-with-stars-episode-three-tiktok-night-contestant-scores-full-list/86453363007/</link><description>The competition on"Dancing with the Stars"is heating up, and it's only episode three.</description></item><item><title>5 best free and fun things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/10/02/top-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton-oct-3-5/86371827007/</link><description>It's a new season in the Sarasota area — the start of fall, and snowbirds beginning to flock back forOctober— and you'll see both reflected in the lineup of events taking place this weekend, including free and outdoor options.</description></item><item><title>How could system off Florida coast affect your plans through weekend?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/10/02/nhc-tracking-disturbance-off-florida-coast-rain-breezy-conditions-impacts/86471432007/</link><description>Two newtropical disturbanceshave appeared on theNational Hurricane Center's tropical outlook map and one of them is located off South Florida.</description></item><item><title>I have flight coming up. Will government shutdown impact air travel?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/02/government-shutdown-florida-airports-delays-donald-trump/86466943007/</link><description>We're officially on day two of thefederal government shutdown, with President Donald Trump and congressional Democratsblaming each otherfor failing to reach a funding agreement.</description></item><item><title>McDonald's Halloween Happy Meals are back, when you can buy Boo Buckets</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/02/mcdonalds-boo-buckets-halloween-happy-meals-cost-when-october-characters-list/86471972007/</link><description>Spooky season is officially upon us andMcDonald’s is celebrating with Boo Bucketsagain!</description></item><item><title>Sarasota group sets date for community event after…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/10/01/sarasota-group-sets-date-for-community-event-after-pridewalk-removal/86332894007/</link><description>In response to the recent painting over of Sarasota’s “Pridewalk”, Project Pride SRQ will host a “compassion at the crosswalk” event on October 4at the former Pride crosswalk sitein downtown Sarasota, which was removed in August. 28.</description></item><item><title>How different positions grade, star college player or…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/10/02/ranking-florida-prospects-college-football-nfl-future/86302793007/</link><description>Recruiting rankings are an inexact science and putting a list of top recruits together can lead to heated arguments.</description></item><item><title>10 burning questions at the midway point of the prep…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/florida-high-school-football-midseason-10-questions/86455424007/</link><description>The Florida high school football season has passed its halfway point.</description></item><item><title>What you need to know about latest tropical conditions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/10/02/tropical-updates-storm-tracker-hurricane-imelda-florida-impacts-national-hurricane-center/86460620007/</link><description>We know your time is valuable. Here is a quick look at what's happening in the tropics to help you stay informed.Want more details?</description></item><item><title>40-year-old Kilwins reopening symbolizes post-hurricane resilienceMark J. Rochester</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/10/02/sarasota-fl-kilwins-st-armands-circle-reopening-hurricane/86372405007/</link><description>Sometimes, the most important news in a coastal town isn't the political wrangling in Tallahassee or thelatest development proposal. Sometimes, the true pulse of a community is found in the simple, familiar pleasures — like the scent of warm, hand-paddled fudge wafting down John Ringling Boulevard.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Week 7 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/week-7-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/86371291007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Oct. 3, 2025.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive, Defensive Player of the Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Luxury condo tower pitched for downtown Sarasota with pools and park</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/real-estate/2025/10/02/new-sarasota-luxury-condo-tower/86367139007/</link><description>A Chicago-baseddeveloperis looking to build a luxury condominium in downtown Sarasota's Rosemary District.</description></item><item><title>Florida October hurricane forecast: After Humberto derails Imelda, threat focus shifts</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hurricane/2025/10/02/florida-hurricane-forecast-for-october-when-threats-shift-to-gulf/86463274007/</link><description>Like an email from Mr. António Guterres informing you that you have won 67,000,000 USD in the U.N. Global Raffle, things that seem too good to be true usually are.</description></item></channel></rss>