<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:19:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Maryland pizza chain makes Sarasota County debut</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/09/maryland-ledo-pizza-chain-opens-first-sarasota-restaurant-north-port/84495397007/</link><description>Maryland pizza chain makes Sarasota County debut</description></item><item><title>Scottish Open: Tee times, TV options for Round 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/pga/2025/07/09/scottish-open-tee-times-round-1-tv-streaming/84517507007/</link><description>The PGA Tour takes its talents to Scotland as the Scottish Open begins Thursday morning.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship softball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>These 10 supplements are up to 72% off during Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/prime-day-deals-supplements-creatine-iron-vitamin-d-protein-more-on-sale/84479237007/</link><description>I don't gatekeep my health secrets. I'm on a GLP-1 for weight loss, but I also pair it with a substantial list ofsupplements to reduce the side effects of the injections, while maximizing the health benefits. Because my kitchen counter looks like a pharmacy, I'm usually on the lookout for good deals on supplements whenever I'm running low.</description></item><item><title>Up to 86% off: Top Prime Day deals on smartwatches</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/amazon-prime-day-deals-smartwatches/84492719007/</link><description>Even though it's a bit late for New Year's resolutions, it's never too late to start a new workout goal. A great way to do that? Buying a brand new smartwatch.</description></item><item><title>13 popular Prime Day deals that might surprise you</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/popular-prime-day-deals-that-might-surprise-you-people/84526410007/</link><description>During a major sales event likeAmazon Prime Day, I can count on certain products to be pretty popular.Everyone loves a good Apple deal, and a lot of those devices have been best-sellers during this week's Prime Day sale. Other popular purchases typically include big ticket items likeTVsandlaptops. It all makes sense.</description></item><item><title>Petition groups get partial victory in Florida lawsuit…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/09/judge-blocks-part-of-new-florida-law-restricting-amendment-process/84517330007/</link><description>A federal judge upheld most of a new Florida law toughening regulations for petition gathering, butordered that state officialscouldn't enforce a provision forsome petition groupsthat prohibited nonresident and noncitizen volunteers from gathering signatures.</description></item><item><title>Craving a Snack Wrap? Fan-favorite returns to McDonald's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/mcdonald-snack-wrap-menu-new-spicy-mcmuffin/84523099007/</link><description>McDonald's isbringing back the Snack Wrap for good,after years of fans demanding its return.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day deals on pool pumps, vacuums, LED…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/how-long-amazon-prime-days-pool-pumps-vacuums-led-lights-deals-discounts/84502325007/</link><description>Today marks the second day of Amazon’s biggest online shopping sale of the year.Amazon Prime Daystarted as a one-day sales event in 2015 to celebrate the company’s 20th anniversary.</description></item><item><title>Nathan Benderson Park doesn't need massive, wasteful…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/08/benderson-park-rowing-sports-money/84505188007/</link><description>I have loved and supportedNathan Benderson Parksince before it held its first event more than 15 years ago.</description></item><item><title>Venice City Council gives green light to SMH to build…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/07/09/next-buildings-on-smh-venice-campus-could-be-as-hight-as-150-feet-tall/84500472007/</link><description>Venice City Council gives green light to SMH to build…</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County moves $10 million for stormwater drainage improvements</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/09/sarasota-county-puts-more-money-for-phillippi-after-24-storm-flooding/84503514007/</link><description>Sarasota County moves $10 million for stormwater drainage improvements</description></item><item><title>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/09/sarasota-officers-rescue-driver-after-fiery-wreck/84513084007/</link><description>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</description></item><item><title>Manatee County earns highest-ever grade on Florida school report card</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/07/09/manatee-schools-see-gains-in-science-graduation-and-a-rated-campuses/84517624007/</link><description>Manatee County earns highest-ever grade on Florida school report card</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Florida's appeal to enforce immigration law</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/09/supreme-court-rejects-florida-appeal-to-enforce-immigration-law-uthmeier/84523556007/</link><description>WASHINGTON − Florida can't enforce a controversialnew lawtargeting undocumented immigrants entering Florida, theSupreme Courtdetermined on July 9 in rejecting anemergency appeal from the state.</description></item></channel></rss>