<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Review: ‘Cabaret’ sings, dances and stings at Sarasota Players</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/02/review-sarasota-players-stage-powerful-cabaret-for-summer-run/85472584007/</link><description>Review: ‘Cabaret’ sings, dances and stings at Sarasota Players</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship football team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/28/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-football-team-poll/85345091007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area football teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Our can't miss Sarasota, Manatee area high school football games list</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/29/2025-high-school-football-games-to-watch-in-sarasota-manatee-county/85306567007/</link><description>Our can't miss Sarasota, Manatee area high school football games list</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high school football schedules</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/02/florida-lottery-results-saturday-august-2-2025/85495474007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, Aug. 2, 2025</description></item><item><title>Hidden gem: Topsail has it all from the gulf, lakes and…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/08/03/hidden-gem-found-at-topsail-hill-preserve-state-park/84465672007/</link><description>This story is part of our weekly Hidden Gems feature series as the USA TODAY Network-Florida takes readers around the state to highlight some of our most interesting attractions.</description></item><item><title>"Good Trouble" rises in Bradenton: hundreds rally for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/08/03/bradenton-joins-good-trouble-lives-on-protests/85276177007/</link><description>The cacophony of car horns reverberating off the Manatee County Administration building earlier this month, wasn't just noise; it was a testament to a vibrant, engaged community making its voice heard.</description></item><item><title>Explore the hidden mangrove tunnels and wildlife at…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/08/03/ted-sperling-park-at-south-lido-key-sarasotas-premier-nature-park-for-kayaking-mangrove-tunnels-and/85199397007/</link><description>Explore the hidden mangrove tunnels and wildlife at…</description></item><item><title>Mental health crisis: Amid suicide spike, frontline…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/03/florida-211-helpline-suicide-988-tallahassee-country-club-mental-health-crisis/85312098007/</link><description>988 SUICIDE AND CRISIS LIFELINE:Navigating a mental health issue for yourself or a loved one can be a difficult experience. You can call or text 988 to connect with a trained counselor.</description></item><item><title>Former Rep. Al Lawson could join 2026 Florida governor race</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/02/tallahassee-al-lawson-says-he-may-run-for-florida-governor-in-2026/85493064007/</link><description>Democratic former U.S. Rep. and longtime state lawmakerAl Lawson Jr.says he's mulling a run for Florida governor in 2026, attributing his interest to what he calls the displeasure of the state's Black community with themost prominent Democratic candidatein the race so far having been a Republican.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota area this weekend (July 31-Aug. 3)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/31/things-to-do-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice-fla/85377075007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota area this weekend (July 31-Aug. 3)</description></item><item><title>FST actor gets in shape asfor comedy ‘Don’t Dress for Dinner’</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/03/romantic-affairs-trigger-comic-farce-dont-dress-for-dinner-at-fst/85275157007/</link><description>Even as he works to best understand and connect with his character in the comedy “Don’t Dress for Dinner” at Florida Studio Theatre, actor Gil Brady knows that some of his most important preparation will be in staying in shape.</description></item><item><title>Manatee High alum enjoying his 'Prime' for Savannah Bananas</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/03/vin-mannix-manatee-high-alum-enjoying-his-prime-for-savannah-bananas/84367564007/</link><description>Correlle Primeknows he is entertaining.</description></item></channel></rss>