<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 23:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/15/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-palmetto/85528088007/</link><description>As we enter mid-August, we're definitely in the slow time of the year for Sarasota area events, including live music. However, we still found five items for this week's concert picks installment, starting with a few notable tribute shows.</description></item><item><title>The Fab 15: Who are the Sarasota, Manatee volleyball players to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/12/sarasota-manatee-county-top-15-volleyball-players-to-watch-in-2025/85512979007/</link><description>On the surface, it looked as if it was a down year for volleyball in the Sarasota and Manatee area a year ago since no team made it to the state semifinals.</description></item><item><title>Vote for best 2025 high school football team in Manatee, Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/best-manatee-sarasota-area-2025-high-school-football-team-vote/85531382007/</link><description>High school football teams are getting ready to take the field for the first time in the 2025 season on Friday, Aug. 15.</description></item><item><title>Football Roundup: Venice cruises past Gadsden; Booker edges Manatee in ugly win</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/sarasota-manatee-football-roundup-for-fhsaa-ssaa-games-for-aug-15/85542153007/</link><description>VENICE – It is, after all, a “Kickoff Classic.” A new beginning.</description></item><item><title>Leadership Manatee selects members for annual civic engagement program</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/17/leadership-manatee-selects-members-for-annual-civic-engagement-program/85359313007/</link><description>Leadership Manatee recently announced the 2025-26 Leadership Manatee Class, a program of the Manatee Chamber Foundation in partnership with Bradenton Kiwanis.</description></item><item><title>A love letter to our community, with a citrus-scented…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/08/17/manatee-co-defies-scrutiny-with-13-5-m-farm-purchase-for-library/85477630007/</link><description>There has been a lot of local news from Manatee County in recent weeks, but one of the best-read stories has been the unanimous decision to purchase the Mixon Fruit Farms property.</description></item><item><title>Step back in time and through a forest portal to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/08/17/step-back-in-time-to-richloam-general-store-in-webster-florida/85505615007/</link><description>This story is part of our weeklyHidden Gems feature seriesas the USA TODAY Network-Florida takes readers around the state to highlight some of our most interesting attractions.</description></item><item><title>Who are the wide-eyed triplets who were born recently in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/17/six-endangered-lemurs-born-at-conservation-reserve-in-myakka-city/85452623007/</link><description>Six lemur infants, all endangered species, were born this season at the Lemur Conservation Foundation’s reserve in Myakka City.</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: Dolphins, Bucs win, Jaguars tie in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/17/preseason-week-2-dolphins-buccaneers-win-jaguars-tie-2md/83674674007/</link><description>Florida's three NFL teams came away with two wins and a tie. Here's what happened in Preseason Week 2:</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 14-17</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/14/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-14-17/85580403007/</link><description>From rocking guitar riffs to side-splitting comedy, this weekend’s Sarasota-Manateeentertainment calendaroffers something for just about every taste.</description></item><item><title>Haters won't admit Trump's success and popularity</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/15/trump-immigrants-inflation-safety-fbi-doge-pelletier/85657736007/</link><description>The truth is thatPresident Donald Trumpis making life for ALL Americans better.</description></item><item><title>New musical by ‘Wicked’ composer opening at Manatee Players</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/17/stephen-schwartz-musical-to-make-local-debut-at-manatee-players/85529368007/</link><description>Director Rick Kerby is excited to have the Manatee Performing Arts Center be one of the first community theaters in the country to get the rights for the musical stage version of the 1998 animated film “The Prince of Egypt.”</description></item><item><title>Protection from hurricanes a priority for Selby Gardens' new expansion</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/17/research-and-collection-protection-at-stake-in-selby-gardens-new-phase/85659039007/</link><description>Marie Selby Botanical Gardens houses a world-class collections of plants, but last year's hurricanes, Helene and Milton, threatened its future. Phase 2 of the garden's masterplan was set up with their protection a priority.</description></item></channel></rss>