<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 05:05:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/10/best-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton-venice-fl/84471720007/</link><description>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</description></item><item><title>MLB Draft: Venice High grad Marek Houston projected to be first rounder</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/mlb/2025/07/11/2025-mlb-draft-first-round-marek-houston-wake-forest-shortstop-venice-graduate/84518614007/</link><description>After his senior season on the Venice High baseball team, Marek Houston received an invitation to attend the Major League Baseball Draft Combine in San Diego.</description></item><item><title>↠ Popular last-chance Prime Day deals worth clicking by midnight</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/11/last-chance-amazon-prime-day-deals-sales/84448163007/</link><description>What day is it? Is it still July? After three product-packed days, we've reached the final countdown:Amazon Prime Day 2025endstonight, July 11. TheUSA TODAY Shopping teamhas been tracking all the most popular price cuts, the deepest discounts and yes, some of the most unexpected finds from the big sale.</description></item><item><title>The craziest Prime Day Apple deals end tonight. Here's what to shop</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/11/last-chance-prime-day-apple-deals/84545803007/</link><description>Still thinking about pulling the trigger on a new pair of Apple AirPods? I'm here to tell you that you should not wait much longer. The2025 Amazon Prime Day sale endstonight, July 11and the best deals are sure to disappear.</description></item><item><title>Time's running out: Save 44% on KitchenAid's cordless gadget bundle</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/11/amazon-prime-day-2025-sale-kitchenaid-go-cordless-bundle-deal/84666104007/</link><description>Why buy just onepopular KitchenAid gadgetwhen you can get four top-sellers in one bundle—and score it while it's on sale at Prime Day 2025? Sound too good to be true? Well, thanks to Amazon's latest batch oflast-chance Prime Day deals, that unicorn find is actually a reality with thisKitchenAid Go Cordless Bundle.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/10/all-time-list-of-every-sarasota-manatee-fhsaa-baseball-championship-team/84287441007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state…</description></item><item><title>Beloved ‘Frog and Toad’ children’s stories sing in Asolo…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/07/11/frog-and-toad-sing-in-family-musical-at-asolo-rep/84458811007/</link><description>Beloved ‘Frog and Toad’ children’s stories sing in Asolo…</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/07/11/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-englewood-anna-maria-island-palmetto/84430282007/</link><description>Like many weeksin Julyandthe Sarasota area's off-season, this week's concert picks largely consist of talented musicians who call Florida home. However, we do kick things off with a reggae musician from California, who visits the area while on tour with a group from Maryland.</description></item><item><title>Steube plays ugly politics with One Big Beautiful Bill…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/07/11/steube-medicaid-one-big-beautiful-bill/84585203007/</link><description>"Borrow and Spend" CongressmanGreg Steubeof Sarasota says theOne Big Beautiful Bill– which was recentlysigned into law– will cut taxes for Americans.</description></item><item><title>State officials lift health advisory warning for North Lido Beach</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/11/sarasotas-north-lido-beach-under-state-bacteria-advisory-warning/84583077007/</link><description>State officials lift health advisory warning for North Lido Beach</description></item><item><title>New foundation led by CAN Community Health aims to address HIV care</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/healthcare/2025/07/11/new-can-community-health-foundation-honors-susan-terry/84499526007/</link><description>New foundation led by CAN Community Health aims to address HIV care</description></item><item><title>Avelo extends Florida flight schedule through February. What to know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/11/avelo-extends-east-coast-flight-schedule-february-battle-boycott-immigration/84612970007/</link><description>Avelo Airlines, which has come under fire for agreeing to transport detained immigrants, announced July 9 it is extending its East Coast flight schedule to mid-February 2026. Avelo has routes to 11 Florida airports.</description></item><item><title>10 essential new Sarasota restaurants that live up to the hype</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/11/best-new-sarasota-restaurants-essentials-that-are-worth-the-hype/83648754007/</link><description>We launched our essential Sarasota restaurants series last week with my picks for10 best everyday dining destinations— satisfying spots that won’t wreck your budget.</description></item></channel></rss>