<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota’s Rise Above stages musical ‘Matilda’ to kick off school year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/10/musical-version-of-roald-dahls-matilda-takes-stage-at-rise-above/85463754007/</link><description>Whenever he stages a show for Rise Above Performing Arts with many young characters, Artistic Director Jacob Ruscoe knows he will see a lot of people sign up for auditions, but even he was surprised by the “huge response” for his upcoming production of “Matilda: The Musical.”</description></item><item><title>The key differences in the preseason coaches and AP poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/08/11/college-football-poll-coaches-ap-differences/85612024007/</link><description>The preseason picture is complete: One week after Bowl Subdivision head coaches weighed in with thedebut US LBM Coaches Poll, media members have their say with theAssociated Press preseason Top 25.</description></item><item><title>Hurricane season is getting busier, here's how to get your house ready</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/08/11/florida-hurricane-preparation-home-before-storms-tropical-storm-erin/85505564007/</link><description>After a slow start to the 2025 hurricane season, things are picking up. TneNational Hurricane Centeris watching Tropical Storm Erin and another Atlantic weather system with the potential to develop into a tropical depression.</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' week 7: How to watch, who got…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/11/when-new-episodes-bachelor-in-paradise-how-where-watch-stream-full-cast-contestant-list/85606374007/</link><description>"Bachelor in Paradise"is back after a year-long hiatus, followingformer Bachelor Nation contestantsas they attempt a second (or third, or fourth) chance at finding their soulmate on national television.</description></item><item><title>David Jolly faces pressure as Al Lawson eyes governor’s…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/11/al-lawson-signals-26-bid-for-governor-if-jolly-cant-unite-democrats/85576787007/</link><description>David Jolly is on notice: He has three months to prove he's built a coalition capable of winning the governor's mansion or Jolly will face a challenge from Al Lawson Jr., the Democratic dean of North Florida politics.</description></item><item><title>The 10 best Florida high school football games vs…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/11/florida-high-school-football-aquinas-chaminade-mater-dei-img-academy-frances-miami-northwestern/85480946007/</link><description>Florida high school football teams will take on some of the biggest programs in the nation this year.</description></item><item><title>What time is Trump speaking today? Watch live remarks on…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/08/11/trump-crime-dc-livestream/85606357007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpis scheduled to speak on Aug. 11 about hispublic safety initiativein Washington, D.C.</description></item><item><title>Tiffany Trump, her mom Marla Maples post baby Boulos…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/11/tiffany-trump-baby-michael-boulos-marla-maples-instagram/85545239007/</link><description>Since the day she was born,Tiffany Trump has grown upin the spotlight − literally.</description></item><item><title>Florida DOGE audit of Manatee County spending starts with site visit</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/11/florida-doge-audit-team-checks-out-manatee-county-spending-in-review/85557667007/</link><description>The Florida Department of Government Efficiency audited and interviewed Manatee County officials and staff onsite during the first week of August as part ofstatewide efforts to cut down on local government spending.</description></item><item><title>Rent prices in Sarasota are down 5% year-over-year in July</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/11/rent-prices-continue-to-fall-in-sarasota/85576196007/</link><description>Sarasota’s July rent report brought good news for renters: Rent prices are falling in the area market.</description></item><item><title>VOTE: Who would you pick to be No. 1 on The Big 15 list for 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/11/vote-for-top-sarasota-herald-tribune-2025-big-15-high-school-football-recruit-poll/85540827007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune unveiled its The Big 15 list of the Sarasota-Manatee counties' top college football recruits entering the 2025 high school football season. To see the full listCLICK HERE</description></item><item><title>Gastropub opens in Lakewood Ranch, with nearby Irish pub in the works</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/11/allswell-gastropub-opens-lakewood-ranch/85541957007/</link><description>Gastropub opens in Lakewood Ranch, with nearby Irish pub in the works</description></item></channel></rss>