<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Stretch your summer at Florida’s best spas and wellness escapes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/09/05/where-to-unwind-in-florida-10-spas-to-keep-summer-going-strong/85851862007/</link><description>Labor Day may mark the unofficial end of summer, but in Florida, the heat and the chance for indulgence between hurricanes linger long after the last backyard barbecue. For those not ready to trade flip-flops for fall, the state’s top spas and wellness spaces offer one more excuse to savor summer.</description></item><item><title>How much are tickets to Ariana Grande's shows? See prices, FL dates</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/09/ariana-grande-tour-tickets-presale-florida-concerts-dates-prices/86049369007/</link><description>Not only is Ariana Grande hitting the road again but she's making a few stops in her home state.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Braden River volleyball, Lakewood Ranch boys golf win</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/09/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-8-13-2025/85855502007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 8-13, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>Three-star QB Darryon Jones transfers to Venice from Chaminade-Madonna</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/08/venice-high-football-quarterback-darryon-jones-transfer-chaminade-madonna-howard-commit/86049526007/</link><description>VENICE — John Peacock spent the entire offseason deciding which player would start under center for the Venice High football team.</description></item><item><title>Epstein’s birthday letter released. Trump denies signing it</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/09/09/trump-epstein-birthday-letter-signature-enigma/86054275007/</link><description>The House Oversight Committeepublished the birthday note to Jeffrey Epsteinpurportedly written by PresidentDonald Trump.</description></item><item><title>The most calamitous date on Sarasota's calendar happens to be Sept. 10</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/08/if-its-a-disaster-chances-are-it-happened-in-sarasota-on-sept-10/85759741007/</link><description>September 11, of course, will forever be remembered as one of the worst dates ever. But September 10 hasn't been so swell either.</description></item><item><title>Bending the Arc seeks 25 students for Civil Rights…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/09/from-selma-to-sarasota-civil-rights-study-trip-returns-for-teens/85973512007/</link><description>A local program that sent 20 students from nine Sarasota-Bradenton area high schools to Alabama to walk in the footsteps of Civil Rights leaders is now seeking its next class of changemakers.</description></item><item><title>Allegiant to add Chattanooga route from Florida that…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/09/allegiant-florida-flights-fort-lauderdale-florida-chattanooga/86053834007/</link><description>Ultra-low-cost airline Allegiant Air on Sept. 9 announced three new routes and one destination, including a Florida route that struggling competitor Spirit Airlines isdropping next month.</description></item><item><title>New Aldi opening Sept. 11 with free swag, chance to win…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/09/aldi-grand-opening-aventura-south-florida/86046765007/</link><description>No-frills discount grocery chain Aldi is opening another location in South Florida Sept. 11, the latest in its massive Florida expansion this year.</description></item><item><title>Could Florida see snow again this winter? See…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/09/florida-winter-old-farmers-almanac-snow-fall-seasons/86038393007/</link><description>Fall might justbe starting now,but some Floridians might be thinking ahead to winter. Will it actually be cold?</description></item><item><title>Where does Florida rank in US for vaccination rates?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/09/florida-ranks-vaccination-rates/86054566007/</link><description>On Sept. 3, Florida made national news when the state surgeon general Dr. Joseph Lapado announced that he, Gov. Ron DeSantis and the Florida Legislature would be working toend all mandatory vaccine requirements, including immunizations for schoolsrequired by law.</description></item><item><title>15 local restaurants get high-priority violations, 7 ace inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/09/sarasota-restaurants-high-priority-violations-health-inspections/86039657007/</link><description>Ourdigital databaseof restaurant health inspections is updated regularly with the latest information on which Sarasota, Bradenton and Venice area restaurants passed or failed.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 10 Football Power Rankings after Week 3</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/09/top-10-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-team-rankings-after-week-3/85849681007/</link><description>The top has grown tighter after each week in the early stages of this high school football season. The top four wins all won in Week 3, and there was some shuffling among them.</description></item><item><title>MAGA needs a lecture on vaccines. Here's why we need them.</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/09/florida-vaccines-ladapo-rfk-conspiracy/86054255007/</link><description>If I were addressing a MAGA convention, here are some questions I would ask the audience:</description></item><item><title>Condo owner sues Bradenton Beach over hurricane damage assessments</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/09/condo-owner-sues-bradenton-beach-over-hurricane-damage-assessments/85779272007/</link><description>The city of Bradenton Beach and local condo owner Bob Bolus, Sr., are headed toward a legal showdown over the property owner's planned lawsuit that claims the city issuedbogus substantial damage assessments for homes affected by hurricanes Helene and Miltonto benefit islanddeveloper Shawn Kaleta.</description></item></channel></rss>