<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 12:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>National Hurricane Center keeping eye on Hurricane Erin, Invest 98L</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/15/hurricane-erin-invest-98l-depression-path-spaghetti-models-florida/85670166007/</link><description>The National Hurricane Center is tracking two systems in the Atlantic basin, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Florida prosecutors who helped Epstein must testify before U.S. HouseEditorial Board</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/editorials/2025/08/15/florida-prosecutors-epstein-trump-krischer-acosta/85616674007/</link><description>Florida prosecutors who helped Epstein must testify before U.S. HouseEditorial Board</description></item><item><title>Haters won't admit Trump's success and popularity</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/15/trump-immigrants-inflation-safety-fbi-doge-pelletier/85657736007/</link><description>The truth is thatPresident Donald Trumpis making life for ALL Americans better.</description></item><item><title>Greater Sarasota Chamber of Commerce hosts annual Leadership Awards</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/11/greater-sarasota-chamber-of-commerce-hosts-annual-leadership-awards/85404410007/</link><description>TheGreater Sarasota Chamber of Commercewill host the annual Celebrate Outstanding Leadership Awards on Aug. 13 from 11:30 a.m. to 1 p.m. at Michael’s On East in Sarasota.</description></item><item><title>The Big Beautiful Bill and its big opportunity for wealthy families</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/11/the-big-beautiful-bill-and-its-big-opportunity-for-wealthy-families/85402413007/</link><description>If you’ve ever felt like everything shifted overnight – tax laws, investment dynamics, retirement realities – you’re not imagining it. The Big Beautiful Bill, signed July 3, may seem like political theater, but for affluent families, it quietly reshapes how wealth is saved, transferred, and preserved.</description></item><item><title>See the winners of the Herald-Tribune's 2025 Sarasota-Manatee Top Workplaces</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/13/the-herald-tribunes-2025-sarasota-manatee-top-workplaces/85645985007/</link><description>How do you judge the quality of a workplace? Ask the experts: The employees.</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>11,000 gallons of sewage spill into Hatchett Creek in Venice</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/15/workers-treat-spill-of-11000-gallons-of-sewage-in-hatchett-creek/85683258007/</link><description>VENICE – About 11,000 gallons of untreated wastewater spilled in Hatchett Creek early Friday near the intersection of East Venice and Warfield avenues after failure of a contractor’s pumping equipment as part of a city sewer pipeline project.</description></item><item><title>Vote for best 2025 high school football team in Manatee…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/best-manatee-sarasota-area-2025-high-school-football-team-vote/85531382007/</link><description>High school football teams are getting ready to take the field for the first time in the 2025 season on Friday, Aug. 15.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/14/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-14-17/85580403007/</link><description>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug…</description></item><item><title>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/15/best-legendary-sarasota-restaurants-and-bars-to-visit-now/84509634007/</link><description>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now…</description></item><item><title>New College of Florida attracts top educatorsDavid Rohrbacher Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/16/new-college-educators-students/85675977007/</link><description>If you want to see the future of higher education, don’t look to theIvy League. Look to the shores of Sarasota Bay.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota’s performing arts center stalls as other major cultural projects race forward</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/16/sarasota-performing-arts-center-behind-other-projects-in-progress/85673126007/</link><description>Seven years ago, Sarasota unveiled an ambitious plan for its bayfront — a reimagined 53-acre waterfront park crowned by a state-of-the-art performing arts center to replace the agingVan Wezel, funded equally by private donations and public dollars.</description></item></channel></rss>