<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Players stages premiere of festival winning comedy</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/09/festival-winning-comedy-gets-premiere-at-sarasota-players/85458001007/</link><description>As a pastry chef, Hannah Mitchell could be providing any of the sweet treats that accompany the ceremonies that take place in the “Happy Endings Wedding Chapel,” which has its premiere Aug. 12 at the Sarasota Players.</description></item><item><title>10 essential hidden gem restaurants in Sarasota worth discovering</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/08/best-hidden-gem-restaurants-sarasota/83648784007/</link><description>10 essential hidden gem restaurants in Sarasota worth discovering</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>The Big 15: Herald-Tribune's top 2025 college football prospects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/06/top-sarasota-manatee-college-football-prospects-for-2025-high-school-season/84231653007/</link><description>The Big 15: Herald-Tribune's top 2025 college football prospects</description></item><item><title>Beyond the field: capturing the high school football's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/08/10/sarasotas-top-high-school-football-recruits-a-photojournalists-view-on-local-talent-and-evolving-new/85407367007/</link><description>The buzz around high school football never truly fades.</description></item><item><title>Invest 97L development chances increase. Here's the…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/10/national-hurricane-center-invest-96l-invest-97l-tropical-depression-erin/85590160007/</link><description>Two Atlantic weather systems with potential ofdeveloping into topical depressionsnext week are being watched by theNational Hurricane Centeron Aug. 10.</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: Travis Hunter, a 70-yard field goal…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/10/travis-hunter-a-70-yard-field-goal-and-tua-starts-for-dolphins-2md/83674673007/</link><description>The first week of NFL preseason games is in the books. Here's what happened with Florida's three NFL teams:</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for Aug. 10…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/10/florida-lottery-results-sunday-august-10-2025/85604573007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, Aug. 10, 2025</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota’s Rise Above stages musical ‘Matilda’ to kick off school year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/10/musical-version-of-roald-dahls-matilda-takes-stage-at-rise-above/85463754007/</link><description>Whenever he stages a show for Rise Above Performing Arts with many young characters, Artistic Director Jacob Ruscoe knows he will see a lot of people sign up for auditions, but even he was surprised by the “huge response” for his upcoming production of “Matilda: The Musical.”</description></item><item><title>Manatee County sets a date for long-awaited wetlands protection vote</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/10/manatee-county-sets-a-date-for-long-awaited-wetlands-protection-vote/85506904007/</link><description>Manatee County will challenge Florida policies that, for better or for worse,stop local municipalities from increasing development regulationsfor one year after a hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota climate center sticks to forecast for busy hurricane season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/10/climate-adaptation-center-holds-firm-on-2025-hurricane-forecast/85565294007/</link><description>Sarasota climate center sticks to forecast for busy hurricane season</description></item><item><title>Selby Gardens to seek city final approval for next improvements</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/10/selby-gardens-receives-key-approvals-for-conservatory-learning-center/85577410007/</link><description>Sarasota's Planning Board unanimously approved Marie Selby Botanical Gardens’ plans to expand and build a learning pavilion and conservatory at an Aug. 7 meeting.</description></item></channel></rss>