<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 08:05:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>A year later, hurricane damange lingers at Hermitage Artist Retreat</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/10/03/county-commission-dragging-feet-as-hermitage-repairs-sit-for-a-year/86167840007/</link><description>For nearly a year, the Hermitage Artist Retreat has waited on Sarasota County to make hurricane repairs at its Manasota Key campus.Hurricanes Helene and Miltonstruck last fall, leaving the nationally recognized nonprofit with damaged historic buildings and restricted programming. While Hermitage leaders say the work could be completed in weeks, county officials have indicated it may take until late 2026.</description></item><item><title>Did Trump say a shutdown falls on the president? Yes, before he ran</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/10/03/trump-2011-2013-blamed-president-shutdown/86472266007/</link><description>Old news clips are circulating on social media showing PresidentDonald Trumpsaying the fault of agovernment shutdownshould lie with the president.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man found incompetent after stabbing brother’s girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/10/03/bradenton-man-found-incompetent-after-stabbing-brothers-girlfriend/86480455007/</link><description>A Bradenton manaccused of stabbing his brother’s girlfriend multiple timesin mid-August has been found incompetent to proceed with his case, according to court records.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues Bradenton hospital after leg amputation over alleged delay</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/10/03/mom-sues-bradenton-hospital-after-leg-amputation-over-alleged-delay/86062040007/</link><description>When Hailey Van Dam woke up on July 2, 2024, she couldn’t have predicted that her life would forever be changed in less than 24 hours.</description></item><item><title>Pre-order the WSJ 2025 Wine Advent Calendar with free shipping today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wsj-2025-wine-advent-calendar/86501883007/</link><description>Thecountdown to Christmasjust got a lot more festive. TheWSJ Wine Advent Calendar is officially back for 2025and it is already flying off virtual shelves. With 24 mini bottles of wine, each window features a spirited glassful of something delicious, from silky reds to dry whites, refreshing rosés and even award-winning Prosecco for your holiday toasts.</description></item><item><title>Wavytalk’s viral hair tools are up to 40% off for October Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wavytalk-amazon-prime-day-deals/86506025007/</link><description>If your hair could use a seasonal refresh, now’s the time to make it shine.Wavytalk, the fast-growing hair tools brandranked #1 on TikTok Shop and an Amazon best-seller, is making waves ahead of October Prime Day with some unbelievable discounts.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>Herald-Tribune midseason football player and coach of…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/01/sarasota-manatee-midseason-high-school-football-player-coach-of-year-contenders/86373864007/</link><description>High school football in Sarasota and Manatee counties has been one of the best in recent memory this fall.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/10/03/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86312835007/</link><description>It's the first full week of October, a month that'll bringa stacked events calendarto the Sarasota area, including live music. The biggest show in town this week will be an annual Circus Arts Conservatory fundraiser and electronic dance music concert, once again headlined by an internationally renowned DJ.</description></item><item><title>IMG Academy downs feisty Venice squad, 27-14</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/04/img-academy-remains-undefeated-by-handing-venice-third-loss-of-year/86501287007/</link><description>VENICE — Another valiant effort against an elite program fell short for Venice, which lost its third game of the year in a 27-14 tilt to IMG Academy.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item><item><title>Week 7 sees Sarasota win a thriller, while Riverview, Southeast roll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/04/week-7-football-results-for-sarasota-and-manatee-high-school-football-teams/86371203007/</link><description>A roundup of Manatee and Sarasota county high school football games played Friday, Oct. 3, 2025.</description></item><item><title>When will Sarasota feel its first cold front?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/10/04/sarasota-weather-cold-front/86497295007/</link><description>Fall may have started on the calendar, butSarasota-Bradentonwon’t feel it for a while. The first cold front isn’t expected until mid-to-late October, and a real cool-down won't arrive until November.</description></item></channel></rss>