<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 04:16:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sarasota-based Dickinson &amp; Gibbons attorneys named Super Lawyers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/07/14/sarasota-based-dickinson-gibbons-attorneys-named-super-lawyers/84419498007/</link><description>Sarasota-basedDickinson &amp; Gibbonslaw partnersDeborah J. Blue,Gary H. Larsen, andJeffrey D. Peairswere recently named Super Lawyers andJesse R. Butlerwas designated a Florida Rising Star byThomson Reuters.</description></item><item><title>Fly away! Breeze adds 19 new routes, including several from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/02/06/breeze-airways-florida-airports-destinations-new-routes-cost/78251054007/</link><description>Sometimes you just need to get away. Even if where you are is where others head to when they want to get away.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>'Love Island: Beyond the Villa' debut: See cast, airing schedule</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/15/how-when-watch-love-island-beyond-the-villa-cast-new-episodes-kordell-serena-liv-rob/85189858007/</link><description>After a whopping 36-episode season, the“Love Island USA” season seven winners were crownedthis weekend.</description></item><item><title>Arch Manning responds to Steve Spurrier jab at SEC football media days</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/07/15/arch-manning-discusses-steve-spurrier-comments-preseason-hype/85201643007/</link><description>ATLANTA ― Texas football quarterback Arch Manning didn't seem aware of Steve Spurrier's quip aimed in his direction a few weeks ago.</description></item><item><title>Can Vols solve Swamp hex vs Florida football?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/07/15/tennessee-football-aims-to-break-long-losing-streak-at-the-swamp-vs-florida-football/85193714007/</link><description>ATLANTA ― The last time Tennessee beatFlorida footballin The Swamp, George W. Bush was president, and The Matrix Reloaded topped the box office.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Mega Millions, Cash4Life results for July 15, 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/15/florida-lottery-results-tuesday-july-15-2025/85227872007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Tuesday, July 15, 2025</description></item><item><title>Florida's attorney general: Airports should watch out…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/15/floridas-attorney-general-asks-airports-to-watch-out-for-chemtrails/85209875007/</link><description>Florida's attorney generalis asking airports in the state to watch out for signs of weather modification.</description></item><item><title>What is Operation Slow Down? What to know about Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/15/operation-slow-down-florida-new-speeding-laws/85204393007/</link><description>Florida drivers, check yourself. Speeding kills, and when it doesn't it can cause lifelong, debilitating medical conditions.</description></item><item><title>Miccosukee Tribe seeks to join lawsuit against Alligator…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/15/miccosukee-tribe-seeks-to-join-lawsuit-against-alligator-alcatraz/85210780007/</link><description>One of two federally-recognized tribes in Florida wants to join a lawsuit to stop Alligator Alcatraz from operating in the Everglades.</description></item><item><title>Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship baseball team?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/14/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-baseball-team-poll/84537090007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>We must support survivors in Florida. The Diddy verdict shows why.Stacey Efaw Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/15/diddy-sex-trafficking-survivors-florida/85108802007/</link><description>The recent verdict in the high-profiletrial of Sean “Diddy” Combshas sent shockwaves through both the survivor community and the broader public.</description></item><item><title>Rodent droppings temporarily close Sarasota restaurant: inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/15/rodent-droppings-close-sarasota-restaurant-inspections/85190537007/</link><description>Rodent droppings temporarily close Sarasota restaurant: inspections</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County's arts funding process smoother than last year's</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/15/affordable-housing-developers-receive-millions-in-storm-recovery-funds/85199588007/</link><description>Sarasota County's arts funding process smoother than last year's</description></item></channel></rss>