<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item><item><title>Manatee Schools honors LWR athletic trainer for life-saving actions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/10/05/vin-mannix-lwr-athletic-trainer-honored-for-life-saving-actions/85927540007/</link><description>The types of injuriesSydney Suppahas dealt with during nine years as Lakewood Ranch High’s athletic trainer aren’t surprising.</description></item><item><title>Hurricane center tracking Invest 95L, which may strengthen into Jerry</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/05/hurricane-florida-jerry-track-path/86535070007/</link><description>Though there aresystems brewing, all is quietin the tropics − for now.</description></item><item><title>Prime members can get a Bissell Little Green for under $100 this week</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/05/amazon-october-prime-sale-bissell-little-green-cleaner-deal/86087450007/</link><description>Pro-tip:Want the inside scoop on the best early holiday gifts?Tune in to our Amazon livestream on Sunday, October 5 at 4:00pm ETfor the best deals ahead of October Prime Day, popular presents to buy now and more.</description></item><item><title>Target debuts exclusive 'Stranger Things' collection for Season 5</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/05/target-exclusive-stranger-things-collection/86520227007/</link><description>Ready to return to Hawkins with Eleven, Hopper, Dustin, Mike, Nancy, Steve and the rest to the gang?</description></item><item><title>Build your home gym on a budget with my top 5 favorite deals</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/05/amazon-prime-sale-home-gym-fitness-deals/86484103007/</link><description>Having my own home gym was a major goal of mine, marked by how hard it was to cancel my last gym membership when we moved (seriously, why is that so hard?). I always thought it would be way too expensive to actually put a home gym together. But, somecarefully curated Amazon salesallowed me to buy all of my home gym essentials for less than a year's membership to any decent gym.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/10/03/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86312835007/</link><description>It's the first full week of October, a month that'll bringa stacked events calendarto the Sarasota area, including live music. The biggest show in town this week will be an annual Circus Arts Conservatory fundraiser and electronic dance music concert, once again headlined by an internationally renowned DJ.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item><item><title>Game Balls for Week 7 top Sarasota, Manatee high school football performers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/05/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-top-week-7-players/86370441007/</link><description>Week 7 of the Sarasota and Manatee high school football season featured shootouts, a heroic effort against one of the best teams in the country and one player setting a school record.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton homicide investigation leads to arrest of man, 69</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/10/05/bradenton-homicide-investigation-leads-to-arrest-of-man-69/86524777007/</link><description>Bradenton police have arrested a 69-year-old man on Oct. 2 in connection with thestabbing death of 44-year-old Thania Fuenmayor.</description></item><item><title>What does the Fed's rate cut mean for Florida's housing market?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/real-estate/2025/10/05/what-does-fed-rate-cut-mean-for-florida-housing-market/85813350007/</link><description>The Federal Reserve’s recent quarter-point rate cut, the first since last December, comes at a time when the central bank’s independence, something I feel strongly about, faces growing scrutiny and calls for action are louder than ever. While the Fed maintains its official mandate of taming inflation, concerns about economic resilience, highlighted by weaker-than-expected employment data, ultimately tipped the balance. Markets now widely expect the Fed to deliver as many as two additional cuts before year-end.</description></item></channel></rss>