<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:07:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Wendy’s launches 'Wednesday' Meal of Misfortune ahead of season 2</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/06/wendys-wednesday-meal-of-misfortune-florida-netflix/85538038007/</link><description>We might be months away from Halloween, but the eerie vibes are already here.</description></item><item><title>Jen Pawol umpired spring training game in West Palm Beach, set for MLB history</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/mlb/2025/08/06/mlb-first-female-umpire-jen-pawol-miami-marlins-atlanta-braves/85546620007/</link><description>Jen Pawol will become the first woman to umpire a Major League Baseball regular-season game when she works three games during the August 8-10 series between theMiami MarlinsandBravesat Atlanta's Truist Park.</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>The Big 15: Sarasota and Manatee's top 2025 college football prospects</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/06/top-sarasota-manatee-college-football-prospects-for-2025-high-school-season/84231653007/</link><description>The Big 15: Sarasota and Manatee's top 2025 college football prospects</description></item><item><title>Manatee County plans a new curfew for minors</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/08/06/manatee-plans-a-new-curfew-for-minors-despite-chairmans-opposition/85523626007/</link><description>Manatee County willimpose a new curfew on minorsmeant to keep kids safe during overnight hours, despite strong criticism of potential pitfalls from County Commission Chairman George Kruse.</description></item><item><title>Will ‘Superman' fly to streaming services in August…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/06/superman-hbo-max-release-date/85538670007/</link><description>Look up! James Gunns' latest superhero "Superman," starring David Corenswet as the iconic Man of Steel, Rachel Brosnahan as Lois Lane and Nicholas Hoult as Lex Luthor,took the American movie audienceby storm and has earned over half a billion dollars worldwide as of Aug. 6, according toBox Office Mojo.</description></item><item><title>Jacksonville man identified as Fort Stewart shooting…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/military/2025/08/06/fort-stewart-shooting-suspect-is-from-jacksonville-5-soldiers-wounded/85548758007/</link><description>The U.S. Army sergeant arrested afterfive soldiers were shot at Fort Stewartin South Georgia is from Jacksonville, according to officials.</description></item><item><title>Did $2 ticket win you $449 million? Check Wednesday, Aug…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/06/powerball-numbers-wednesday-august-florida-winner-rollover/85523162007/</link><description>Will a$2 Powerball ticket make you a multimillionaire? As they say in the lottery business, “it could happen to you.”</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/06/florida-lottery-results-wednesday-august-6-2025/85553293007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Wednesday, Aug. 6, 2025</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Best local bars? 11 unique spots worth a road trip in Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/06/best-bars-florida-2025/85420804007/</link><description>Thebest barsin Florida aren’t just for grabbing a drink — they’re for creating memories, and maybe a story you shouldn’t share at work on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Pregnant women shouldn't have disability parking access</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/06/pregnant-disabled-parking-florida-mothers/85538049007/</link><description>As a mother, grandmother, anthropologist, disabled senior and rational human being, I'm struggling to retrieve my chin from the floor having read therecent guest columnreferencing a successful bill by state Rep. Fiona McFarland allowing pregnant women to obtain disabled parking permits ("McFarland stands up for Florida's pregnant women," Aug. 4</description></item><item><title>Sarasota deputies arrest woman for arson, homicide after trailer fire</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/06/sarasota-deputies-arrest-woman-for-arson-homicide-after-trailer-fire/85526389007/</link><description>Sarasota County Sheriff’s Office deputieshave arrested a woman for homicide and first-degree arsonfollowing a Nokomis camper trailer fire that killed one person on August 5.</description></item><item><title>The Meadows Country Club submits summary of assets and liabilities</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/06/the-meadows-country-club-submits-bankruptcy-documents-to-court/85507990007/</link><description>The Meadows Country Club submits summary of assets and liabilities</description></item></channel></rss>