<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:04:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school football schedulesfootball</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school football seasonfootball</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week for Aug. 25-30Athlete of the Week</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/01/sarasota-herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-poll-for-aug-25-30/85851897007/</link><description>Each week the Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for theHerald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week pollsponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then votein the online pollto determine the Girls Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week for Aug. 25-30Athlete of the Week</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/01/sarasota-herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-poll-for-aug-25-30/85851674007/</link><description>Each week The Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for the Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then vote in the online poll to determine the Boys Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>'Dancing with the Stars' season 34: Florida-based influencer to joinentertainment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/02/who-dancing-with-the-stars-cast-alix-earle-mormon-wives-when-watch-premiere/85935245007/</link><description>Goodbye reality dating competitions, hello realitydancingcompetitions!</description></item><item><title>Florida will pay local sheriffs to buy vans to transport immigrantsstate</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/02/florida-oks-vans-for-local-sheriffs-to-transport-immigrants/85942168007/</link><description>After Florida law enforcement agencies voiced concerns over the ability to transport immigrants to and from detention facilities,the statehas agreed to buy them vans.</description></item><item><title>Gator hatchling season: What to do if an alligator is on your propertynews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/02/what-months-alligators-most-active-gator-nests-removal-pool-yard-florida/85883935007/</link><description>If you've lived in Florida for long enough, you likely know thatcoexisting with alligatorsis a part of life in the Sunshine State. As long as you keep your distance and never feed one if it crosses your path, you should be fine.</description></item><item><title>When may the Venice Municipal Fishing Pier be repaired?Venice</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/01/progress-on-venice-pier-repairs-may-conclude-at-end-of-september/85866152007/</link><description>VENICE – Repairs of hurricane damage to the Venice Municipal Fishing Pier continue,with contractor Tampa Bay Marine Inc.hoping to have the project complete by the end of September.</description></item><item><title>Gov. Killjoy strikes again with Florida sidewalk art banletters</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/01/desantis-art-sidewalks-ban-florida/85927651007/</link><description>I knowGov. Ron DeSantisdid not originate the term "whitewashing."</description></item><item><title>Sarasota-Manatee coalition helps with bank accounts as benefits go digitallocal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/02/sarasota-manatee-coalition-helps-bank-accounts-as-benefits-go-digital/85885129007/</link><description>Ahead of a looming deadline for when the U.S. government will stop issuing paper checks for Social Security and other federal benefits, local nonprofits and partnering financial institutions are mobilizing to help seniors, veterans, disabled residents and other populations expected to be hardest hit.</description></item><item><title>Anna Maria Island drowning victim was a 20-year-old caught in riptidelocal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/02/anna-maria-island-swimmer-identified-after-body-recovered-offshore/85938023007/</link><description>The Manatee County Sheriff’s Officehas identified a 20-year-old swimmerwho drowned off of Bean Point Beach on Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Man, 41, discovered dead in car on Skyway Bridge Pierlocal</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/02/41-year-old-man-found-dead-in-car-on-skyway-bridge-pier/85941405007/</link><description>Florida Highway Patrol troopers areinvestigating after a 41-year-old man was found dead inside his caron the Skyway Bridge Fishing Pier on Sept. 2.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Police: Weekend shooting leaves woman dead, man injured</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/02/spd-sarasota-shooting-leaves-woman-dead-man-injured/85941210007/</link><description>Sarasota Police officers havearrested a man in connection with a fatal shootingthat killed one person and seriously injured another over the Labor Day holiday weekend.</description></item><item><title>Former Sarasota pet groomer banned from animal work while on probation</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/09/02/woof-gang-pet-groomer-pleads-no-contest-in-sarasota-animal-abuse-case/85940447007/</link><description>The former owner of a Sarasota dog grooming business who was arrested in March 2024 for mistreating animals at her shop has pleaded no contest to five misdemeanor charges of animal cruelty and sentenced to five years of probation.</description></item><item><title>Businesses buy in to innovative workforce housing project in Bradenton</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/02/businesses-buy-in-to-unique-affordable-housing-project-in-bradenton/85820431007/</link><description>Charlie Balliette remembers the day about a year ago when he heard a proposal that he knew would help his employees.</description></item></channel></rss>