<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:04:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>11 Florida bars so charming you’ll want to make a weekend of it</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/13/best-florida-bars-2025/85627369007/</link><description>What’s thebest barin Florida? One so unforgettable you’ll plan a whole weekend trip just to experience it?</description></item><item><title>Is 'Superman' on any streaming service? Not yet, here's when</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/13/superman-digital-release-hbo-max-james-gunn-superheroes/85638622007/</link><description>Look, it's a bird! It's a plane! No, it's a box office hit!</description></item><item><title>Former Sarasota School District chief of police Enos to return to post</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/13/school-board-member-tim-enos-resigns-from-board-for-police-chief-post/85644183007/</link><description>Sarasota County School Board chair Tim Enos will resign from his District 5 seat later this month to return as Chief of Police for the Sarasota County Schools Police Department. His resignation takes effect Aug. 24.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota deputies fatally shoot armed man while serving warrant</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/13/sarasota-deputies-fatally-shoot-man-after-standoff-at-venice-home/85650396007/</link><description>The Sarasota County Sheriff’s Office isinvestigating a fatal deputy-involved shootingin Venice on Aug. 13.</description></item><item><title>The Fab 15: Who are the Sarasota, Manatee volleyball…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/12/sarasota-manatee-county-top-15-volleyball-players-to-watch-in-2025/85512979007/</link><description>The Fab 15: Who are the Sarasota, Manatee volleyball…</description></item><item><title>Did you win $526 million? Check Wednesday, Aug. 13…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/13/powerball-wednesday-august-florida-lottery-winner/85648272007/</link><description>Will a$2 Powerball ticket make you a multimillionaire? As they say in the lottery business, “it could happen to you.”</description></item><item><title>Watch St. Thomas Aquinas vs. Cardinal Mooney live on…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/how-to-watch-st-thomas-aquinas-vs-cardinal-mooney-florida-football-game-live-on-nfhs-network/85650623007/</link><description>St. Thomas Aquinas and Cardinal Mooney enter the season with state championship aspirations and will waste no time testing their mettle by kicking off preseason action against one another. The Cougars, who fell just short of their second state championship in as many years, will travel to a Raiders program looking to bring home their seventh-straight state championship.</description></item><item><title>What's the latest path, spaghetti models for Tropical…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/14/tropical-storm-hurricane-erin-spaghetti-models-tracker-path-florida-impact/85645497007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Erinis beginning to strengthen and is expected to become a hurricane by Friday afternoon and a major hurricane by Sunday morning, Aug. 17, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>FDOT to close Clark Rd./Honore Ave. intersection for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/13/clark-rd-honore-ave-intersection-to-see-overnight-detours-814/85642104007/</link><description>The Florida Department of Transportation will close the intersection of Clark Road and Honore Avenue from 7:30 p.m. Thursday, Aug. 14 until 6 a.m. the next morning.</description></item><item><title>See the winners of the Herald-Tribune's 2025 Sarasota-Manatee Top Workplaces</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/13/the-herald-tribunes-2025-sarasota-manatee-top-workplaces/85645985007/</link><description>How do you judge the quality of a workplace? Ask the experts: The employees.</description></item><item><title>Vote for best 2025 high school football team in Manatee, Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/best-manatee-sarasota-area-2025-high-school-football-team-vote/85531382007/</link><description>High school football teams are getting ready to take the field for the first time in the 2025 season on Friday, Aug. 15.</description></item><item><title>Florida coalition warns of steep costs if ACA tax credits end</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/14/florida-businesses-caution-gop-on-fallout-from-ending-aca-subsidies/85634555007/</link><description>Some 2.2 million Floridianscould lose health coverageif the Republican-controlled Congress fails toextend tax creditsthese working families receive before the end of the year – a loss business leaders call a potentially devastating impact on the state.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 14-17</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/14/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-14-17/85580403007/</link><description>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 14-17</description></item><item><title>'Nothing is for sale': Meadows negotiating with Benderson Development to run golf courses</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/14/mca-negotiating-long-term-lease-contract-with-benderson-development/85647977007/</link><description>'Nothing is for sale': Meadows negotiating with Benderson Development to run golf courses</description></item></channel></rss>