<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:04:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Newish Jewish Play Reading Series features three new works</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/07/19/audiences-get-to-sample-three-new-works-in-new-play-reading-series/84497535007/</link><description>Newish Jewish Play Reading Series features three new works</description></item><item><title>Florida football OL arrested on DUI, weapons charges</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/07/19/florida-football-ol-devon-manuel-arrested-on-dui-weapons-charges/85201672007/</link><description>Florida footballoffensive lineman Devon Manuel was arrested on July 18 on charges of misdemeanor DUI and felony weapons charges.</description></item><item><title>Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship baseball team?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/14/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-baseball-team-poll/84537090007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state volleyball championship teams</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/17/all-time-list-of-every-sarasota-manatee-fhsaa-volleyball-championship-team/84287388007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee's all-time state volleyball championship teams</description></item><item><title>"11 to Save" list includes Manatee County's historic…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/19/preservation-group-lists-saving-manatees-1887-church-as-priority/85270819007/</link><description>"11 to Save" list includes Manatee County's historic…</description></item><item><title>SpaceX rocket launch: Best places to watch the next…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/19/rocket-launch-today-florida-spacex-starlink-nasa-canaveral-kennedy-space-how-watch/85269740007/</link><description>A dinnertimerocket launch from Cape Canaveral, Florida, is slated to lift off on Monday evening.</description></item><item><title>NOAA watches Atlantic tropical disturbance. What to know…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/07/19/hurricane-center-outlook-today-disturbance-atlantic-florida/85280818007/</link><description>The National Hurricane Center is watching an area of disorganized weather in the Atlantic moving east to west, but the chances it will develop are low and conditions aren't favorable for the showers and thunderstorms to come together as as something stronger, forecasters say.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/19/florida-lottery-results-saturday-july-19-2025/85295900007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, July 19, 2025</description></item><item><title>Largest Florida state park has co-starred in film</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/hidden-gems/2025/07/20/fakahatchee-strand-floridas-largest-state-park/84008040007/</link><description>This story is part of our weeklyHidden Gems feature seriesas the USA TODAY Network – Florida takes readers around the state to highlight some of our most interesting attractions.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/07/18/top-5-concerts-this-week-sarasota-bradenton-port-charlotte-punta-gorda/84509023007/</link><description>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte counties</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/17/best-things-to-do-this-weekend-sarasota-bradenton/84636836007/</link><description>5 best things to do this weekend in Sarasota-Manatee</description></item><item><title>Comparing Alligator Alcatraz to concentration camps is offensive</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/07/17/alligator-alcatraz-florida-concentration-camp-holocaust-comparisons/85254703007/</link><description>The accusation by Rev. Leo F. Armbrust that“Alligator Alcatraz” is a concentration campmakes my blood boil.</description></item><item><title>What is the latest innovation at SMH for knee replacement surgery?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/20/smh-orthopedic-surgeons-use-hand-held-robots-for-knee-replacement/84545407007/</link><description>Sarasota Memorial Hospital is expanding its orthopedic surgery capabilitieswith the addition of 10 hand-held, wireless robots, which surgeons started using this week in select knee replacement cases.</description></item></channel></rss>