<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/22/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice/85630718007/</link><description>This week inSarasota area eventswill feature concerts by out-of-town acts touring, locally based musicians playing their hometown, and even one show combining both.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 21-24</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/21/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-21-24/85677582007/</link><description>Don’t let the summer heat keep you from enjoying all the fun in Sarasota and Bradenton, witheventsstarting today and running through the weekend.</description></item><item><title>Top Sarasota restaurant for Philly cheesesteaks closed — what’s next</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/22/sarasota-philly-cheesesteak-restaurant-gentiles-closes-johnny-longhots-opening-oct/85758265007/</link><description>One of thebest sandwich shops in Sarasotahasshuttered.</description></item><item><title>New CEO chosen to head Early Learning Coalition of Sarasota County</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/23/new-ceo-chosen-to-head-early-learning-coalition-of-sarasota-county/85774189007/</link><description>The Early Learning Coalition of Sarasota County has announced the hiring of a new chief executive officer who has deep ties in the world of early learning and nonprofits serving children.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Sarasota boys golf wins match against…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-august-18-23-2025/85715808007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Aug. 18-23, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>Trump vows to ban mail ballots; DeSantis defends Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/23/desantis-mail-votes-trump/85763387007/</link><description>President Donald Trump wants toeliminate voting by mailthroughout the country, but Gov. Ron DeSantis doesn’t think he means it, at least for Florida.</description></item><item><title>Manatee officials are no profiles in courage. But can you blame them?Martin Hyde Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/23/manatee-desantis-threats-developers-commission/85786136007/</link><description>Last year Manatee County voterselected three new county commissioners and reelected an anti-establishment incumbent,– each of whom ran on the simple platform of not being funded and influenced by land development interests.</description></item><item><title>High School Football Roundup: See which teams came out as winners in Week 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/23/high-school-football-week-1-roundup-cardinal-mooney-cruises-to-win-manatee-venice-fall/85565985007/</link><description>SARASOTA – The Cougars scored 35 points before the Friday Night Lights were even turned on for the regular-season opener, but they had no answer for Friday Night Lightning.</description></item><item><title>Developer again seeks to build homes on Bird Bay Village golf course</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/23/quest-to-develop-homes-on-golf-course-at-bird-bay-may-go-to-court/75138423007/</link><description>VENICE – The developerseeking to build homes on the Hawk’s Run Golf Course at Bird Bay Villagein south Sarasota County has formally notified Venice that he plans to sue the city, invoking a formal dispute mediation process.</description></item></channel></rss>