<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Music Festival director leaving after nine years</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/27/sarasota-music-festival-cut-to-two-weeks-for-2026-in-transition-period/85821633007/</link><description>After 61 years as one of the more prominent summer chamber music training programs, theSarasota Music Festivalis heading into transition period with some significant changes coming.</description></item><item><title>Who do you think is the most famous Floridian? Vote top 50 in our poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/27/famous-floridians-florida-vote-poll-actors-singers-politicians/85846670007/</link><description>Florida has a long history of attracting therich,talentedandfamous, while producing somelegends and iconsitself.</description></item><item><title>Who are the high school boys swimmers to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/swimming-diving/2025/08/28/top-high-school-boys-swimmers-in-sarasota-manatee-area-for-2025/85715433007/</link><description>After the Sarasota boys swim team claimed the 2023 FHSAA Class 4A State Championship crown, the Sailors slipped to fourth place as a team in 2024. Right behind the Riverview Rams in third place.</description></item><item><title>School Board picks local educator as new superintendent in district</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/27/manatee-graduate-chosen-as-superintendent-in-manatee-school-district/85846717007/</link><description>The School Board of Manatee County has selected Laurie Breslin as the district’s next superintendent following a 10-week search. Breslin is a Manatee Schools graduate and the mother of a current student. She is expected to step into the role in early September, pending contract approval.</description></item><item><title>Florida DOE now starting day with Pledge of Allegiance…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/28/desantis-backs-education-departments-patriotic-morning-broadcasts/85837451007/</link><description>Education Commissioner Anastasios "Stasi" Kamoutsas wants the 1,500 employees at the state Department of Education in Tallahassee to start their days just as Florida students do:</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 2 Sarasota, Manatee game…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/28/week-2-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85758026007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Aug. 29, 2025.Game times are 7:30 p.m. unless otherwise listed.</description></item><item><title>All Florida Costco locations closing for a day in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/28/costco-florida-closed-labor-day/85829030007/</link><description>If you need bulk hot dogs, drinks or a new BBQ for yourLabor Daycelebrations, you may want to hitCostcoearly.</description></item><item><title>Frontier Airlines adds 20 routes, 7 in Florida, as…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/28/frontier-airlines-new-flights-routes-fort-lauderdale-florida/85853851007/</link><description>As Florida-based Spirit Airlines struggles to recover from bankruptcy and a lost merger opportunity, Frontier Airlines is stepping up with 20 new routes.</description></item><item><title>Looking for Labor Day fun? 5 top events in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/28/best-things-to-do-sarasota-labor-day-weekend-2025/85779365007/</link><description>Looking forfun waysto spend the long Labor Day weekend? From the waters of Sarasota Bay to the streets of Englewood, the holiday brings a mix of family-friendly events and more adult-oriented entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Voters don't want Rose on School Board. Why won't Ron DeSantis listen?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/28/desantis-sarasota-county-conservative-melania/85851808007/</link><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis recently appointedKaren Rose to the Sarasota County School Boardafter she lostre-election in 2024 to Liz Barker.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota city commissioner advocated for project while paid by developer</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/investigations/2025/08/28/as-mayor-and-vice-mayor-battie-advocated-for-employers-development/75075871007/</link><description>During Kyle Battie's first years on the Sarasota City Commission, records show he was employed by a shell corporation owned by a local developer, while helping that developer gain access to city officials, a Herald-Tribune investigation has found.</description></item><item><title>‘They should be ashamed’: Sarasota artists speak out over sidewalk art removal, ban</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/28/sarasota-artists-activists-grieve-and-mobilize-after-sidewalk-art-ban/85864266007/</link><description>Beck Laynesobbed as she walked along the colored sidewalksoutside the Social Equity through Education (SEE) Alliance building, filled with artwork from artists like Layne, on August 27.</description></item></channel></rss>