<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:04:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Review: ‘Don’t Dress for Dinner’ closes FST summer with hearty laughs</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/12/review-1960s-french-farce-gets-laughs-in-new-fst-summer-production/85599407007/</link><description>Review: ‘Don’t Dress for Dinner’ closes FST summer with hearty laughs</description></item><item><title>VOTE: Who would you pick to be No. 1 on The Big 15 list for 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/11/vote-for-top-sarasota-herald-tribune-2025-big-15-high-school-football-recruit-poll/85540827007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune unveiled its The Big 15 list of the Sarasota-Manatee counties' top college football recruits entering the 2025 high school football season. To see the full listCLICK HERE</description></item><item><title>Sarasota city water customers will pay new convenience fee in October</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/12/sarasota-will-no-longer-absorb-convenience-fees-for-water-customers/85609318007/</link><description>The city of Sarasota announced on Aug. 11 that it will launch arevamped online payment systemfor its water utility customers.</description></item><item><title>School board member named new leader at Project Pride SRQ</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/nonprofits/2025/08/12/familiar-face-and-community-advocate-takes-helm-at-project-pride-srq/85613876007/</link><description>Sarasota County School Board member Tom Edwards is stepping into a new spotlight as the next executive director of Project Pride SRQ, a nonprofit that champions LGBTQ+ inclusion and celebrates diversity through high-profile events, community programs and year-round advocacy.</description></item><item><title>Florida's top immigration cops don't use body-worn…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/11/florida-immigration-officers-dont-use-body-worn-cameras-for-arrests/85358888007/</link><description>It took 12 minutes before a Florida Highway Patrol officer checked Griselda Vazquez-Duran for injuries after bashing the driver's window of her gray GMC with a baton.</description></item><item><title>Tropical Storm Erin expected to become hurricane. Here's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/12/tropical-storm-erin-hurricane-tracker-spaghetti-models-florida-impact/85612925007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Erinis expected to begin strengthening soon and is likely to become a hurricane in the next 48 hours, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Disturbance in Gulf could bring up to 6 inches of rain…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/12/national-hurricane-center-tropical-storm-erin-gulf-florida-impacts-tracker-spaghetti-models/85613465007/</link><description>TheNational Hurricane Centeris tracking three systems in the Atlantic basin, including a system in the Gulf andTropical Storm Erin.</description></item><item><title>When will the Taylor Swift episode of New Heights air…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/12/taylor-swift-travis-kelce-new-heights-new-album-podcast/85622387007/</link><description>The Swifties were right … another Taylor Swift album is coming!</description></item><item><title>Cardinal Mooney-Aquinas game voted best 2025 matchup to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/12/cardinal-mooney-st-thomas-aquinas-game-voted-best-football-matchup-in-2025/85557299007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Out of all the games, theHerald-Tribuneselected 14 marquee matchupsfor the 2025 football season, including a couple of preseason classics.</description></item><item><title>The Fab 15: Who are the Sarasota, Manatee volleyball players to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/12/sarasota-manatee-county-top-15-volleyball-players-to-watch-in-2025/85512979007/</link><description>The Fab 15: Who are the Sarasota, Manatee volleyball players to watch this season?</description></item><item><title>Focus on gun violence, not food dyes in Fruit Loops</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/12/guns-children-death-fruit-loops/85606551007/</link><description>Wow, soon we won't have to worry aboutkiller dyein our kids' Fruit Loops.</description></item><item><title>How has growth changed in North Port's Wellen Park?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/12/wellen-park-growth-continues-as-some-home-prices-soar-past-forecasts/85465503007/</link><description>How has growth changed in North Port's Wellen Park?</description></item><item><title>Rodent droppings found at Sarasota area restaurants, other inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/12/rodent-droppings-sarasota-bradenton-restaurants/85609968007/</link><description>Rodent droppings found at Sarasota area restaurants, other inspections</description></item></channel></rss>