<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Stretch your summer at Florida’s best spas and wellness escapes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/09/05/where-to-unwind-in-florida-10-spas-to-keep-summer-going-strong/85851862007/</link><description>Labor Day may mark the unofficial end of summer, but in Florida, the heat and the chance for indulgence between hurricanes linger long after the last backyard barbecue. For those not ready to trade flip-flops for fall, the state’s top spas and wellness spaces offer one more excuse to savor summer.</description></item><item><title>Who is 'The Golden Bachelor' in 2025? How to watch episode 2 tonight</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/10/01/who-got-roses-went-home-golden-bachelor-mel-owens-women-cast-how-watch-florida/86453203007/</link><description>It's Wednesday, time foranother set of rosesto be given out.</description></item><item><title>American Heritage No. 1 in Class 4A in Week 7 high school football poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/01/american-heritage-no-1-florida-high-school-poll-st-augustine-vero-beach-aquinas-armwood-chaminade/86430617007/</link><description>And it's American Heritage back on top in Class 4A. At least for this week.</description></item><item><title>Florida No. 1 in book bans for 3rd year, report says</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/10/01/florida-has-most-book-bans-in-us-free-speech-group-says/86420289007/</link><description>For a third year in a row, Florida was rated No. 1 in the nation forbook bans.</description></item><item><title>Did the government shut down? What to know about mail, parks, more</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/01/givernment-shutdown-last-night-florida-services-affected/86453243007/</link><description>The deadline came and went and President Donald Trump and congressional Democrats were unable to make a deal, blaming each other for the funding standoff. Thefederal government shut downat midnight, Oct. 1.</description></item><item><title>National parks to remain partially open in shutdown. What that means</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/01/national-parks-open-closed-government-shutdown/86455040007/</link><description>Thefederal government shut downafter midnight on Wednesday, Oct. 1, after President Donald Trump and congressional Democrats remained at a standoff over health care funding.</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/29/sarasota-herald-tribune-high-school-girls-athlete-of-week-poll-sept-22-27/86369995007/</link><description>Each week The Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for the Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then vote in the online poll to determine the Girls Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Yacht Club sailing director wins F18 North…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/local/2025/09/30/sarasota-yacht-club-sailing-director-wins-2025-formula-18-americas-championship/86218995007/</link><description>Dalton Tebo and John Casey spent four days sailing an 18-foot catamaran named El Cucuy around Newport, Rhode Island, at the end of August.</description></item><item><title>Trooper's Law: New Florida law punishes animal neglect…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/30/hurricane-milton-dog-trooper-sparks-new-law-in-florida/86438867007/</link><description>Anew Florida law, which takes effect Oct. 1, was inspired by the heartbreaking story of a dog that was tied up and abandoned along a Florida interstate during Hurricane Milton.</description></item><item><title>Class of 2027 recruiting watchlist: top juniors to know…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/01/florida-football-recruiting-2027-watchlist-top-juniors/86330004007/</link><description>The middle of the regular season is upon us, and it's usually a great time to stop and look around at where things stand in the current season.</description></item><item><title>Yom Kippur, the holiest Jewish holiday, starts Wednesday…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/01/yom-kippur-wednesday-what-how-observed/86442946007/</link><description>The holiest day of the year in Judaism begins on Wednesday, Oct. 1, just before sunset. It's calledYom Kippur, or the Day of Atonement, and it lasts about 26 hours or until nightfall on Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Out of all Sarasota legends, here's why I want to meet Stephen KingRoger Brown</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/09/30/stephen-king-charlie-kirk-x-apology-sarasota/86433348007/</link><description>Here’s a confession:</description></item><item><title>Holidays arrive in Sarasota with Publix limited-edition ice cream</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/30/publix-limited-edition-holiday-ice-creams-sarasota-flavors/86445885007/</link><description>It may still feel like summer in Sarasota, where highs can flirt with 90 even as the calendar says fall, butPublix has already turned its attention to the holiday season.</description></item><item><title>Herald-Tribune midseason football player and coach of the year lists, team rankings</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/01/sarasota-manatee-midseason-high-school-football-player-coach-of-year-contenders/86373864007/</link><description>High school football in Sarasota and Manatee counties has been one of the best in recent memory this fall.</description></item><item><title>New adventure park opens in Sarasota with family fun attractions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/10/01/sarasota-new-urban-air-adventure-park-family-fun-attractions/86445539007/</link><description>Another adventure park just opened its doors in Sarasota County for family fun, afterDo The Beach Adventure Parkopened in North Port earlier this month.</description></item></channel></rss>