<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:05:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 3: 8 items to get rid of for sure</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/30/marni-jameson-walking-the-rightsizing-walk-part-3-the-power-purge/85813421007/</link><description>I am so embarrassed. All these columns and books I have written on downsizing and decluttering and my oh my, the mess I am in. Moving is the ultimate truth test. As I pack up the house my husband, DC, and I have lived in for eight years, box towers line the halls, packed and stacked like big city skylines. Each room coughs up its contents like a kid with consumption. I fear I may never see a clear counter again.</description></item><item><title>Who won 'Bachelor in Paradise' finale? See who got the cash prize</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/03/bachelor-paradise-finale-winners-jess-spencer-engaged-kat-dale-alexe-andrew/85952123007/</link><description>For the first time ever, two couples took home a significant chunk of change on the“Bachelor in Paradise” season 10 finale, which aired on Tuesday, Sept. 2.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend: Sept. 4-7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/04/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-sept-4-7/85866691007/</link><description>September may be Sarasota’s slowest month forlocal events, but there are still plenty of reasons to get out — includingthe start of the 2025 NFL season.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week: ODA football player Brady Cleveland</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/04/herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-out-of-door-academy-football-player-brady-cleveland/85892560007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects boys athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week: Venice volleyball player Madi Robinson</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/04/herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-venice-volleyball-player-madi-robinson/85892973007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects girls athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 3 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/04/week-3-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85852367007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Sept. 5, 2025</description></item><item><title>Is Florida ending vaccine requirements? Here’s what we…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/florida-desantis-end-vaccine-mandate-requirements-who-joseph-ladapo/85969495007/</link><description>Florida is poised to become the first state to drop all vaccine requirements, including immunizations for schools.</description></item><item><title>When is Saturday Night Live coming back? See new…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/04/saturday-night-live-season-october-peacock-streaming-florida/85968843007/</link><description>Live from New York, it's almost time forSaturday Night Live!</description></item><item><title>Powerball jackpot for next drawing third largest ever…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/what-new-powerball-jackpot-florida-lottery-record/85972906007/</link><description>Nobody won the$1.4 billion Powerball jackpoton Sept. 3.</description></item><item><title>See spaghetti models for Invest 91L. What Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/09/04/invest-91l-spaghetti-models-tropcial-storm-gabrielle-florida-impacts-what-to-know/85976556007/</link><description>The National Hurricane Center designated a tropical wave in the eastern Atlantic as Invest 91L, Thursday afternoon, Sept. 4.</description></item><item><title>Frontier adds 22 more new routes, here are the Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/frontier-airlines-adds-more-routes-spirit-reduces-flights/85976278007/</link><description>Just as Florida-basedSpirit Airlines cancels routes to 11 citiesas it struggles with a second bankruptcy in a year, Frontier Airlines, Spirit's major competitor in the ultra-low-fare airline industry is surging forward with 22 new routes across the United States, the Caribbean and Latin America launching in late 2025, according toa Sept. 4 release.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man arrested for second-degree murder in death of girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/04/bradenton-man-arrested-for-second-degree-murder-in-death-of-girlfriend/85971535007/</link><description>Manatee County deputies arrested a 33-year-old on Sept. 3 for the second-degree murder of his girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>Community leaders have mixed emotions on SCS board appointment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/04/sarasota-school-board-seat-to-be-filled-by-rose-after-campaign-loss/85869351007/</link><description>Karen Rose’s return to the Sarasota County School Board — throughappointment by Gov. Ron DeSantisless than a year after she lost her seat in an election — is drawing mixed reactions from board members and education advocates who are weighing what her presence could mean for classrooms, families and district stability.</description></item><item><title>Battle on the right: Florida-based Newsmax takes Fox News to court</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/04/lawsuit-florida-based-newsmax-says-fox-news-froze-it-out-of-conservative-cable/85972120007/</link><description>Two of the largestright-wing TV outletsare battling their claims over being the nation's top right-leaning news source inMiami's federal court.</description></item><item><title>How may PGT's parent firm's plant closures affect Venice, Fort Myers?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/04/pgt-parent-company-plans-plant-closures-on-east-coast-of-florida/85957242007/</link><description>A “strategic realignment” of  Florida operations bythe parent company of PGT Innovationsmeans closure of window and door manufacturing plants in South Florida's Medley and Hialeah, with some of the work shifting to PGT facilities in Venice and Fort Myers.</description></item></channel></rss>