<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fly away! Breeze adds 19 new routes, including several from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/02/06/breeze-airways-florida-airports-destinations-new-routes-cost/78251054007/</link><description>Sometimes you just need to get away. Even if where you are is where others head to when they want to get away.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship volleyball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/21/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-volleyball-team-poll/85258207007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area volleyball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>1993 Sarasota High wins All-Time Best Baseball Team Poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/22/1993-sarasota-high-wins-all-time-best-baseball-team-poll/85312756007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune looked back at all the area Sarasota-Manatee baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Court allows July 31 execution in 1994 Florida murder case</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/07/22/florida-supreme-court-upholds-execution-in-1994-murder-case/85329966007/</link><description>TALLAHASSEE — The Florida Supreme Court on July 22 refused to halt the scheduled July 31 execution of Edward Zakrzewski, who was sentenced to death in the 1994 murders of his wife and two children in their Okaloosa County home.</description></item><item><title>When Travis Kelce (and Taylor Swift?) visits Florida for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/nfl/2025/07/22/kansas-city-chiefs-jaguars-schedule-travis-kelce-taylor-swift-florida/85303103007/</link><description>Football fans are loving the return of the NFL.</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' week 3: Here's who went home, who…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/22/what-happened-bachelor-in-paradise-last-night-who-got-roses-went-home-cast-list-goldens/85319901007/</link><description>"Bachelor in Paradise" season 10is heating up. Last night's new episode featured the first rose ceremony with the "Golden" contestants and the first time an intergenerational rose has ever been given out.</description></item><item><title>Florida sheriff deputies will soon be able to make…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/22/florida-sheriff-deputies-will-soon-be-able-to-make-immigration-arrests/85324750007/</link><description>Florida sheriffs' deputies will soon begin to detain undocumented immigrants, and officials say they will need more detention space to hold them all but they're still being blocked by the feds.</description></item><item><title>Increased rain chances for Sarasota and Bradenton in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/22/locally-heavy-rain-possible-this-week-for-sarasota-and-manatee/85323272007/</link><description>Increased rain chances for Sarasota and Bradenton in…</description></item><item><title>Trump doubles down on accusations against Obama amid…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/22/trump-arrest-obama-video-epstein-treason-tulsi-gabbard/85320358007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpis ramping up accusations that former PresidentBarack Obamawas involved in a 2016 conspiracy to undermine Trump's victory, which the former president's office called a “weak attempt at distraction.”</description></item><item><title>Checking in with Venice's top recruits as football season approaches</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/22/mizzou-fsu-pushing-for-edge-asharri-charles-other-venice-recruiting-updates-miami-commit-ucla/85244772007/</link><description>Checking in with Venice's top recruits as football season approaches</description></item><item><title>Roaches, insects found at Sarasota area restaurants: inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/22/roaches-flying-insects-found-at-sarasota-area-restaurants-inspections/85305865007/</link><description>Roaches, insects found at Sarasota area restaurants: inspections</description></item><item><title>North Port leaders decide big new police station would be too costly</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/07/23/north-port-commissioners-seek-to-downsize-proposed-police-station/85315422007/</link><description>The North Port City Commission puntedon plans to build a $122.7 million police station Tuesday, deciding to hold a future meeting to shrink a proposal for a space designed to fill the city’s needs until 2065.</description></item><item><title>Pop star Pink surprises Sarasota restaurant with performance</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/22/pop-star-pink-performs-at-sarasota-restaurant-amore/85321473007/</link><description>Pop star Pink surprises Sarasota restaurant with performance</description></item></channel></rss>