<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Who won 'Bachelor in Paradise' finale? See who got the cash prize</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/03/bachelor-paradise-finale-winners-jess-spencer-engaged-kat-dale-alexe-andrew/85952123007/</link><description>For the first time ever, two couples took home a significant chunk of change on the“Bachelor in Paradise” season 10 finale, which aired on Tuesday, Sept. 2.</description></item><item><title>When is Saturday Night Live coming back? See new comedian from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/04/saturday-night-live-season-october-peacock-streaming-florida/85968843007/</link><description>Live from New York, it's almost time forSaturday Night Live!</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend: Sept. 4-7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/09/04/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-sept-4-7/85866691007/</link><description>September may be Sarasota’s slowest month forlocal events, but there are still plenty of reasons to get out — includingthe start of the 2025 NFL season.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week: ODA football player Brady Cleveland</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/04/herald-tribune-boys-athlete-of-the-week-out-of-door-academy-football-player-brady-cleveland/85892560007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects boys athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>The Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week: Venice volleyball player Madi Robinson</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/04/herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-the-week-venice-volleyball-player-madi-robinson/85892973007/</link><description>Each week during the school year the Sarasota Herald-Tribune selects girls athletes that stood out the week before based on a combination of coach reports and school nominations sent to sports htincoming@gmail.com and our coverage. Those athletes are put in a poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. each Monday on heraldtribune.com and you, our readers, vote on who you think did it best.To get to know our winners better, the Herald-Tribune will have a question-and-answer session with each athlete weekly.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 3 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/04/week-3-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85852367007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Sept. 5, 2025</description></item><item><title>Can Florida lottery winners remain anonymous? See what…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/powerball-lottery-billion-jackpot-florida-winner-anonymous-law/85968818007/</link><description>No one has claimed thePowerball jackpot, as of Thursday, Sept. 4.</description></item><item><title>Will you be able to see total lunar eclipse in Florida…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/total-lunar-eclipse-september-blood-moon-where-visible-florida/85969003007/</link><description>A "blood moon" is coming this weekend.</description></item><item><title>Are we getting close to the peak of hurricane season…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/atlantic-hurricane-season-peak-florida-tropical-storm-kiko-lorena/85968838007/</link><description>While thePacific Ocean is dealing with two hurricanes, one barrelling toward Hawaii as a Category 4 storm, Floridians might be wondering if they will be the next ones to cope with a major hurricane.</description></item><item><title>3 Dem states ditch RFK's CDC with new vaccine alliance</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/california-oregon-washington-defy-rfk-west-coast-vaccine-alliance-florida/85969493007/</link><description>On the same day that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and state Surgeon General Joseph Ladapo announced they would beending the state's vaccine mandates, including school immunization requirements, three Democrat-led states announced theformation of the West Coast Health Allianceto provide recommendations on immunizations and ensure the public gets credible information on vaccine safety and efficacy.</description></item><item><title>Having problems getting to Powerball's website? What to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/04/is-powerball-website-down-what-to-know-florida-lottery-current-jackpot-next-drawing/85973819007/</link><description>Powerball feveris sweeping the United States.</description></item><item><title>Safe to swim? Palma Sola South advisory lifted after bacteria drop</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/04/no-swim-advisory-lifted-at-palma-sola-south-after-bacteria-levels-drop/85970988007/</link><description>The Florida Department of Health in Manatee Countylifted a water quality health advisoryfor Palma Dola South beach on Sept. 4.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton man arrested for second-degree murder in death of girlfriend</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/04/bradenton-man-arrested-for-second-degree-murder-in-death-of-girlfriend/85971535007/</link><description>Manatee County deputies arrested a 33-year-old on Sept. 3 for the second-degree murder of his girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>Community leaders have mixed emotions on SCS board appointment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/04/sarasota-school-board-seat-to-be-filled-by-rose-after-campaign-loss/85869351007/</link><description>Karen Rose’s return to the Sarasota County School Board — throughappointment by Gov. Ron DeSantisless than a year after she lost her seat in an election — is drawing mixed reactions from board members and education advocates who are weighing what her presence could mean for classrooms, families and district stability.</description></item><item><title>How may PGT's parent firm's plant closures affect Venice, Fort Myers?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/04/pgt-parent-company-plans-plant-closures-on-east-coast-of-florida/85957242007/</link><description>A “strategic realignment” of  Florida operations bythe parent company of PGT Innovationsmeans closure of window and door manufacturing plants in South Florida's Medley and Hialeah, with some of the work shifting to PGT facilities in Venice and Fort Myers.</description></item></channel></rss>