<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Beloved Sarasota dog bar is back with new owners and new food menu</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/14/sarasota-dog-bar-restaurant-to-reopen-with-new-owners-new-food-menu/84611228007/</link><description>Beloved Sarasota dog bar is back with new owners and new food menu</description></item><item><title>1995 Cardinal Mooney wins All-Time Best Softball Team Poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/14/1995-cardinal-mooney-wins-all-time-best-softball-team-poll/85191992007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune looked back at all the area Sarasota-Manatee fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>MLB Draft: Venice alum Marek Houston picked by Minnesota 16th overall</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/mlb/2025/07/13/mlb-draft-2025-minnesota-twins-draft-venice-alum-wake-forest-shortstop-marek-houston-16th/84541737007/</link><description>Marek Houston went right where he was projected to go by Baseball America.</description></item><item><title>Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship baseball team?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/baseball/2025/07/14/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-baseball-team-poll/84537090007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area baseball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>As anger mounts over Epstein's 'client list,' where's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/14/epsteins-client-list-ghislaine-maxwell-florida/85191013007/</link><description>One of the few people, maybe even the only person, who could confirm if there is or ever was a list ofJeffrey Epstein's clientsis imprisoned in a federal women's prison in Florida.</description></item><item><title>PSLF faces uncertain future: What student loan borrowers…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/14/will-trump-reverse-student-loan-forgiveness-pslf/84516280007/</link><description>If you benefit from student loan forgiveness in the U.S., you may have to start paying interest again soon. As the Trump Administration’s crackdown on the Department of Education continues, around 8 million borrowers will have to resume paying interest after a year of forgiveness.</description></item><item><title>Trump is a sports-loving president: Wins golf…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/14/trump-sports-golf-fifa-booed-ufc-mma/85194590007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpwent viral while celebrating on stage at theFIFA Club World Cup on July 13, the latest of several sporting events he has attended as president.</description></item><item><title>'Love Island USA' season 7 comes to a close: When the…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/14/who-won-love-island-usa-season-seven-nic-olandria-amaya-bryan-when-reunion-drops-peacock-how-watch/85189714007/</link><description>After a whopping 36-episode season, the“Love Island USA” season sevenwinners were crowned this weekend. Florida was represented in the finale episode byJacksonville’s Nic Vansteenberghe,who didn’t win the title of “America’s favorite couple,” but did place runner-up with his partner Olandria.</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' week 2 brings 2 episodes: How to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/14/when-golden-contestants-bachelor-in-paradise-how-when-where-watch-stream-cast-list-couples/85189834007/</link><description>As this year's chapter of"Love Island USA"closes, another major American reality dating competition show hosted on a foreign beach is just getting started.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis declines to comment on reported West Bank murder of Floridian</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/14/desantis-no-comment-on-floridian-allegedly-beaten-to-death-west-bank/85194989007/</link><description>DeSantis declines to comment on reported West Bank murder of Floridian</description></item><item><title>Sarasota attorney among 19 disciplined since 2020. Here's what to know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/07/14/sarasota-attorney-among-19-disciplined-since-2020-heres-what-to-know/84603835007/</link><description>Sarasota attorney among 19 disciplined since 2020. Here's what to know</description></item><item><title>Study to pin down why Palma Sola beach often has high bacteria levels</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/14/the-source-of-palma-sola-bacteria-woes-remains-a-mystery-in-manatee/84519699007/</link><description>Study to pin down why Palma Sola beach often has high bacteria levels</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee weather forecast this week: Keep that umbrella handy</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/severe/2025/07/14/storms-could-bring-4-to-6-inches-of-rain-to-sarasota-and-manatee/85192790007/</link><description>Sarasota and Manatee counties could see 4 to 6 inches of rain to start the workweek as a storm system pushes across most of Florida.</description></item></channel></rss>