<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Round 3 of 'Famous Floridians' poll is here. Pick top 10 celebrities</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/10/famous-floridians-vote-third-round-poll-draft-florida-celebrities/86076352007/</link><description>Florida has a long history of attracting therich,talentedandfamous, while producing somelegends and iconsitself. But which one is the most famous?</description></item><item><title>Iconic Sarasota restaurant open since 1987 closing for remodel</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/10/sarasota-restaurant-michaels-on-east-remodel-closure/86055608007/</link><description>One of Sarasota’s top fine-dining icons — renowned as a premier special-occasion destination and among thecity’s most romantic restaurants— will soon close for a major makeover ahead of its 40th anniversary.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota boys basketball selected for 52nd City of Palms Classic field</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/basketball/2025/09/10/sarasota-sailors-basketball-selected-to-52nd-city-of-palms-classic/86085252007/</link><description>FORT MYERS —When Donnie Wilkie decides which basketball teams he’s going to invite to the nationally renowned City of Palms Classic, he looks for three things.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 8 Volleyball Power Rankings after Week 3</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/09/10/top-8-sarasota-manatee-high-school-volleyball-team-rankings-after-week3/85855744007/</link><description>The cream is starting to rise to the top in local high school volleyball.</description></item><item><title>District weighs closing Wilkinson Elementary amid low enrollment</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/09/09/rebalancing-is-best-approach-sarasota-superintendent-lays-out-plan/86060740007/</link><description>The fate of Wilkinson Elementary School has become the flashpoint in a wider debate about how Sarasota County Schools will confront declining enrollment, aging facilities and state laws that make it easier for charter schools to claim unused district buildings.</description></item><item><title>The most troublesome pond at Piney Point will be closed soon</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/10/milestone-reached-in-closure-of-manatee-countys-piney-point/85851607007/</link><description>A troublesome pond at the former Piney Point fertilizer processing plant that has caused environmental disaster multiple times over the decades in Manatee County will soon be filled once and for all.</description></item><item><title>Longboat Key's Charlie Kirk killed in Utah. Who was the conservative firebrand?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/09/10/longboat-key-recharlie-kirk-shot-in-utah-who-is-the-longboat-key-resident-and-conservative-firebrand/86081660007/</link><description>MAGA starCharlie Kirkwasreportedly killed after being shotat an event at Utah Valley University in Orem, Utah.</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Braden River volleyball, Lakewood Ranch boys…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/09/09/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-sept-8-13-2025/85855502007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Sept. 8-13, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>Poll: Jolly ahead of Donalds but behind Renner in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/09/10/most-florida-voters-unfamiliar-with-jolly-donalds-renner-poll/86081173007/</link><description>A poll released Sept. 10 indicates whoever wants to be the next Florida governor needs to start introducing themselves to the electorate.</description></item><item><title>Florida reacts to shooting, murder of conservative…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/10/florida-leaders-react-after-shooting-death-of-charlie-kirk/86082254007/</link><description>Florida's statewide elected officials and others in politics reacted to the Sept. 10 shooting of conservative influencer and part-time Florida residentCharlie Kirkduring an event at a Utah university.</description></item><item><title>NASA's IMAP, free pass for KSC visitor complex and more…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/tech/science/space/2025/09/10/nasa-imap-ksc-free-pass-and-iss-resupply-space-beat/86082329007/</link><description>This week on Space Beat, host Rob Landers and space team reporter Brooke Edwards talk about NASA's upcoming IMAP mission to study the solar wind and the heliosphere around our solar system. Also, future explorers get a free pass to Kennedy Space Center Visitor Complex this month and ISS astronauts get ready for a fresh batch of supplies.</description></item><item><title>Did the Venice City Council vote to cut property taxes?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/11/for-the-second-time-in-three-years-venice-council-trims-millage-rate/85994558007/</link><description>VENICE – On a 5-2 vote, the Venice City Council approved a cut in the property tax rate for the 2025-26 fiscal year,when it adopted a rolled-back millage rate.</description></item><item><title>Authorites raise concern about Palma Sola Causeway businesses</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/09/11/holmes-beach-manatee-county-authorites-raise-concern-about-palma-sola-causeway-businesses-bradenton/86045950007/</link><description>Authorities are raising safety concerns about the growing number of businesses setting up and making sales onPalma Sola Causeway, and they are asking the City of Bradenton and Manatee County to bring order to thepopular recreation area.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Target hosting midnight Taylor Swift album release</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/09/11/sarasota-target-midnight-taylor-swift-album-release-travis-kelce/86082698007/</link><description>Global superstarTaylor Swift's 12th studio album is almost here. Are you ready for it?</description></item><item><title>What's being built in downtown Sarasota? See developments that are under way</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/11/new-condos-and-developments-being-built-in-downtown-sarasota/85994822007/</link><description>Downtown Sarasota is rapidly changing as multiple new multi-use developments shoot into the skyline and some Sarasota staples transform into new versions of themselves.</description></item></channel></rss>