<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>A year later, hurricane damange lingers at Hermitage Artist Retreat</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/10/03/county-commission-dragging-feet-as-hermitage-repairs-sit-for-a-year/86167840007/</link><description>For nearly a year, the Hermitage Artist Retreat has waited on Sarasota County to make hurricane repairs at its Manasota Key campus.Hurricanes Helene and Miltonstruck last fall, leaving the nationally recognized nonprofit with damaged historic buildings and restricted programming. While Hermitage leaders say the work could be completed in weeks, county officials have indicated it may take until late 2026.</description></item><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item><item><title>Fall back time change in 2025, see when daylight saving time ends</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/05/when-time-change-clocks-reset-fall-back-daylight-savings-dst-date/86494486007/</link><description>As fall rolls inandHalloween decorationsstart popping up in yards and stores, we are just under a month away from falling back and changing our clocks to get one more hour of sleep and less daylight.</description></item><item><title>Hurricane center tracking AL95, which may strengthen into storm Jerry</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/05/hurricane-florida-jerry-track-path/86535070007/</link><description>Though there aresystems brewing, all is quietin the tropics − for now.</description></item><item><title>Get this Halloween board game for under $20 at Target</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/04/the-haunting-at-wicker-ridge-board-game-target-circle-week-deal/86519630007/</link><description>As October rolls in and cooler temperatures begin to make their appearance, you might begin to spend a lot more time indoors. Instead of scrolling on your phone orbinge-watchinganotherseason of your feel-good show, why not switch off the screen and enjoy some competitive, spooky good fun with your friends and family?</description></item><item><title>Target debuts exclusive 'Stranger Things' collection for Season 5</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/05/target-exclusive-stranger-things-collection/86520227007/</link><description>Ready to return to Hawkins with Eleven, Hopper, Dustin, Mike, Nancy, Steve and the rest to the gang?</description></item><item><title>Amazon Big Deal Days are bringing major discounts for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/05/amazon-prime-membership-perks-cost-discounts-when-what-big-deal-days/86494442007/</link><description>If you haven't heard the news,Amazonhas officially announced the dates for its upcoming Prime Day in October (AKA:Prime Big Deal Days), and we're beyond ready to kick off the holiday shopping season with this epic sales event!</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/10/03/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86312835007/</link><description>It's the first full week of October, a month that'll bringa stacked events calendarto the Sarasota area, including live music. The biggest show in town this week will be an annual Circus Arts Conservatory fundraiser and electronic dance music concert, once again headlined by an internationally renowned DJ.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Could a moon of Saturn support life? Molecules in ocean…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/nation/2025/10/03/saturn-moon-enceladus-life-molecules/86458556007/</link><description>The evidence that an ocean-covered moonorbiting around Saturncould support life just got a little stronger.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item><item><title>Game Balls for Week 7 top Sarasota, Manatee high school football performers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/05/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-top-week-7-players/86370441007/</link><description>Week 7 of the Sarasota and Manatee high school football season featured shootouts, a heroic effort against one of the best teams in the country and one player setting a school record.</description></item><item><title>Bradenton homicide investigation leads to arrest of man, 69</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/10/05/bradenton-homicide-investigation-leads-to-arrest-of-man-69/86524777007/</link><description>Bradenton police have arrested a 69-year-old man on Oct. 2 in connection with thestabbing death of 44-year-old Thania Fuenmayor.</description></item><item><title>What does the Fed's rate cut mean for Florida's housing market?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/real-estate/2025/10/05/what-does-fed-rate-cut-mean-for-florida-housing-market/85813350007/</link><description>The Federal Reserve’s recent quarter-point rate cut, the first since last December, comes at a time when the central bank’s independence, something I feel strongly about, faces growing scrutiny and calls for action are louder than ever. While the Fed maintains its official mandate of taming inflation, concerns about economic resilience, highlighted by weaker-than-expected employment data, ultimately tipped the balance. Markets now widely expect the Fed to deliver as many as two additional cuts before year-end.</description></item></channel></rss>