<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 06:05:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive, Defensive Player of the Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason Newcomer, Coach of Year</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Powerball for Oct. 4, days after a Florida ticket wins $1 million</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/04/powerball-numbers-saturday-october-florida-lottery-winner-clalim/86524367007/</link><description>September was alucky month for lottery jackpots. What about October? Four weekends after the historic $1.8 billion Powerball,lottery fever is still spiking. And a Florida ticketholder this week had a secondary win.</description></item><item><title>Top 15 deals under $100 to shop before Amazon Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/04/amazon-october-prime-day-deals-under-100/86480350007/</link><description>Holiday sales are ramping up, but scoring a great deal doesn't mean you have to blow your budget. Amazon is packed with tons of deals under $100 ahead of thePrime Big Deal Days sale, which runs fromTuesday, October 7, to Wednesday, October 8. It's the perfect time tosnag giftsand everyday upgrades for less.</description></item><item><title>Pre-order the WSJ 2025 Wine Advent Calendar with free shipping today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wsj-2025-wine-advent-calendar/86501883007/</link><description>Thecountdown to Christmasjust got a lot more festive. TheWSJ Wine Advent Calendar is officially back for 2025and it is already flying off virtual shelves. With 24 mini bottles of wine, each window features a spirited glassful of something delicious, from silky reds to dry whites, refreshing rosés and even award-winning Prosecco for your holiday toasts.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/10/04/florida-lottery-results-saturday-october-4-2025/86532034007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, Oct. 4, 2025</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Here's the weekly 2025 Sarasota and Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/16/2025-weekly-high-school-football-schedules-scores-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306534007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Your guide to the 2025 Sarasota, Manatee high school…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-your-guide-to-the-2025-fhsaa-ssaa-season/85306859007/</link><description>From preseason practices through the state championship games, theHerald-Tribunewill be covering the high school football season every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>A Publix sold Oct. 3 Florida Lottery ticket worth $29…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/04/publix-florida-lottery-winner-weston-shell-baby-supermarket/86529518007/</link><description>Looks like a trip to the grocery storereallypaid off for a Publix shopper: A Florida Lottery ticket purchased there is worth almost $30,000.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Memorial Hospital makes Forbes’ list of Best Employers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/10/04/sarasota-memorial-hospital-forbes-list-best-employers/86366750007/</link><description>Sarasota Memorial Health Care Systemwas recognized in Forbes’ list of America’s Best Employers for Healthcare Professionals for 2025.</description></item><item><title>Our children attend Wilkinson Elementary. We will fight to save it.Wilkinson Elementary School parents Guest columnists</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/10/04/sarasota-wilkinson-school-choice-closing/86504416007/</link><description>We are parents of children atWilkinson Elementary, and we love our school.</description></item><item><title>When will Sarasota feel its first cold front?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/10/04/sarasota-weather-cold-front/86497295007/</link><description>Fall may have started on the calendar, butSarasota-Bradentonwon’t feel it for a while. The first cold front isn’t expected until mid-to-late October, and a real cool-down won't arrive until November.</description></item></channel></rss>