<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Submit Community News</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2021/05/24/how-submit-letters-editor-community-news-and-business-news-sarasota-herald-tribune/7417438002/</link><description>We have changed how community news is submitted. Please see below for details on how to submit Community News, Letters to the Editor and Business News.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County commissioner gave campaign surplus to husband's nonprofit</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/27/county-commissioner-gave-leftover-campaign-funds-to-husbands-group/85779858007/</link><description>After her election victory in 2024, Sarasota County Commissioner Teresa Mast donated the unspent remainder of her campaign funds — nearly $30,000 — to a nonprofit run by her husband from which the county had pulled funding earlier this year.</description></item><item><title>Will the city of Venice cut property taxes for the 2025-26 budget?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/27/city-of-venice-may-cut-properety-tax-rate-at-sept-9-budget-hearing/85832580007/</link><description>VENICE – The Venice City Council indicated a desire to adopt the reduce property tax rate to keep revenues flat when itapproves the 2025-26 fiscal year budget in September.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 8 Volleyball Power Poll after Week 1</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/08/27/top-10-sarasota-manatee-high-school-volleyball-2025-team-rankings-after-week-1/85746153007/</link><description>The top spot in local high school volleyball is up for grabs this year.</description></item><item><title>Big talk and tiny results: Corcoran's disastrous reign at New CollegeWilliam Rosenberg Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/27/new-college-spending-woke-athletes/85830702007/</link><description>In 2023New College of FloridaPresidentRichard Corcorandemanded a change to the school's mascot.</description></item><item><title>School Board picks local educator as new superintendent in district</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/27/manatee-graduate-chosen-as-superintendent-in-manatee-school-district/85846717007/</link><description>The School Board of Manatee County has selected Laurie Breslin as the district’s next superintendent following a 10-week search. Breslin is a Manatee Schools graduate and the mother of a current student. She is expected to step into the role in early September, pending contract approval.</description></item><item><title>What is cashless bail? Pres. Trump's executive order tackles cashless bail</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/08/27/what-is-cashless-bail-pres-trumps-executive-order-tackles-cashless-bail/85832068007/</link><description>President Donald Trump signed an executive order Monday, Aug. 25, to eliminate cashless bail citing public safety concerns and threatening to withhold state and federal funding to local and state governments that offer the bail option.</description></item><item><title>5 Sarasota restaurants opening, 2 closing — plus downtown fave moving</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/27/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing-downtown-fave-moving/85746714007/</link><description>From afine-dining favorite calling it quitsto adowntown sushi spot preparing for a big move, there’s been no shortage of restaurant news around Sarasota and Manatee counties this past month.</description></item></channel></rss>