<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 16:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Florida high school football: When does practice, season start?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/09/when-does-high-school-football-season-start-florida/84511860007/</link><description>Florida high school footballseason is right around the corner with summer break soon to give way to fall camp, practices and more preseason gridiron action.</description></item><item><title>Why Big Ten desperately wants to rig College Football Playoff</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2025/07/09/college-football-playoff-format-big-ten-plan/84493690007/</link><description>At leastBig Tencommissioner Tony Petitti dropped any pretense that his vision for the future format of theCollege Football Playoffwould be a boon for anyone other than his conference.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship softball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Save $200 on iRobot's Roomba 104 vacuum + mop combo for Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/limited-amazon-prime-deal-irobot-roomba-104-combo/84494073007/</link><description>If you're as curious as I've been about self-cleaning vacuum's, this sweetiRobot vacuumis sure to pique your interest, especially with a 44% Prime member-exclusive discount duringPrime Day this week.</description></item><item><title>This hair dryer never goes on sale: Save 30% on the BaBylissPro now</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/prime-day-2025-babylisspro-hair-dryer-deal/84517846007/</link><description>If you love going to the salon for a professional blowout but your budget does not always approve, I found a crazy rare Prime Day deal for you.</description></item><item><title>⌚️ Get $120 off the Apple Watch Series 10 for Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/apple-watch-series-10-amazon-prime-day-deal/84516405007/</link><description>The evolution of smartwatches has boomed in recent years as technology continues to advance every single day. Even with wearable tech fromSamsung, Google and many other top brands, people consistently gravitate towards the unwaveringApple Watch.</description></item><item><title>Will Florida avoid similar setup that lead to Chantal?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/07/09/national-hurricane-center-tropical-waves-saharan-dust-dexter/84506773007/</link><description>The tropics are quiet right now, with no activity expected over the next seven days, according to the National Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>What is Grok? Elon Musk’s AI service praises Hitler…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/grok-ai-elon-musk-xai-hitler-mechahitler-updates/84502468007/</link><description>Tesla billionaire Elon Musk vowed in June to retrain hisAI chatbot Grokafter getting frustrated with how it was answering user questions. When the artificial intelligence company xAI he co-founded released a new version of the AI chatbot over the weekend, Musk said it has been “improved significantly” and that users would“notice a difference”when they asked questions.</description></item><item><title>Delta flight diverted for burning personal battery. What…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/delta-1334-fire-lithium-ion-battery-tsa-ban-luggage/84516842007/</link><description>A Delta flight from Atlanta to Fort Lauderdale with nearly 200 people on board diverted tomake an emergency landing in Fort Myersafter officials said a personal battery caught on fire.</description></item><item><title>Nathan Benderson Park doesn't need massive, wasteful…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/08/benderson-park-rowing-sports-money/84505188007/</link><description>I have loved and supportedNathan Benderson Parksince before it held its first event more than 15 years ago.</description></item><item><title>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/08/josh-cramer-officially-replaces-controversial-melanie-bevan-as-chief/84507671007/</link><description>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police…</description></item><item><title>Miami man sentenced for stealing $94k in car parts, fatal hit-and-run</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/07/09/miami-man-sentenced-for-stealing-94k-in-car-parts-fatal-hit-and-run/84503568007/</link><description>Miami man sentenced for stealing $94k in car parts, fatal hit-and-run</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County moves $10 million for stormwater drainage improvements</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/09/sarasota-county-puts-more-money-for-phillippi-after-24-storm-flooding/84503514007/</link><description>Sarasota County has reallocated $10 million of stormwater funds to focus on Phillippi Creek drainage improvements, amid adelay of a major flood mitigation projectand a hurricane season well underway.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/09/sarasota-officers-rescue-driver-after-fiery-wreck/84513084007/</link><description>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</description></item><item><title>Report highlights fecal contamination issues at Palma Sola in Manatee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/09/report-highlights-unsafe-swimming-issues-at-palma-sola-in-manatee/84505511007/</link><description>Report highlights fecal contamination issues at Palma Sola in Manatee</description></item></channel></rss>