<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 22:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>A year later, hurricane damange lingers at Hermitage Artist Retreat</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/10/03/county-commission-dragging-feet-as-hermitage-repairs-sit-for-a-year/86167840007/</link><description>For nearly a year, the Hermitage Artist Retreat has waited on Sarasota County to make hurricane repairs at its Manasota Key campus.Hurricanes Helene and Miltonstruck last fall, leaving the nationally recognized nonprofit with damaged historic buildings and restricted programming. While Hermitage leaders say the work could be completed in weeks, county officials have indicated it may take until late 2026.</description></item><item><title>5 exciting Sarasota restaurant openings but a sad closing</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/10/03/sarasota-restaurants-opening-closing/86460008007/</link><description>While this time of year is typically the slowest in Sarasota, September brought plenty of exciting — and, yes, sad — dining developments, withopenings, a high-profile reopening, and a notableclosure.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee high school football scores: Live FHSAA, SSAA updates from Week 7</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/florida-football-scores-sarasota-manatee-area-updates-week-7/86371255007/</link><description>We are getting deeper into the high school football season as the calendar flips to October, the final month of the regular season. FHSAA Sarasota and Manatee county schools enter Week 7 play and some SSAA teams are getting ready to play their eighth game.</description></item><item><title>Hurricane center tracking 2 systems in Atlantic. Next storm is Jerry</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/04/hurricane-florida-jerry-track-path/86507470007/</link><description>(This story has been updated with new information.)</description></item><item><title>Watch the Cubs face the Brewers in the NLDS on Sling</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/04/how-to-watch-brewers-vs-cubs-mlb-playoffs-sling-live-stream-tbs/86477100007/</link><description>The Chicago Cubs are headed to the National League Division Series! The Cubbies sent the San Diego Padres packing with a dominant performance in the decisive Game 3 of the Wild Card Round. Now, they will face MLB's best, the Milwaukee Brewers. The entireNLDS will be available to watch on Sling.</description></item><item><title>Pre-order the WSJ 2025 Wine Advent Calendar with free shipping today</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/10/03/wsj-2025-wine-advent-calendar/86501883007/</link><description>Thecountdown to Christmasjust got a lot more festive. TheWSJ Wine Advent Calendar is officially back for 2025and it is already flying off virtual shelves. With 24 mini bottles of wine, each window features a spirited glassful of something delicious, from silky reds to dry whites, refreshing rosés and even award-winning Prosecco for your holiday toasts.</description></item><item><title>Powerball for Oct. 4, days after a Florida ticket wins…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/10/04/powerball-numbers-saturday-october-florida-lottery-winner-clalim/86524367007/</link><description>September was alucky month for lottery jackpots. What about October? Four weekends after the historic $1.8 billion Powerball,lottery fever is still spiking. And a Florida ticketholder this week had a secondary win.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's Football Midseason Offensive…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/02/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-offensive-defensive-player-of-the-year/86461354007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Offensive and Defensive Player of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Treasure hunters discover $1M in coins from 1715 Spanish…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/nation/2025/10/03/silver-gold-coins-spanish-shipwreck-florida-treasure-coast/86489430007/</link><description>SEBASTIAN, FL — More than 1,000 silver coins and five gold coins worth about $1 million were recovered from a1715 Spanish shipwreckoff the coast of Florida, a shipwreck salvage company said.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/10/03/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton/86312835007/</link><description>It's the first full week of October, a month that'll bringa stacked events calendarto the Sarasota area, including live music. The biggest show in town this week will be an annual Circus Arts Conservatory fundraiser and electronic dance music concert, once again headlined by an internationally renowned DJ.</description></item><item><title>Vote for Herald-Tribune's 2025 Football Midseason…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/03/vote-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-midseason-newcomer-coach-of-year/86476559007/</link><description>We have reached the halfway point of the Sarasota-Manatee high school football season. As we head into the second half of the season, we made our picks for thefront runners for Newcomer and Coach of the Year.</description></item><item><title>IMG Academy downs feisty Venice squad, 27-14</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/10/04/img-academy-remains-undefeated-by-handing-venice-third-loss-of-year/86501287007/</link><description>VENICE — Another valiant effort against an elite program fell short for Venice, which lost its third game of the year in a 27-14 tilt to IMG Academy.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Memorial Hospital makes Forbes’ list of Best Employers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/10/04/sarasota-memorial-hospital-forbes-list-best-employers/86366750007/</link><description>Sarasota Memorial Health Care Systemwas recognized in Forbes’ list of America’s Best Employers for Healthcare Professionals for 2025.</description></item><item><title>Our children attend Wilkinson Elementary. We will fight to save it.Wilkinson Elementary School parents Guest columnists</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/10/04/sarasota-wilkinson-school-choice-closing/86504416007/</link><description>We are parents of children atWilkinson Elementary, and we love our school.</description></item><item><title>When will Sarasota feel its first cold front?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/10/04/sarasota-weather-cold-front/86497295007/</link><description>Fall may have started on the calendar, butSarasota-Bradentonwon’t feel it for a while. The first cold front isn’t expected until mid-to-late October, and a real cool-down won't arrive until November.</description></item></channel></rss>