<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Freedom Boat Club launches new mobile app as part of digital upgrade</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/07/21/freedom-boat-club-launches-new-mobile-app-as-part-of-digital-upgrade/85257708007/</link><description>VENICE — The Freedom Boat Club, the world’s largest boat club and a Brunswick Corporation brand, recently announced the launch of its new mobile app, redefining how members interact with the club from reservation to water.</description></item><item><title>Fly away! Breeze adds 19 new routes, including several from Florida</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/travel/2025/02/06/breeze-airways-florida-airports-destinations-new-routes-cost/78251054007/</link><description>Sometimes you just need to get away. Even if where you are is where others head to when they want to get away.</description></item><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Ozzy Osbourne: Where to stream his MTV reality show for free</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/23/stream-osbournes-free-amazon-prime-how-when-watch-ozzy/85335302007/</link><description>Heavy metal legendOzzy Osbourne diedat 76 years old yesterday, about five years after publicly announcing a Parkinson’s disease and emphysema diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Cook Out is coming to Florida. Here's where new locations are opening</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/23/cook-out-restaurants-florida-locations/85335201007/</link><description>Florida is finally, officially invited to join a 10-state cookout.Cook Out, probably the only fast food restaurant where you can order a quesadilla as a side to your cheeseburger, is expanding to the Sunshine State after 36 years of service andmore than 350 locationsthroughout the southeast.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship volleyball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/21/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-volleyball-team-poll/85258207007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area volleyball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>When is National Chicken Finger Day? Where to find deals…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/24/national-chicken-finger-day-raising-canes-florida-spots-deals/85335098007/</link><description>A food item so good, even the most picky of children love it.</description></item><item><title>Is your electric bill high? These tips could save you…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/07/24/electric-bill-florida-save-money-stay-cool/85319854007/</link><description>Summer is here with a vengeance. Florida is just now coming out from under a heat dome that saw broiling heat and high heat index values across the state, butAugust is traditionally the hottest monthfor the Sunshine State so there's more hot weather coming.</description></item><item><title>Religious opt-out for Florida school vaccinations hurts…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/2025/07/24/florida-anti-vaccine-parents-school-kids-measles/85325487007/</link><description>Religious opt-out for Florida school vaccinations hurts…</description></item><item><title>St. Armands residents want quicker access back home after hurricanes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/24/survey-shows-support-on-st-armands-for-city-to-manage-stormwater/85321419007/</link><description>St. Armands residents want quicker access back home after hurricanes</description></item><item><title>Sarasota, Manatee real estate market still favoring buyers</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/24/report-sarasota-manatee-real-estate-prices-sales-continue-decline/85347443007/</link><description>The Sarasota-Bradenton area'sreal estate market continued its slowdownin June, according to themost recent industry report.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/24/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-july-24-27/85272193007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</description></item><item><title>Manatee County utilities crew unearths giant ground sloth fossil</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/24/manatee-county-utilities-crew-finds-giant-ground-sloth-claw-in-trench/85338162007/</link><description>Manatee County utilities crew unearths giant ground sloth fossil</description></item></channel></rss>