<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:04:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Open kitchen shelves may look great, Marni says, but are they for you?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/04/19/marni-jameson-open-kitchen-shelves-look-great-but-are-they-for-you/83021785007/</link><description>I know it’s tempting. You see those clean, uncluttered open shelves in kitchens, with their matching ceramic dishes, beautifully staged glassware, lots of negative space, and you think, “Why not? If my kitchen had open shelving, my belongings would look great, too! Plus, everything would be so easy to reach.”</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/07/24/best-things-to-do-in-sarasota-this-weekend-july-24-27/85272193007/</link><description>5 best things to do in Sarasota this weekend (July 24-27)</description></item><item><title>Florida basketball PG undergoes hernia surgery before end of summer workouts</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/basketball/2025/07/24/florida-basketball-pg-boogie-fland-undergoes-sports-hernia-surgery/85367303007/</link><description>Florida basketballcoach Todd Golden said incoming transfer point guard Boogie Fland underwent sports hernia surgery on July 3 and sat out the second half of summer workouts.</description></item><item><title>VOTE for Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship volleyball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/volleyball/2025/07/21/sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-volleyball-team-poll/85258207007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area volleyball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee all-time state football championship teams</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/24/looking-back-manatee-sarasota-all-time-football-championship-teams/84181976007/</link><description>Looking back at Sarasota, Manatee all-time state football championship teams</description></item><item><title>National Hurricane Center now tracking 4 waves in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/2025/07/25/national-hurricane-center-rain-storms-gulf/85363213007/</link><description>The low-pressure system bringing rain and thunderstorms across Florida the last few days is expected to move out of the Gulf inland over southeastern Texas or western Louisiana going into the weekend, ending any chances for further development, according to theNational Hurricane Center's July 25 update.</description></item><item><title>What to know about Ben Crump. 'The Attorney General of…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/crime/2025/07/25/ben-crump-civil-rights-attorney-william-mcneil-why-famous/85335083007/</link><description>Ben Crump, widely known as “The Attorney General of BlackAmerica,”is a high-profile civil rights attorney recognized for representing families in some of the nation’s most prominent cases involving police brutality and racial injustice.</description></item><item><title>Trump endorses Florida senator Joe Gruters for RNC Chair…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/25/trump-rnc-chair-joe-gruters-republican-national-committee/85369862007/</link><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis may havesnubbed state Sen. Joe Grutersfor the Florida CFO spot, picking staunch allySen. Blaise Ingogliainstead, but Gruters may have a new job to step into. On July 24, President Donald Trump endorsed him to be the new Republican National Committee chair.</description></item><item><title>Where can I watch Marvel 'Thunderbolts*'? See predicted…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/25/thunderbolts-rent-purchase-disney-plus-streaming-marvel/85370072007/</link><description>Marvel's favorite antiheroes are headed to yourtelevision screens.</description></item><item><title>New Florida cases of 'flesh-eating' bacteria reported…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/25/vibrio-vulnificus-new-cases-florida-update-flesh-eating-bacteria/85260984007/</link><description>New Florida cases of 'flesh-eating' bacteria reported…</description></item><item><title>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announces DOGE audit for Manatee County</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/24/florida-gov-ron-desantis-announces-doge-audit-for-manatee-county/85361775007/</link><description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announces DOGE audit for Manatee County</description></item><item><title>Trump wants Sarasota politician to run Republican National Committee</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/25/trump-backs-sarasotas-gruters-as-rnc-chair-amid-florida-cfo-race/85370742007/</link><description>Trump wants Sarasota politician to run Republican National Committee</description></item><item><title>Video: Heckler calls Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis a "nazi"</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/state/2025/07/25/video-heckler-calls-florida-gov-ron-desantis-a-nazi-during-remarks-about-hulk-hogan-death/85371873007/</link><description>Florida Gov.Ron DeSantis put Manatee County front and centeron Thursday, July 24, inhis effort to impose DOGE-styled, state scrutiny and potentially mandated budget cuts on local governments across the state.</description></item><item><title>Best Florida restaurants? 16 wacky spots locals love — and totally worth the road trip</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/25/best-florida-restaurants-unique-spots-worth-road-trip/84505274007/</link><description>Forget the chainsduring your next road trip. Florida is home tosome of the finest restaurants in the country— and also some of the funkiest, funniest, and flat-out most unforgettable.</description></item></channel></rss>