<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sarasota must put limits on downtown parties, special eventsDavid Lough Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/18/downtown-sarasota-parties-events-noise/85706697007/</link><description>The city of Sarasota is developing a new special event ordinance – a local law that regulates public events such as festivals, celebrations and block parties held on city streets, sidewalks and other public areas (including parks).</description></item><item><title>Roth shock: How a hasty conversion can cost Florida retirees thousands</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/business/2025/08/18/evan-guido-plan-carefully-before-making-plunge-with-a-roth-conversion/85511893007/</link><description>Imagine you’re retired in Florida, relying on Social Security and a modest nest egg. You read about Roth conversions – moving taxable IRA funds into a tax-free Roth – and think, “Smart idea.” But that move could end up costing you more in taxes and Medicare premiums than you’d expect. Those so-called “senior benefits” from the IRS barely make a dent.</description></item><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>When do Starbucks, Dunkin’ Donuts fall menus come out? Rumored dates</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/19/starbucks-dunkin-donuts-fall-menus-release-dates-items/85718766007/</link><description>While it might be another few months until we actually feel the fall weather, it's less than a week until we starttastingit.</description></item><item><title>2025 Class 6A-11 Football Previews: Lakewood Ranch, Palmetto, Parrish Community</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/19/2025-class-6a-11-high-school-football-team-previews-lakewood-ranch-palmetto-parrish-community/85545321007/</link><description>The Sarasota Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in FHSAA District 6A-11.</description></item><item><title>New women's clothing store opens at UTC</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/19/the-mall-at-utc-announces-new-opening-of-garage-fashion-store/85712821007/</link><description>New women's clothing store opens at UTC</description></item><item><title>HS ROUNDUP: Mustangs golf teams finish high in John Ryan…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/2025/08/18/sarasota-manatee-high-school-sports-roundup-for-week-of-august-18-23-2025/85715808007/</link><description>A roundup of high school sports contests played the week of Aug. 18-23, 2025, in Manatee and Sarasota counties.</description></item><item><title>What's the latest path, spaghetti models for Hurricane…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/19/hurricane-erin-spaghetti-models-tracker-path-updates-florida-impacts-rip-currents/85715325007/</link><description>Hurricane Erinweakened overnight but remains a major hurricane, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Here's a quick look on what you should know about…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/19/hurricane-erin-projected-path-florida-impact-answers/85715369007/</link><description>Tight on time? This story is for you. It's an abbreviated, text view of what's happening with Hurricane Erin. Click here formore detailsand to see thelatest spaghetti models.</description></item><item><title>How to attend public meetings amid proposal to raise fire assessment fees</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/19/sarasota-county-eyes-third-straight-increase-of-fire-assessment-fees/85663133007/</link><description>How to attend public meetings amid proposal to raise fire assessment fees</description></item><item><title>50+ things to do in September in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/19/best-things-to-do-in-september-sarasota-bradenton-venice-punta-gorda/85615156007/</link><description>50+ things to do in September in Sarasota, Manatee, Charlotte</description></item><item><title>Prospective Sarasota County lobbyist is major GOP fundraiser</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/18/new-college-presidents-brother-seeks-top-sarasota-county-contract/85645487007/</link><description>Prospective Sarasota County lobbyist is major GOP fundraiser</description></item><item><title>28 Sarasota area restaurants get high-priority violations; 8 ace inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/19/sarasota-restaurants-health-inspections-violations/85709049007/</link><description>28 Sarasota area restaurants get high-priority violations; 8 ace inspections</description></item></channel></rss>