<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/22/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-venice/85630718007/</link><description>This week inSarasota area eventswill feature concerts by out-of-town acts touring, locally based musicians playing their hometown, and even one show combining both.</description></item><item><title>Top Sarasota restaurant for Philly cheesesteaks closed — what’s next</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/22/sarasota-philly-cheesesteak-restaurant-gentiles-closes-johnny-longhots-opening-oct/85758265007/</link><description>One of thebest sandwich shops in Sarasotahasshuttered.</description></item><item><title>Two-Minute Drill: Find out what happened between Jaguars and Dolphins</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/2025/08/24/jaguars-play-dolphins-in-south-florida-college-football-is-back-2md/83674675007/</link><description>The NFL preseason is over. Next stop: Week 1 after Labor Day. Here's what happened on the final weekend forFlorida's NFL teams.</description></item><item><title>Shotgun or under center? Breakdown of 15 college football teams in 2024</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/football/2025/08/25/shotgun-or-under-center-breakdown-of-15-college-football-team-goal-line-situations-2024-season/85541374007/</link><description>To shotgun, or not to shotgun on the opponent's goal line? In college football, "not to" is the right answer. Yet many offensive coordinators prefer remaining in the shotgun just a yard away from paydirt despite a higher success rate with quarterbacks under center.</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Cash4Life, Fantasy 5 results for Aug. 24, 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/24/florida-lottery-results-sunday-august-24-2025/85811673007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Sunday, Aug. 24, 2025</description></item><item><title>Florida Lottery Powerball, Lotto, Cash4Life results for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/23/florida-lottery-results-saturday-august-23-2025/85804086007/</link><description>TheFlorida Lotteryoffers several draw games for those hoping to win one of the available jackpots. Here’s a look at the winning numbers for games played on Saturday, Aug. 23, 2025</description></item><item><title>New Trader Joe's planned for Sarasota, sparks community…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/2025/08/24/new-trader-joes-proposed-for-sarasota-how-a-second-location-could-solve-parking-nightmares-and-revit/85577632007/</link><description>Sunday morning in Sarasota often means a leisurely coffee, a stroll along the beach, and, for many, a trip to the grocery store. But not just any grocery store. For a certain segment of our community, a trip to Trader Joe’s is a pilgrimage. It’s an adventure marked by unique finds, friendly staff, and, often, a heroic effort to find a parking space.</description></item><item><title>Where is Tropical Storm Fernand? NHC tracks AL99. Next…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/24/fernand-hurricane-florida-track-path/85806187007/</link><description>Fernand has formed− what else is out in the Atlantic?</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>The Patterson Foundation donates $500,000 to hurricane recovery fund</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/24/patterson-foundation-donates-500000-to-sarasota-hurricane-recovery/85774649007/</link><description>As area residents prepare for the heart of hurricane season, The Patterson Foundation is also getting ready by once again seeding theSuncoast Disaster Recovery Fundwith a $500,000 contribution.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota must act now on Van Wezel's future</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/08/22/van-wezel-sarasota-maga-canada-trump/85777984007/</link><description>Just as it is unreasonable for the Sarasota City Commission totake over a year choosing a new city manager, it is also unreasonable to take more than two years todecide the fate of the Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall.</description></item><item><title>Hermitage wants to buy beach site from Sarasota County as repairs lag</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/24/hermitage-seeks-to-buy-campus-have-more-control-of-hurricane-recovery/85669242007/</link><description>(This story was updated to correct a typographical error).</description></item><item><title>Van Wezel blends comedy, music, Broadway and legends for new season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/arts/2025/08/24/van-wezel-season-celebrates-musical-legends-on-stage/85574102007/</link><description>With three Broadway musicals celebrating the careers of pop music stars, a handful of living musical legends and tributes to other classic rock acts, the Van Wezel Performing Arts Hall’s 2025-26 season may resemble a nostalgic survey of changing musical styles over the last 60 years.</description></item></channel></rss>