<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:19:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>7 area restaurants ace inspections, 2 get high-priority violations</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/08/sarasota-restaurants-health-inspections-high-priority-violations/84491492007/</link><description>7 area restaurants ace inspections, 2 get high-priority violations</description></item><item><title>Create your own team in College Football 26 using the Team Builder</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/college/2025/07/08/college-football-26-team-builder-how-to-use/84504973007/</link><description>College Football 26 is back, and so too is the popular feature,Team Builder, with plenty of updates.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Woods, Miles Russell earn Junior Players Championship invitations</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/golf/pga-tour/2025/07/08/charlie-woods-miles-russell-junior-players-championship-tpc-sawgrass-pga-tour/84510438007/</link><description>Miles Russell, a Jacksonville Beach resident and the American Junior Golf Association’s top-ranked player, andCharlie Woodshave officially earned invitations to theJunior Players ChampionshipAug. 28-31 at the Players Stadium Course at TPC Sawgrass.</description></item><item><title>Editor-approved deal: Get 48% off the viral Cosrx Snail Mucin</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/amazon-prime-day-2025-sale-cosrx-deals/84507555007/</link><description>As a shopping editor, I've covered alotof Amazon sales in my lifetime—big spring sales, Black Friday sales and yes, even the sale-to-end-all-sales: Prime Day. With years of extensive deal-hunting experience, I'm rarely surprised by any Amazon discounts, no matter how steep they may be—that is until today, when I saw that select Cosrx skincare products are up to52% offatPrime Day 2025.</description></item><item><title>Finally! The Shark StainStriker is under $100 for Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/amazon-prime-day-deal-shark-stainstriker-upholstery-cleaner/84511059007/</link><description>Prime Day is here! There were a few items in particular that I was tracking ahead of the sale, but my first Amazon purchase on Tuesday morning was one I really think everyone should know about.</description></item><item><title>This TikTok-viral breader bowl is up to 50% off for Prime Day 2025</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/08/amazon-prime-day-kitchen-gadget-breader-bowl-deal/84500313007/</link><description>I spend a lot of time in my kitchen, andthis viral better breader batter bowl(say that five times fast!) is at the top of my list to purchase to make some meal prep easier. I found this kitchen tool ina viral TikTok recipe for fried chicken, and it made breading the chicken look so much easier. I just made this recipe again recently and was so mad at myself for not buying this bowl beforehand! But it's on sale now duringAmazon's massive four-day Prime shopping event, so it's the perfect time to add it to your kitchen.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day expands to 4 days for the first time…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/02/when-amazon-prime-day-deals-discounts-how-long-lasts-dates-membership-price/84330089007/</link><description>Summertime is here, which means beach days, the Fourth of July and, of course,Amazon Prime Day.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Memorial reveals the pain and resilience of enslaved…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/08/florida-slave-memorial-aims-for-reflection-and-healing/84491901007/</link><description>It is a visibly striking piece of art.</description></item><item><title>Where does Florida stand on its latest mass immigration…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/politics/2025/07/08/florida-mass-deportation-legal-alligator-alcatraz-open/84502215007/</link><description>So far, more than 1,000 migrants have been detained under the state’s aggressive“Operation Tidal Wave,”a crackdown that officials say could become a model for federal immigration enforcement. The operation gained traction in May after a joint ICE raid led to over 100 arrests at construction sites in Tallahassee.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day 2025: Everything you need to know about…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/08/how-much-amazon-prime-video-subscription-costs-price-what-included-streaming-service/84502361007/</link><description>AnAmazon Prime membershipcomes packed with many perks and benefits, including access toPrime Video.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County announces leader of forthcoming Stormwater Department</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/08/sarasota-county-names-director-of-new-stormwater-department/84498355007/</link><description>Sarasota County announces leader of forthcoming Stormwater Department</description></item><item><title>Booker, Sarasota High among Sarasota Schools that improved grades</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/07/08/school-grades-2025-sarasota-county-maintains-top-state-ranking/84502203007/</link><description>Booker, Sarasota High among Sarasota Schools that improved grades</description></item><item><title>Nathan Benderson Park doesn't need massive, wasteful sports facilityTerry Galvin Guest columnist</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/08/benderson-park-rowing-sports-money/84505188007/</link><description>I have loved and supportedNathan Benderson Parksince before it held its first event more than 15 years ago.</description></item><item><title>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police Chief</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/manatee/2025/07/08/josh-cramer-officially-replaces-controversial-melanie-bevan-as-chief/84507671007/</link><description>It's official. Josh Cramer is Bradenton's new Police Chief</description></item></channel></rss>