<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 23:04:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Maryland pizza chain makes Sarasota County debut</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/07/09/maryland-ledo-pizza-chain-opens-first-sarasota-restaurant-north-port/84495397007/</link><description>Maryland pizza chain makes Sarasota County debut</description></item><item><title>Charlie Woods, Cameron Kuchar commit to Junior Players</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/golf/pga-tour/2025/07/09/charlie-woods-cameron-kuchar-junior-players-championship-tiger-woods-pga-tour/84518357007/</link><description>Charlie Woodsand Cameron Kuchar will double the number of sons of past Players Championship winners to compete in the American Junior Golf AssociationJunior Players ChampionshipAug. 28-31 at the Players Stadium Course at TPC Sawgrass.</description></item><item><title>Vote: Who is Sarasota-Manatee's all-time best state championship softball team</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/softball/2025/07/07/who-is-sarasota-manatee-all-time-best-state-championship-softball-team-poll/84457578007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the fast-pitch softball teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Highly-rated SodaStream Terra Bundle: 47% Prime Day savings</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/sodastream-terra-bundle-sale-amazon-prime-day-deal-2025/84515941007/</link><description>With thesummer heaturging us to stay hydrated, are you finding it tough to choose healthier drink options when the same old taste of water just gets boring? And let's not forget how thecost of sodas, juices, and pre-bottled drinks has skyrocketed over the last few years. Well, then it might be time to grab aSodaStreamand dive into the world of making your own bubbly sparkling waters right at home!</description></item><item><title>10 Prime Day beauty deals currently in my Amazon shopping cart 🛒</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/amazon-prime-day-sale-editor-approved-beauty-deals-im-shopping/84512254007/</link><description>ShoppingAmazon Prime Dayisn't for the faint of heart; with over 300,000 live deals scattered all across Amazon's site, it can be overwhelming knowing where to even look—and more importantly, which deals are truly worth buying.</description></item><item><title>These 10 supplements are up to 72% off during Prime Day</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/shopping/2025/07/09/prime-day-deals-supplements-creatine-iron-vitamin-d-protein-more-on-sale/84479237007/</link><description>I don't gatekeep my health secrets. I'm on a GLP-1 for weight loss, but I also pair it with a substantial list ofsupplements to reduce the side effects of the injections, while maximizing the health benefits. Because my kitchen counter looks like a pharmacy, I'm usually on the lookout for good deals on supplements whenever I'm running low.</description></item><item><title>Jacksonville’s Nic Advances to Love Island USA Season 7…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/07/09/love-island-usa-season-finale-nic-vansteenberghe-florida/84516131007/</link><description>With the 'Love Island USA' Season 7 finaleairing Sunday, July 13, Jacksonville native Nick Vansteenberghe has emerged as one of the season’s standout Islanders and a fan favorite to watch.</description></item><item><title>Craving a Snack Wrap? Fan-favorite returns to McDonald's…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/mcdonald-snack-wrap-menu-new-spicy-mcmuffin/84523099007/</link><description>McDonald's isbringing back the Snack Wrap for good,after years of fans demanding its return.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day deals on pool pumps, vacuums, LED…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/07/09/how-long-amazon-prime-days-pool-pumps-vacuums-led-lights-deals-discounts/84502325007/</link><description>Today marks the second day of Amazon’s biggest online shopping sale of the year.Amazon Prime Daystarted as a one-day sales event in 2015 to celebrate the company’s 20th anniversary.</description></item><item><title>Nathan Benderson Park doesn't need massive, wasteful…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/07/08/benderson-park-rowing-sports-money/84505188007/</link><description>I have loved and supportedNathan Benderson Parksince before it held its first event more than 15 years ago.</description></item><item><title>Venice City Council gives green light to SMH to build…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/07/09/next-buildings-on-smh-venice-campus-could-be-as-hight-as-150-feet-tall/84500472007/</link><description>Venice City Council gives green light to SMH to build…</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County moves $10 million for stormwater drainage improvements</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/07/09/sarasota-county-puts-more-money-for-phillippi-after-24-storm-flooding/84503514007/</link><description>Sarasota County moves $10 million for stormwater drainage improvements</description></item><item><title>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/07/09/sarasota-officers-rescue-driver-after-fiery-wreck/84513084007/</link><description>Sarasota officers free woman trapped in burning car after crash</description></item><item><title>Manatee County earns highest-ever grade on Florida school report card</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/07/09/manatee-schools-see-gains-in-science-graduation-and-a-rated-campuses/84517624007/</link><description>Manatee County earns highest-ever grade on Florida school report card</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Florida's appeal to enforce immigration law</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/07/09/supreme-court-rejects-florida-appeal-to-enforce-immigration-law-uthmeier/84523556007/</link><description>WASHINGTON − Florida can't enforce a controversialnew lawtargeting undocumented immigrants entering Florida, theSupreme Courtdetermined on July 9 in rejecting anemergency appeal from the state.</description></item></channel></rss>