<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:04:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Florida's top immigration cops don't use body-worn camerasstate</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/08/11/florida-immigration-officers-dont-use-body-worn-cameras-for-arrests/85358888007/</link><description>It took 12 minutes before a Florida Highway Patrol officer checked Griselda Vazquez-Duran for injuries after bashing the driver's window of her gray GMC with a baton.</description></item><item><title>Cardinal Mooney-Aquinas game voted best 2025 matchup to watchfootball</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/12/cardinal-mooney-st-thomas-aquinas-game-voted-best-football-matchup-in-2025/85557299007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Out of all the games, theHerald-Tribuneselected 14 marquee matchupsfor the 2025 football season, including a couple of preseason classics.</description></item><item><title>ULA mission: Did your Florida city make rocket launch visibility map?news</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/12/rocket-launch-florida-vulcan-canaveral-visibility-map-time/85622359007/</link><description>Godspeed, Vulcan!</description></item><item><title>Seeking thrills or chills? What's on new Royal Caribbean cruise shipnews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/12/royal-caribbean-star-of-the-seas-port-canaveral-florida-cruise-ship/85622389007/</link><description>Royal Caribbean's giant new ship, Star of the Seas,arrived in Brevard CountyAug. 9, and will provide another travel option for Florida cruisers.</description></item><item><title>Tropical Storm Erin spaghetti models, path. Sarasota impact?hurricane</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricane/2025/08/12/noaa-nhc-tropical-storm-erin-hurricane-spaghetti-models-path-track-sarasota-florida/85627509007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Erinis expected to gradually strengthen Aug. 13 and could become a hurricane by late on Aug. 14, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Trump discusses reclassifying marijuana. Is weed legal in Florida?news</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/12/donald-trump-reclassifying-marijuana-florida-weed-laws/85622388007/</link><description>PresidentDonald Trumpannounced that his administration is consideringreclassifying marijuanaas a less dangerous drug and will make a decision in the coming weeks.</description></item><item><title>Will Floridians get a rebate or stimulus check in 2025? What to knownews</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/12/trump-stimulus-checks-american-worker-rebate-act-hawley-florida/85622394007/</link><description>President Donald Trumphas shared a possible plan to givemoneyfromtariffsback to taxpayers.</description></item><item><title>How has growth changed in North Port's Wellen Park?Venice</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/12/wellen-park-growth-continues-as-some-home-prices-soar-past-forecasts/85465503007/</link><description>NORTH PORT – Six years ago, when the designs of many of Wellen Park planned neighborhoods were being approved, developers foresaw a community of homes selling for more than $500,000 to upwards of $1 million.</description></item><item><title>Cameras to capture school-zone speeders in Sarasota and Bradentonsarasota</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/12/school-zone-speed-cameras-return-to-bradenton-and-sarasota/85515451007/</link><description>It's back to school time for students in Bradenton and Sarasota. Speeders beware.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota city water customers will pay new convenience fee in Octobersarasota</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/12/sarasota-will-no-longer-absorb-convenience-fees-for-water-customers/85609318007/</link><description>The city of Sarasota announced on Aug. 11 that it will launch arevamped online payment systemfor its water utility customers.</description></item><item><title>Review: ‘Don’t Dress for Dinner’ closes FST summer with hearty laughstheater</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/theater/2025/08/12/review-1960s-french-farce-gets-laughs-in-new-fst-summer-production/85599407007/</link><description>If you tried to explain all the romantic combinations, misdirections and plot twists that make up the comedy “Don’t Dress for Dinner” without giving too much away, your head might explode from confusion and you’d miss the joyous giddyness of watching it all unfold before you.</description></item></channel></rss>