<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:31:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk, part 2: How I stopped hyperventilating</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/16/marni-jameson-my-rightsizing-part-2-how-i-stopped-hyperventilating/85453008007/</link><description>Now that my husband, DC, and I had sold the Happier Yellow House to the first buyer who saw it, we were quite suddenly, technically, homeless. Yeep! My head was literally spinning. I need to sit down often and put my head between my knees.</description></item><item><title>Who do you think is the most famous Floridian? Vote top 50 in our poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/27/famous-floridians-florida-vote-poll-actors-singers-politicians/85846670007/</link><description>Florida has a long history of attracting therich,talentedandfamous, while producing somelegends and iconsitself.</description></item><item><title>When does 'Saturday Night Live' premiere? Big changes coming to cast</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/28/snl-lorne-michaels-cast-changes-premiere-schedule-florida/85863062007/</link><description>Live from New York, it's getting closer toSaturday Night Live!</description></item><item><title>Looking for Labor Day fun? 5 top events in Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/28/best-things-to-do-sarasota-labor-day-weekend-2025/85779365007/</link><description>Looking forfun waysto spend the long Labor Day weekend? From the waters of Sarasota Bay to the streets of Englewood, the holiday brings a mix of family-friendly events and more adult-oriented entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Who are the high school boys swimmers to watch this season?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/swimming-diving/2025/08/28/top-high-school-boys-swimmers-in-sarasota-manatee-area-for-2025/85715433007/</link><description>After the Sarasota boys swim team claimed the 2023 FHSAA Class 4A State Championship crown, the Sailors slipped to fourth place as a team in 2024. Right behind the Riverview Rams in third place.</description></item><item><title>High School Football: Week 2 Sarasota, Manatee game previews and predictions</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/28/week-2-previews-for-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-games/85758026007/</link><description>Preview capsules and predictions for high school football games being played by Sarasota and Manatee County teams on Friday, Aug. 29, 2025.Game times are 7:30 p.m. unless otherwise listed.</description></item><item><title>Big talk and tiny results: Corcoran's disastrous reign…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/columns/guest/2025/08/27/new-college-spending-woke-athletes/85830702007/</link><description>In 2023New College of FloridaPresidentRichard Corcorandemanded a change to the school's mascot.</description></item><item><title>Owner seeks to rezone 10.7-acre site for residential in…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/28/owner-of-parcel-at-auburn-and-border-roads-seeks-zoning-for-54-homes/85819457007/</link><description>VENICE – A proposal toestablish city zoning on 10.7 acres in a rapidly growing area of Venicewith the potential for residential development will be showcased in an online workshop this week.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota County to introduce processing fees for online…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/28/sarasota-county-will-allow-new-online-payment-processor-to-charge-fees/85829170007/</link><description>Sarasota County residents will soon begin paying small transaction fees for their online charges for local public services, after a vote by the County Commission on Aug. 26.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota City Commission pushes forward in city manager…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/28/city-manager-search-continues-for-sarasota-city-commission/85834852007/</link><description>During its special meeting on Aug. 26, the Sarasota City Commission decided to interview all three city manager search firms that it confirmed as finalists during its July 7 meeting.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota artists, activists grieve and mobilize after sidewalk art ban</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/28/sarasota-artists-activists-grieve-and-mobilize-after-sidewalk-art-ban/85864266007/</link><description>Beck Laynesobbed as she walked along the colored sidewalksoutside the Social Equity through Education (SEE) Alliance building, filled with artwork from artists like Layne, on August 27.</description></item><item><title>Woman sentenced to 35 years in prison for role in deadly drive-by shooting</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/courts/2025/08/28/woman-sentenced-to-35-years-for-2022-drive-by-shooting-that-killed-teen-sarasota/85846367007/</link><description>A 20-year-old woman was sentenced to 35 years in prison in connection with the2022 drive-by shooting on Palmadelia Avenue in Sarasotathat left one teen dead and two others injured.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota city commissioner advocated for project while paid by developer</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/investigations/2025/08/28/as-mayor-and-vice-mayor-battie-advocated-for-employers-development/75075871007/</link><description>During Kyle Battie's first years on the Sarasota City Commission, records show he was employed by a shell corporation owned by a local developer, while helping that developer gain access to city officials, a Herald-Tribune investigation has found.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota crews remove 'PrideWalk' mural as required by Gov. DeSantis</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/28/sarasota-crews-remove-pridewalk-mural-as-required-by-gov-desantis/85869529007/</link><description>The city of Sarasota beganremoving Project PRIDE SRQ’s “PrideWalk” art installationon Aug. 28.</description></item></channel></rss>