<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:45:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Tampa rapper Doechii snubs Florida during upcoming tour. See all shows</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/04/doechii-live-from-the-swamp-tour-florida-dates-tickets/85502384007/</link><description>Doechiiis hitting the road this fall!</description></item><item><title>'Bachelor in Paradise' had 2 rose ceremonies last night. See recap</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/08/05/bachelor-in-paradise-how-watch-episode-week-six-recap/85521121007/</link><description>Last night's episode of "Bachelor in Paradise"raised the stakes for the contestants, who now all have a chance at going home up to $500,000 richer, depending on how strong their relationships become in the next few weeks.</description></item><item><title>29 local restaurants get high-priority violations, 6 ace inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/05/sarasota-restaurants-get-high-priority-violations-health-inspections/85509841007/</link><description>29 local restaurants get high-priority violations, 6 ace inspections</description></item><item><title>2023 Cardinal Mooney state champion win All-Time Best Football Team Poll</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/2023-cardinal-mooney-wins-all-time-best-football-team-poll/85511663007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune has gone back and documented the area football teams that have won state championships.</description></item><item><title>Who's committed, who has offers: IMG Academy's top football recruits</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/recruiting-img-academy-football-recruits-jake-kreul-breck-kolojay-preston-carey/85471053007/</link><description>IMG Academy has a new head coach, and plenty of transfers ready to make an impact.</description></item><item><title>Fall is here as Spirit Halloween shares list of…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/05/spirit-halloween-florida-locations-list-hiring-jobs/85525222007/</link><description>Release the spooks!</description></item><item><title>Spirit Airlines adding new Caribbean routes from this…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/05/spirit-airlines-adds-fort-lauderdale-flights-to-belize-grand-cayman/85529735007/</link><description>Spirit Airlines is ready to take you to the island with what the company says are the first nonstop flights from Fort Lauderdale to thesunny Caribbean destinationsof Belize City and Grand Cayman, according to a release Aug. 5.</description></item><item><title>Lake Mary, Florida plays for return to LLWS! Here's how…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/baseball/2025/08/05/florida-llws-schedule-lake-mary-little-league-world-series-regionals-championship/85526135007/</link><description>The boys fromLake Mary, Floridaare one win away from returning to Williamsport for the2025 Little League World Series.</description></item><item><title>Football Recruiting 2026: Florida high school summer…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/06/11/2026-football-recruiting-summer-commitment-tracker-high-school/84073516007/</link><description>It's summertime.</description></item><item><title>Here's the 2025 team-by-team Sarasota and Manatee high…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/07/30/2025-team-by-team-high-school-football-schedules-sarasota-manatee-counties/85306452007/</link><description>The 2025 high school football season begins with Florida High School Athletic Association Kickoff Classics on Aug. 14. The regular season begins Aug. 21 and runs through Oct. 31 (with the exception of IMG which will play into November) with most teams playing 10 games in 11 weeks.</description></item><item><title>POLL: Vote for best Sarasota, Manatee high school football game for 2025 season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/05/best-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-game-of-2025-season-poll/85359362007/</link><description>There are plenty of quality games on the high school football slates this year in Manatee and Sarasota counties. Area teams are opting for out-of-area, and in some cases, out-of-state opponents when filling out their regular-season schedule. Even some of the fall classics have teams travelling up to 3 hours for a game that does not count toward their record for a chance to beef up their slates.</description></item><item><title>Four candidates in running for Manatee County Schools superintendent</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/education/2025/08/05/nationwide-superintendent-search-narrows-to-four-candidates-in-manatee/85475865007/</link><description>Four candidates in running for Manatee County Schools superintendent</description></item><item><title>Sarasota City Commission rejects development at Temple Beth Sholom</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/05/city-commission-rejects-development-at-temple-beth-shalom-synagogue/85506773007/</link><description>Sarasota City Commission rejects development at Temple Beth Sholom</description></item><item><title>FPL customers facing largest utility rate hike in U.S. history</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/2025/08/05/florida-power-and-light-pushes-largest-rate-hike-in-u-s-history/85508181007/</link><description>Florida Power and Lightwill face considerable opposition next week when it goes before a typically utility-friendly Florida Public Service Commission with a request that board members approve what would be the biggest rate hike in Florida and U.S., history.</description></item></channel></rss>