<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Award-winning actor Robert Redford dies at 89</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/movies/2025/09/16/robert-redford-dead-movies-sundance/5586910002/</link><description>Robert Redford, the legendary leading man with boyish good looks and charm who used his star power to advocate for independent filmmaking,environmentalismand LGBTQ rights, has died at age 89.</description></item><item><title>'Love Island Games' season 2: Here's when it drops, how to watch</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/2025/09/16/love-island-games-new-season-watch-premiere/86172710007/</link><description>Just got a text! Summer may be over, but the "Love Island" fun is far from it.</description></item><item><title>Vote for the Herald-Tribune Girls Athlete of the Week for Sept. 8-13</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/athlete-of-the-week/2025/09/15/sarasota-herald-tribune-girls-athlete-of-week-poll-for-september-8-13/86112548007/</link><description>Each week The Herald-Tribune staff will select nominees for the Herald-Tribune Boys Athlete of the Week poll sponsored by Central Florida Behavioral Network, Inc. Nominees are derived from scores and stats emailed in by Sarasota and Manatee county coaches during the week tohtincoming@gmail.com. Readers can then vote in the online poll to determine the Boys Athlete of the Week.</description></item><item><title>Florida high school football: Spruce Creek, DeLand debut on Super 25</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/16/img-florida-super-25-football-usa-today-high-school-deland-spruce-creek-academy-northwestern-aquinas/86169834007/</link><description>After a chaotic first month of the season, things may be starting to settle down in Florida.</description></item><item><title>How long does it take to download iOS 26? What Apple users should know</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/16/apple-ios-26-release-date-compatible-iphones-florida/86173299007/</link><description>iOS 26is officially here!</description></item><item><title>Sarasota couple charged with neglect after 5-year-old found in filth</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/15/disturbing-discovery-of-severely-neglected-girl-made-in-sarasota/86165054007/</link><description>Inside a Sarasota home that smelled like cigarettes and motor oil, investigators dislodged a baby gate and entered the bedroom.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota Memorial Hospital leads clinical study of new…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/09/16/sarasota-memorial-hospital-leads-clinical-study-of-new-thyroid-nodule-treatment/86109651007/</link><description>Sarasota Memorial Hospital is part of a multicenter studyto capture the clinical and quality of life benefits of a new ablation treatment for non-cancerous thyroid nodules.</description></item><item><title>Where will AdventHealth build a new free-standing ER?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/16/adventhealth-to-expand-healthcare-in-punta-gorda-with-free-standing-er/85997032007/</link><description>CHARLOTTE COUNTY – AdventHealth plans toexpand its footprint in Charlotte County, with a new free-standing emergency department off Jones Loop Road, west of Punta Gorda Airport.</description></item><item><title>Flamingo? Scrub jay? Florida’s official bird battle…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/state/2025/09/16/lawmakers-file-bill-to-boot-mockingbird-as-floridas-state-bird/86162822007/</link><description>Two Republican House members have signaled they are prepared to continue one of the statehouse’s longest running political feuds.</description></item><item><title>Don't want AI on your phone? Here's how to turn off…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/16/apple-intelligence-new-features-latest-ios-how-turn-off/86166848007/</link><description>Apple's latest major update with iOS 26,now available for download, brings anew, translucent and bubbly interface, streamlined menus, and new features powered by Apple Intelligence including call screening, emoji combination and more.</description></item><item><title>3 celestial objects prepare to form conjunction. How to…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/09/16/moon-venus-conjunction-when-florida/86176614007/</link><description>Threecelestial bodies are about to meet upfor one night in September in a cosmic party that should be widely visible in the United States – including Florida.</description></item><item><title>11 local restaurants get high-priority violations, 17 ace inspections</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/09/16/sarasota-restaurants-high-priority-health-violations/86162811007/</link><description>Ourdigital databaseof restaurant health inspections is updated regularly with the latest information on which Sarasota, Bradenton and Venice area restaurants passed or failed.</description></item><item><title>Who leads The Herald-Tribune Top 10 Football Power Rankings after Week 4?</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/09/16/top-10-sarasota-manatee-high-school-football-team-rankings-after-week-4/86081656007/</link><description>It's been a month since the high school football season began, which has allowed for enough games to figure out which teams are the best.</description></item><item><title>Florida: The (Stupid) Sunshine State</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/opinion/letters/2025/09/16/florida-stupid-vaccines-kirk-trump/86169123007/</link><description>I spent most of my life living in Pennsylvania until retiring and spending the last eight years in Florida.</description></item><item><title>$9.4M project to rehabilitate Manasota Beach Road bridge approved</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/09/16/sarasota-county-approves-9-4m-manasota-beach-road-bridge-fixes/86063836007/</link><description>Sarasota County is preparing a major rehabilitation project for the Manasota Beach Road drawbridge, which hasn’t seen a major touch-up in over two decades.</description></item></channel></rss>