<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Herald-Tribune (Custom RSS - Broad Article Grab)</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com</link><description>A personal RSS feed with broader article scraping from heraldtribune.com</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:07:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Marni's sentimental guide to giving the past a presence in our homes</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/05/10/marni-jameson-a-guide-to-giving-the-past-a-presence-in-our-homes/83460519007/</link><description>Over the years, I have earned the reputation as the stuff police. I am forever nagging you to purge, declutter, toss, donate, edit, dump, oust, clear, lighten up and let go. But today, sit down, I am going to sentimentally suggest that some old things you should keep.</description></item><item><title>Walking the rightsizing walk. Here's why I decided to sell the house</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/lifestyle/real-estate/2025/08/09/marni-jameson-heres-why-i-decided-to-sell-my-happy-yellow-house/85452850007/</link><description>I should know by now, if you venture into an exploratory hypothetical conversation with a real estate broker, you might as well start packing. One casual conversation with a broker friend started the house hurricane.</description></item><item><title>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 14-17</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/events/2025/08/14/things-to-do-sarasota-bradenton-aug-14-17/85580403007/</link><description>Top 5 things to do in Sarasota-Manatee this weekend, Aug. 14-17</description></item><item><title>Vote for best 2025 high school football team in Manatee, Sarasota area</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/14/best-manatee-sarasota-area-2025-high-school-football-team-vote/85531382007/</link><description>High school football teams are getting ready to take the field for the first time in the 2025 season on Friday, Aug. 15.</description></item><item><title>Football: Thompkins scored 3 TDs, IMG routs The First Academy</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/15/img-academy-the-first-academy-football-kickoff-classic/85656182007/</link><description>ORLANDO —Le'Khy Thompkinshas only been atIMG Academyfor a few weeks, but the big running back certainly seems to be fitting in.</description></item><item><title>Nonprofit will test for 'forever chemicals' in North Port water</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/venice/2025/08/15/suncoast-waterkeeeper-launches-free-testing-for-forever-chemicals/85638893007/</link><description>NORTH PORT –Suncoast Waterkeeper is launching a free water testing programin the city, designed to raise awareness about the presence of “forever chemicals” in water.</description></item><item><title>Artist Series sets past favorites and rising stars for…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/15/music-stars-and-emerging-artists-mark-artist-series-30th-season/85546679007/</link><description>Artist Series sets past favorites and rising stars for…</description></item><item><title>Top 5 concerts this week in Sarasota, Manatee counties</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/music/2025/08/15/top-5-concerts-this-week-near-me-in-sarasota-bradenton-palmetto/85528088007/</link><description>As we enter mid-August, we're definitely in the slow time of the year for Sarasota area events, including live music. However, we still found five items for this week's concert picks installment, starting with a few notable tribute shows.</description></item><item><title>Fall time change: Here's when daylight saving time ends…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/2025/08/15/when-time-changes-daylight-saving-fall-back/85654814007/</link><description>The years-long struggle to decidewhether or not to “lock the clock”is continuing in the halls of Congress, meaning as of August 2025, we will still “fall back” in a few months.</description></item><item><title>What's the latest path, spaghetti models for Tropical…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/15/tropical-storm-erin-spaghetti-models-tracker-path-florida-impacts/85670146007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Erin is expected tobecome a hurricaneFriday, Aug. 15, and then become a "powerful" Category 4 storm within the next three days, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>Erin expected to strengthen into Category 4 hurricane…</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2025/08/15/hurricane-erin-path-spaghetti-models-tracker-florida/85670066007/</link><description>Tropical Storm Erin is now expected to become a Category 4 hurricane, with maximum sustained winds of 130-mph, according to the latest advisory from theNational Hurricane Center.</description></item><item><title>SSAA Previews: Bradenton Christian, ODA, Saint Stephen's, Sarasota Christian</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/sports/high-school/football/2025/08/15/2025-ssaa-football-previews-bradenton-christian-out-of-door-saint-stephens-sarasota-christian/85542079007/</link><description>The Herald-Tribune will get you ready for the 2025 high school football season. Here are previews for the teams competing in the Sunshine State Athletic Association.</description></item><item><title>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now, before season</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/entertainment/dining/2025/08/15/best-legendary-sarasota-restaurants-and-bars-to-visit-now/84509634007/</link><description>10 iconic Sarasota restaurants and bars to visit now, before season</description></item><item><title>Meadows Community to lease golf course to Benderson Development</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/14/mca-negotiating-long-term-lease-contract-with-benderson-development/85647977007/</link><description>Meadows Community to lease golf course to Benderson Development</description></item><item><title>Florida transportation department to resurface Sarasota downtown road</title><link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/story/news/local/sarasota/2025/08/15/one-mile-stretch-of-u-s-301-set-for-7-1-million-repaving-in-2026/85627426007/</link><description>Everyhardened Sarasota motoristknows the stretch of Washington Boulevard near downtown can get pretty gnarly, and it may get a little bit worse before it gets a little bit better.</description></item></channel></rss>